<HTMLQuestion xmlns="http://mechanicalturk.amazonaws.com/AWSMechanicalTurkDataSchemas/2011-11-11/HTMLQuestion.xsd">
<HTMLContent><![CDATA[
<!DOCTYPE html>
<html>
<head>
<meta http-equiv='Content-Type' content='text/html; charset=UTF-8'/>
<script type='text/javascript' src='https://s3.amazonaws.com/mturk-public/externalHIT_v1.js'></script>
<script src="https://sdk.amazonaws.com/js/aws-sdk-2.142.0.min.js"></script>
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://stackpath.bootstrapcdn.com/bootstrap/4.2.1/css/bootstrap.min.css" integrity="sha384-GJzZqFGwb1QTTN6wy59ffF1BuGJpLSa9DkKMp0DgiMDm4iYMj70gZWKYbI706tWS" crossorigin="anonymous">
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://www.w3schools.com/w3css/4/w3.css">
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://unpkg.com/bootstrap-material-design@4.1.1/dist/css/bootstrap-material-design.min.css" integrity="sha384-wXznGJNEXNG1NFsbm0ugrLFMQPWswR3lds2VeinahP8N0zJw9VWSopbjv2x7WCvX" crossorigin="anonymous">
<style>
  dt{
    font-size: medium;
  }

  dd{
    margin-bottom: 1rem; 
    margin-left: 0;
  }
  
  .card-text{
    margin-bottom: 2rem;
  }

  h5{
    font-weight: bold;
  }
  .tablink{
    font-weight: 600;
  }

  .btn-lg{
    font-size: 2rem;
    line-height: 4rem;
  }
  h2{
    margin-top: 1rem;
  }
  p{
    font-size: 1rem;
  }
</style>
</head>

<body>
<section class="container mb-3 mt-3">
  <fieldset class="shadow bg-white mb-3">
<div class="w3-container">
  <h2 class="text-info" style="font-weight: bolder">Instructions and Examples</h2>
  <div id="Instructions" class="w3-container ins w3-animate-opacity" style="display:block">
    <h2>Instructions</h2>
    <p>Read the premise, hypothesis and realation, select a segment from premise that can determine the relation between premise and hypothesis.</p>
    <ul>
      <!-- We are adding a template variable below which we will replace with an actual link in our code later -->
      <li>Read the premise, hypothesis and the relation.</li>
      <li>On the basis of your own judgement, select a "sequential" segment from premise that can determine the relation between premise and hypothesis.</li>
      <li>The length is not restricted, as long as the segment provides sufficient informations.</li>
      <li>Copy the segment from premise and paste it into the following box.</li>
      <li><strong>SPAM and non-sequential segments will be rejected.</strong></li>
      </ul>
    <p>The following section is the definition of the three realations, which comes from the RTE-5 task guideline. If you are familiar with NLI tasks such as SNLI, MNLI, RTE, you can skip the section below.</p>
    <p>We define textual entailment as a directional relationship between a pair of text fragments, which we call the "Premise" and the "Hypothesis". We say that: </p>
    <p><strong><i>Premise entails Hypothesis, if a human reading premise would infer that hypothesis is most likely true. </i></strong></p>
    <p>For example, given assumed common background knowledge of the business news domain and the following premise: </p>
    <p style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><strong><i>Premise1 Internet media company Yahoo Inc. announced Monday it is buying Overture Services Inc. in a $1.63-billion (U.S.) cash-and-stock deal that will bolster its on-line search capabilities.</i></strong></p>
    <p>the following hypothesis is entailed:</p>
    <ul>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.1 Yahoo boutght Overture</i></p></li>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.2 Overture acquired by Yahoo</i></p></li>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.3 Overture was bought</i></p></li>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.4 Yahoo is an internet company</i></p></li>
    </ul>
    <p>For example, the following hypothesis are contradicted by Premise above:</p>
    <ul>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.5 Overture bought Yahoo</i></p></li>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.6 Yahoo sold Overture</i></p></li>
    </ul>
    <p>While the following ones cannot be judged on the basis of Premise above:</p>
    <ul>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.7 Yahoo manufatures cars</i></p></li>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.8 Overture shareholders will receive $4.75 cash and 0.6108 Yahoo stock for each of their shares.</i></p></li>
    </ul>
  </div>
  
</div>
</fieldset>
<fieldset class="shadow bg-white mb-3">
  <div id="Entailment" class="w3-container ins w3-animate-opacity">
    <h2>Entailment Example</h2>
    <p>Here is a pair of premise and hypothesis with entailment relation. The following is the Segment you need to respond, which we also emphasize in the premise.</p>
    <ul>
      <dt style="font-size: medium;">Premise</dt>
      <dd style='margin-bottom: 1rem; margin-left: 0;'>CNN) -- Malawians are rallying behind <strong class="w3-text-deep-orange">Madonna as she awaits a ruling Friday on whether she can adopt a girl from the southern African nation. The pop star, who has three children</strong>, adopted a son from Malawi in 2006. She is seeking to adopt Chifundo "Mercy" James, 4. "Ninety-nine percent of the people calling in are saying, 'let her take the baby,' " said Marilyn Segula, a presenter at Capital FM, which broadcasts in at least five cities, including the capital, Lilongwe.</t>
      <h>Madonna has three children.</dd>
      <dt>Hypothesis</dt>
      <dd>Madonna has three children.</dd>
      <dt>Relation</dt>
      <dd>Entailment</dd>
      <dt>Segment (Your response)</dt>
      <dd>Madonna as she awaits a ruling Friday on whether she can adopt a girl from the southern African nation. The pop star, who has three children</dd>
    </ul>
  </div>
</fieldset>
<fieldset class="shadow bg-white mb-3">
  <div id="Neutral" class="w3-container ins w3-animate-opacity">
    <h2>Neutral Example</h2>
    <p>Here is a pair of premise and hypothesis with neutral relation. The following is the Segment you need to respond, which we also emphasize in the premise.</p> 
    <ul>
      <dt>Premise</dt>
      <dd>Concerns have been raised that potential leads in the hunt for missing York woman <strong class="w3-text-deep-orange">Claudia Lawrence are not being followed up quickly enough. It comes after hotel staff in Malton contacted police</strong> after a stranger in the bar expressed satisfaction when asked if the chef was still missing. The incident happened more than three weeks ago and staff said detectives had not yet been in touch. Police said leads were being assessed in a methodical and structured way.</dd>
      <dt>Hypothesis</dt>
      <dd>Claudia Lawrence resides in Malton.</dd>
      <dt>Relation</dt>
      <dd>Neutral</dd>
      <dt>Segment (Your response)</dt>
      <dd>Claudia Lawrence are not being followed up quickly enough. It comes after hotel staff in Malton contacted police</dd>
    </ul>
  </div>
</fieldset>
<fieldset class="shadow bg-white mb-3">
  <div id="Contradiction" class="w3-container ins w3-animate-opacity">
    <h2>Contradiction Example</h2>
    <p>Here is a pair of premise and hypothesis with Contradiction relation. The following is the Segment you need to respond, which we also emphasize in the premise.</p> 
    <ul>
      <dt>Premise</dt>
      <dd>But an O2 insider said there had been problems with a companies trying to sell the pass codes. Some people were "bound to have been turned away" because of fraudulent tickets. <strong class="w3-text-deep-orange">Led Zeppelin, formed in 1968</strong>, were one of the most influential bands of the 1970s with songs such as Whole Lotta Love and Stairway To Heaven. They split in 1980 after the death of the drummer John Bonham. Kenneth Donnell, 25, who was not born in 1980, spent 83,000 on two tickets in a BBC Children in Need auction.</dd>
      <dt>Hypothesis</dt>
      <dd>The band Led Zeppelin was formed in 1980.</dd>
      <dt>Relation</dt>
      <dd>Contradiction</dd>
      <dt>Segment (Your response)</dt>
      <dd>Led Zeppelin, formed in 1968</dd>
    </ul>
  </div>
</fieldset>
</section>

<!-- Questions Section -->
<section class="container">
  <div class="alert alert-danger text-center shadow" role="alert" style="font-weight: bold; font-size: large">
  All answers will be manually checked, SPAM and blank answers will be definitely rejected.
  </div>  
  <form name='mturk_form' method='post' id='mturk_form' action='https://www.mturk.com/mturk/externalSubmit'><input type='hidden' value='' name='assignmentId' id='assignmentId'/>
    <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 1</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Pop music producer Phil Spector who produced a large number of hit records in the 1960s and 1970s has been convicted of second-degree murder in the 2003 shooting of actress Lana Clarkson at the L.A. Superior Court in Los Angeles California. Spector currently 68 faces a minimum of 18 years in prison. Clarkson died February 3 2003 at Spector's mansion the "Pyrenees Castle" in Alhambra California after returning home with Spector for a drink after they met during her shift at a nightclub where she worked as a hostess. Spector was arrested after police were called to the mansion finding Clarkson dead of a gunshot wound; Spector insisted that her death was an "accidental suicide"</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Actress Lana Clarkson killed music producer Phil Spector.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Contradiction</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="281" id="281" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 2</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">The memorandum came in a series of agreements between Chinese Premier Wen Jiabao and Indian Prime Minister Manmohan Singh during Jiabao's state visit to India April 9-12 at Singh's invitation. India is expected to provide the funding architectural design landscape planning a Buddha idol and other materials for the completed temple. China is offering to provide official cooperation and permits and facilitate the travel of Indian architects and other construction experts to the site. The temple is planned to be located on 2667 square meters of land provided by the Chinese government.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Manmohan Singh is employed by India.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="282" id="282" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 3</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Senator Dunn started off the meeting by thanking the panelists and parents for showing their support by attending. "We are trying to address a very very important issue. What's the issue? We have high rates of cancer leukemia and respiratory problems in our children. Why are our kids sick? This is a very difficult question" he said. "What's causing the sickness in our children and how can we avoid it? We can all agree that no one wants to see another sick child in Santa Ana." The audience applauded. "Three weeks ago we heard from two parents and a teacher they told us about some deaths."</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Senator Dunn was born in Santa Ana.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Neutral</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="283" id="283" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 4</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">A stadium disaster has claimed well over a dozen lives in the Ivory Coast. A crush which may have occured after a wall collapse took place today at the Félix Houphouët-Boigny Stadium in Abidjan and according to interior minister Desire Tagro killed 22 people and wounded 132 others.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Desire Tagro is employed at the Félix Houphouët-Boigny Stadium.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Contradiction</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="284" id="284" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 5</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">According to the DNC chairman Howard Dean Senator Clinton has cancelled a speech at a Democratic National Committee meeting in Vienna Virginia and all other events today to deal with the situation. Her husband former US President Bill Clinton canceled a speech in New York City. Senators Barack Obama and John Edwards also have campaign offices down the street which have been closed and locked down along with the rest of downtown Rochester. Clinton's campaign offices located in Des Moines Iowa have also been closed on a temporary basis. "Unfortunately as some of you know there is a hostage situation in New Hampshire involving a Clinton campaign staff person. The details are sketchy at this time but understandably Sen.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Bill Clinton used to be President of the United States.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="285" id="285" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 6</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">After the murder of Grace's fiancee in 1979 she became a prosecutor in her native Georgia and later hosted her own show on Court TV followed later by her CNN tenure. Grace however has been criticized for her sense of ethics and allegedly playing fast and loose with the facts both in the courtroom and on the air. Grace's heated interview however was not without proper motive. The police had long suspected Melinda Duckett of involvement in her son's disappearance due to her behavior and contradictory statements. After Duckett's suicide police named her as a prime suspect in her son's disappearance. Recently they have announced that they have reason to believe that Trenton Duckett is still alive.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Grace was born in Georgia.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="286" id="286" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 7</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">The primary camera on the Hubble Space Telescope has shut down and is likely to only be restored to partial functionality according to reports from the National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA). The camera on the telescope known as the "Advanced Camera for Surveys" or ACS can be reactivated but will be restored to only one-third of its operating capacity. The restoration will probably take place in mid-February. The camera shut down over the weekend probably due to a failure of its backup power supply. It was the third such shutdown of the camera in the past calendar year. The camera had been operating on its backup power since June 30 2006 when engineers switched from the primary power supply ("Side A") to the backup ("Side B") due to a malfunction. A review board was convened on January 29 to assess all options and to decide on a course of action. Their findings will be reported to NASA on March 2 2007. The ACS developed jointly by four American agencies was installed in March of 2002.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">The Hubble Space Telescope was built in 2002.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Neutral</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="287" id="287" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 8</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">The art consultant who lived at the Bailey Howth Co Dublin died in August 2004. According to his will which went to probate last week he left an estate of €4607478. Mr Hunt a father of three who left everything to his wife Patricia had items valued at €1.7m on loan to the VA Museum in London and items on loan to the HSE valued at €300000. His own collection was valued at €1m plus and he had items on loan to the Hunt Museum valued at €487000. He also had almost €1m in various accounts.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Mr. Hunt died in August 2004.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="288" id="288" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 9</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Bill McMaster is running for the Family Coalition Party in the Ontario provincial election in the Lambton-Kent-Middlesex riding. Wikinews' Nick Moreau interviewed him regarding his values his experience and his campaign. Stay tuned for further interviews; every candidate from every party is eligible and will be contacted. Expect interviews from Liberals Progressive Conservatives New Democratic Party members Ontario Greens as well as members from the Family Coalition Freedom Communist Libertarian and Confederation of Regions parties as well as independents.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Bill McMaster is a resident of Middlesex.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Neutral</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="289" id="289" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 10</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">The United States will become the 67th signatory to the non-binding document which was proposed by France and the Netherlands and "condemn[s] the human rights violations based on sexual orientation or gender identity wherever they occur in particular the use of the death penalty on this ground extrajudicial summary or arbitrary executions the practice of torture and other cruel inhuman and degrading treatment or punishment arbitrary arrest or detention and deprivation of economic social and cultural rights including the right to health". Accepting the proposal which according to US State Department spokesman Robert Wood "commits us to no legal obligations" would nonetheless be a reversal from the Bush administration's refusal to sign.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Bush is in favor of the death penalty.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Neutral</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="290" id="290" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 11</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">At 11:38 a.m. the President of Georgia Mikheil Saakashvili announced the mobilization of reserve troops to withstand what he called "a large-scale military aggression" by Russia and called Russia to stop the "bombardment of Georgian towns." Prime Minister of Russia Vladimir Putin said that "it is regrettable that on the day before the opening of the Olympic Games the Georgian authorities have undertaken aggressive actions in South Ossetia."</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Vladimir Putin is the President of Georgia.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Contradiction</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="291" id="291" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 12</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Dr. Roger Vickers team used radar to locate three chambers within the rocky hill atop of which is the Temple of Taposiris Magna dedicated to the goddess Isis. The temple was constructed about 300 BC by Ptolemy II. The Supreme Council of Antiquities (SCA) expedition led by Hawass has yet to excavate the burial chambers 40 feet (12 meters) underground where they hope to find a crown or Egyptian hieroglyph cartouches revealing the names of royalty. The team will employ radar again on April 22. The Supreme Council of Antiquities expedition consists of Zahi Hawass Secretary General of the SCA and Martinez who has extensively researched the life of Cleopatra.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Temple of Taposiris Magna is dedicated to Ptolemy II.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Contradiction</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="292" id="292" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 13</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Pittsburgh Pennsylvania Local caterers get ready for big business as almost three thousand fans converge on the David L. Lawrence Convention Center over the Independence Day weekend for the world's largest ever furry convention Anthrocon 2007. Many hope to renew acquaintances or meet new friends. Others look to buy from dealers and artists or show off new artwork or costumes. Some attend to make money or even learn a thing or two. But one thing unites them: They're all there to have fun.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">The David L. Lawrence Convention Center is located in Pittsburgh.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="293" id="293" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 14</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Authorities say a parking enforcement officer issued a ticket for a pickup truck outside an Alabama emergency room while a woman lay dead inside the vehicle. Authorities say Rebecca Kate Haley 25 had been dead for at least seven hours when a ticket for illegal parking was put on the windshield. Police spokesman Sgt. Johnny Williams says the officer didn't see Haley because she was slumped over in the truck's cab. Drug paraphernalia was found in the truck but Williams said Tuesday that Haley's cause of death had not been determined. About an hour after the ticket was issued at 10:15 a.m. Monday outside the UAB hospital a passer-by spotted Haley. Police do not suspect foul play but are investigating whether someone else was in the truck before she died.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Rebecca Kate Haley was a drug user.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Neutral</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="294" id="294" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 15</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">In the 2006 municipal elections in Belgium the political party Vlaams Belang ("Flemish Cause") advanced in almost all municipalities just like the last elections. But its rise was brought to a halt in the cities Mechelen and also in its stronghold Antwerp. Vlaams Belang is considered by observers and opponents as a far right party supporting Flemish independence from Belgium and restricted immigration.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Mechelen is not far from Antwerp.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Neutral</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="295" id="295" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 16</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">A TORY Island hotelier who built a car park on the remains of a 150-year-old holiday home which burnt down may have to pay damages to its former owner. A High Court judge who is presiding over a legal row over a holiday home which allegedly "disappeared" and became a car park for an adjoining hotel yesterday said the case may be dealt with on the basis of unjust enrichment by the hotel. This requires someone who has obtained a benefit at the expense of another without a legal justification to provide compensation or restitution for their loss. Film maker Neville Presho (61) has brought a High Court action against hotelier Patrick Doohan and his hotel Ostan Thoraigh Comhlacth Teoranta for ongoing trespass and physical damage to his one-time holiday home on Tory Island off the Donegal coast.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Patrick Doohan is the owner of a hotel on Tory island.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="296" id="296" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 17</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">President Nicolas Sarkozy of France married the supermodel-turned-singer Carla Bruni at the Elysée Palace on Saturday witnesses said. The Italian news agency ANSA quoted Bruni's mother Marisa Borini as confirming the wedding had taken place. Two French radio stations said the marriage conducted by François Lebel mayor of Eighth Arrondissement of Paris where the Elysée Palace is situated. "The bride was wearing white and was ravishing" Lebel told Europe 1 radio without naming the couple. "The bridegroom wasn't bad either." Sarkozy and Bruni indicated last month that they planned to marry and made it clear that any wedding would be a private affair far from the eyes of the media. A French newspaper report on Jan. 14 that they had married proved unfounded.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Nicolas Sarkozy is married to Carla Bruni.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="297" id="297" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 18</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Japan has welcomed Greenpeace's decision to leave the Southern Ocean. Hideki Moronuki from Japan's Fisheries Agency is pleased the whaling mission will no longer be obstructed: "Although Greenpeace say that they're activities are peaceful their activities are really dangerous and illegal" he said. Protesters spent much of their time in the Southern Ocean in inflatable Zodiac boats placing themselves precariously between harpoons and whales. They escaped serious injury when the Japanese allegedly rammed their vessel and when a protester was pulled overboard by a harpoon rope. Activists were also blasted out of boats by water cannons.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Fisheries Agency is the employer of Hideki Moronuki.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="298" id="298" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 19</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Iraqi terrorists extended the ultimatum by calling Romanian Prima TV the station where two of the kidnapped journalists worked. The news director of Prima TV Dan Dumitru said he received a call from Iraq on late Tuesday in which he spoke both to the kidnappers and the journalists. The kidnappers gave the government a further 24 hours to withdraw their troops while the kidnapped journalists told Dumitru to put pressure on the Romanian government for the withdrawal of the troops. The three made a "final appeal" to the Romanian president Traian Basescu to withdraw the troops saying that the time of their killing was set on Wednesday at 14:00 UTC.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Primia TV is based in Romania.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="299" id="299" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 20</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">American Major League Baseball relief pitcher Joba Chamberlain of the New York Yankees returned a call to his sister after an 8-5 loss to the Boston Red Sox Sunday night. After speaking with his sister who was in Lincoln Nebraska he was in tears and being consoled by manager Joe Girardi. Joba's father Harlan Chamberlain 55 collapsed at his home in Lincoln and is currently at St. Elizabeth Regional Medical Center. Although the exact nature of his collapse is unknown Harlan a full-blooded Winnebago Native American has struggled with post-polio syndrome since childhood. He has been known to be in declining health in recent years.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Joba Chamberlain is the son of the 55-year-old Harlan.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="300" id="300" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>

  <button type="submit" class="btn btn-info btn-raised btn-lg btn-block" id='submitButton'>Submit</button>
  
</form>
</section>
<script language='Javascript'>turkSetAssignmentID();</script>

     

</body>
</html>

<script src="https://code.jquery.com/jquery-3.3.1.slim.min.js" integrity="sha384-q8i/X+965DzO0rT7abK41JStQIAqVgRVzpbzo5smXKp4YfRvH+8abtTE1Pi6jizo" crossorigin="anonymous"></script>
<script src="https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/popper.js/1.14.6/umd/popper.min.js" integrity="sha384-wHAiFfRlMFy6i5SRaxvfOCifBUQy1xHdJ/yoi7FRNXMRBu5WHdZYu1hA6ZOblgut" crossorigin="anonymous"></script>
<script src="https://stackpath.bootstrapcdn.com/bootstrap/4.2.1/js/bootstrap.min.js" integrity="sha384-B0UglyR+jN6CkvvICOB2joaf5I4l3gm9GU6Hc1og6Ls7i6U/mkkaduKaBhlAXv9k" crossorigin="anonymous"></script>
]]>
</HTMLContent>
<FrameHeight>0</FrameHeight>
</HTMLQuestion>