<HTMLQuestion xmlns="http://mechanicalturk.amazonaws.com/AWSMechanicalTurkDataSchemas/2011-11-11/HTMLQuestion.xsd">
<HTMLContent><![CDATA[
<!DOCTYPE html>
<html>
<head>
<meta http-equiv='Content-Type' content='text/html; charset=UTF-8'/>
<script type='text/javascript' src='https://s3.amazonaws.com/mturk-public/externalHIT_v1.js'></script>
<script src="https://sdk.amazonaws.com/js/aws-sdk-2.142.0.min.js"></script>
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://stackpath.bootstrapcdn.com/bootstrap/4.2.1/css/bootstrap.min.css" integrity="sha384-GJzZqFGwb1QTTN6wy59ffF1BuGJpLSa9DkKMp0DgiMDm4iYMj70gZWKYbI706tWS" crossorigin="anonymous">
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://www.w3schools.com/w3css/4/w3.css">
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://unpkg.com/bootstrap-material-design@4.1.1/dist/css/bootstrap-material-design.min.css" integrity="sha384-wXznGJNEXNG1NFsbm0ugrLFMQPWswR3lds2VeinahP8N0zJw9VWSopbjv2x7WCvX" crossorigin="anonymous">
<style>
  dt{
    font-size: medium;
  }

  dd{
    margin-bottom: 1rem; 
    margin-left: 0;
  }
  
  .card-text{
    margin-bottom: 2rem;
  }

  h5{
    font-weight: bold;
  }
  .tablink{
    font-weight: 600;
  }

  .btn-lg{
    font-size: 2rem;
    line-height: 4rem;
  }
  h2{
    margin-top: 1rem;
  }
  p{
    font-size: 1rem;
  }
</style>
</head>

<body>
<section class="container mb-3 mt-3">
  <fieldset class="shadow bg-white mb-3">
<div class="w3-container">
  <h2 class="text-info" style="font-weight: bolder">Instructions and Examples</h2>
  <div id="Instructions" class="w3-container ins w3-animate-opacity" style="display:block">
    <h2>Instructions</h2>
    <p>Read the premise, hypothesis and realation, select a segment from premise that can determine the relation between premise and hypothesis.</p>
    <ul>
      <!-- We are adding a template variable below which we will replace with an actual link in our code later -->
      <li>Read the premise, hypothesis and the relation.</li>
      <li>On the basis of your own judgement, select a "sequential" segment from premise that can determine the relation between premise and hypothesis.</li>
      <li>The length is not restricted, as long as the segment provides sufficient informations.</li>
      <li>Copy the segment from premise and paste it into the following box.</li>
      <li><strong>SPAM and non-sequential segments will be rejected.</strong></li>
      </ul>
    <p>The following section is the definition of the three realations, which comes from the RTE-5 task guideline. If you are familiar with NLI tasks such as SNLI, MNLI, RTE, you can skip the section below.</p>
    <p>We define textual entailment as a directional relationship between a pair of text fragments, which we call the "Premise" and the "Hypothesis". We say that: </p>
    <p><strong><i>Premise entails Hypothesis, if a human reading premise would infer that hypothesis is most likely true. </i></strong></p>
    <p>For example, given assumed common background knowledge of the business news domain and the following premise: </p>
    <p style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><strong><i>Premise1 Internet media company Yahoo Inc. announced Monday it is buying Overture Services Inc. in a $1.63-billion (U.S.) cash-and-stock deal that will bolster its on-line search capabilities.</i></strong></p>
    <p>the following hypothesis is entailed:</p>
    <ul>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.1 Yahoo boutght Overture</i></p></li>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.2 Overture acquired by Yahoo</i></p></li>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.3 Overture was bought</i></p></li>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.4 Yahoo is an internet company</i></p></li>
    </ul>
    <p>For example, the following hypothesis are contradicted by Premise above:</p>
    <ul>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.5 Overture bought Yahoo</i></p></li>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.6 Yahoo sold Overture</i></p></li>
    </ul>
    <p>While the following ones cannot be judged on the basis of Premise above:</p>
    <ul>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.7 Yahoo manufatures cars</i></p></li>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.8 Overture shareholders will receive $4.75 cash and 0.6108 Yahoo stock for each of their shares.</i></p></li>
    </ul>
  </div>
  
</div>
</fieldset>
<fieldset class="shadow bg-white mb-3">
  <div id="Entailment" class="w3-container ins w3-animate-opacity">
    <h2>Entailment Example</h2>
    <p>Here is a pair of premise and hypothesis with entailment relation. The following is the Segment you need to respond, which we also emphasize in the premise.</p>
    <ul>
      <dt style="font-size: medium;">Premise</dt>
      <dd style='margin-bottom: 1rem; margin-left: 0;'>CNN) -- Malawians are rallying behind <strong class="w3-text-deep-orange">Madonna as she awaits a ruling Friday on whether she can adopt a girl from the southern African nation. The pop star, who has three children</strong>, adopted a son from Malawi in 2006. She is seeking to adopt Chifundo "Mercy" James, 4. "Ninety-nine percent of the people calling in are saying, 'let her take the baby,' " said Marilyn Segula, a presenter at Capital FM, which broadcasts in at least five cities, including the capital, Lilongwe.</t>
      <h>Madonna has three children.</dd>
      <dt>Hypothesis</dt>
      <dd>Madonna has three children.</dd>
      <dt>Relation</dt>
      <dd>Entailment</dd>
      <dt>Segment (Your response)</dt>
      <dd>Madonna as she awaits a ruling Friday on whether she can adopt a girl from the southern African nation. The pop star, who has three children</dd>
    </ul>
  </div>
</fieldset>
<fieldset class="shadow bg-white mb-3">
  <div id="Neutral" class="w3-container ins w3-animate-opacity">
    <h2>Neutral Example</h2>
    <p>Here is a pair of premise and hypothesis with neutral relation. The following is the Segment you need to respond, which we also emphasize in the premise.</p> 
    <ul>
      <dt>Premise</dt>
      <dd>Concerns have been raised that potential leads in the hunt for missing York woman <strong class="w3-text-deep-orange">Claudia Lawrence are not being followed up quickly enough. It comes after hotel staff in Malton contacted police</strong> after a stranger in the bar expressed satisfaction when asked if the chef was still missing. The incident happened more than three weeks ago and staff said detectives had not yet been in touch. Police said leads were being assessed in a methodical and structured way.</dd>
      <dt>Hypothesis</dt>
      <dd>Claudia Lawrence resides in Malton.</dd>
      <dt>Relation</dt>
      <dd>Neutral</dd>
      <dt>Segment (Your response)</dt>
      <dd>Claudia Lawrence are not being followed up quickly enough. It comes after hotel staff in Malton contacted police</dd>
    </ul>
  </div>
</fieldset>
<fieldset class="shadow bg-white mb-3">
  <div id="Contradiction" class="w3-container ins w3-animate-opacity">
    <h2>Contradiction Example</h2>
    <p>Here is a pair of premise and hypothesis with Contradiction relation. The following is the Segment you need to respond, which we also emphasize in the premise.</p> 
    <ul>
      <dt>Premise</dt>
      <dd>But an O2 insider said there had been problems with a companies trying to sell the pass codes. Some people were "bound to have been turned away" because of fraudulent tickets. <strong class="w3-text-deep-orange">Led Zeppelin, formed in 1968</strong>, were one of the most influential bands of the 1970s with songs such as Whole Lotta Love and Stairway To Heaven. They split in 1980 after the death of the drummer John Bonham. Kenneth Donnell, 25, who was not born in 1980, spent 83,000 on two tickets in a BBC Children in Need auction.</dd>
      <dt>Hypothesis</dt>
      <dd>The band Led Zeppelin was formed in 1980.</dd>
      <dt>Relation</dt>
      <dd>Contradiction</dd>
      <dt>Segment (Your response)</dt>
      <dd>Led Zeppelin, formed in 1968</dd>
    </ul>
  </div>
</fieldset>
</section>

<!-- Questions Section -->
<section class="container">
  <div class="alert alert-danger text-center shadow" role="alert" style="font-weight: bold; font-size: large">
  All answers will be manually checked, SPAM and blank answers will be definitely rejected.
  </div>  
  <form name='mturk_form' method='post' id='mturk_form' action='https://www.mturk.com/mturk/externalSubmit'><input type='hidden' value='' name='assignmentId' id='assignmentId'/>
    <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 1</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">The pope flew by helicopter from Vatican City to a tent camp near the village of Onna where he led a prayer in the cold and rainy weather for the hundreds killed in the April 6 quake. The camp houses hundreds of families left homeless when the magnitude-6.3 quake destroyed their homes. Residents there welcomed the pope who kissed and hugged some of the children. "I have come here personally to this splendid and hurt land of yours which is living days of great pain and precariousness to express in the most direct way my kind closeness" the pope told residents. "I've followed the news with apprehension sharing with you your consternation ... for the dead along with your anxious worries about how much you've lost in a brief moment.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">The pope flew by helicopter from Vatican City to a tent camp near the village of Onna where he led a prayer in the cold and rainy weather for the hundreds killed in the April 6 quake. The camp houses hundreds of families left homeless</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="81" id="81" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 2</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Currently there is no specific treatment available against dengue fever which is the most widespread tropical disease after malaria. Sanofi Pasteur is collaborating with the Communicable Disease Center in Singapore and the Pasteur Institute in Vietnam to conduct these clinical studies in children and adults. "Controlling the mosquitoes that transmit dengue is necessary but not sufficient to fight against the disease. A safe and effective vaccine has been long awaited to prevent dengue epidemics" said Professor Leo Yee Sin director of the Communicable Disease Center in Singapore. "Clinical studies in Singapore are critical steps to advance the development of a vaccine for the prevention of dengue in Asia. We are happy to contribute to scientific research that would benefit the entire region."</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Malaria is the most widespread disease transmitted by mosquitoes.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Neutral</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="82" id="82" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 3</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">A Ugandan spy who set up a bogus charity and embezzled thousands of dollars of funding meant for Aids patients has been jailed for 10 years. Teddy Sseezi Cheeye 51 took $56000 (£38000) from the Global Fund charity which aims to prevent HIV tuberculosis and malaria. He set up an NGO the Uganda Centre for Accountability which received cash in 2005 to do HIV/Aids community work. But the High Court in Kampala heard Cheeye siphoned off the funds instead.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Teddy Sseezi Cheeye is an Ugandan spy.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="83" id="83" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 4</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">TWO years ago Sheik Adil Kalbani dreamed that he had become an imam at the Grand Mosque in Mecca Islam's holiest city. Waking up he dismissed the dream as a temptation to vanity. Although he is known for his fine voice Sheik Adil is black and the son of a poor immigrant from the Persian Gulf. Leading prayers at the Grand Mosque is an extraordinary honor usually reserved for pure-blooded Arabs from the Saudi heartland.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Sheik Adil Kalbani is the first black man to lead prayers in Mecca.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Neutral</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="84" id="84" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 5</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">(CBS) The world knows Philip Markoff only by his headline nickname the "Craigslist killer" but to Morgan Houston he is more than a suspect or a defendant. To her Markoff was a classmate and a friend someone she thought she knew. "I thought he was very nice" she tells 48 Hours Mystery correspondent Richard Schlesinger. "He was dorky but so many of us are. I mean I can be a big dork too. So you can't hold that against him." Houston first heard that her college friend had been arrested from another friend on the social networking Web site Facebook.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Philip Markoff is a medicine student at the Boston University School of Medicine.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Neutral</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="85" id="85" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 6</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Washington Kirk Kerkorian the billionaire mogul and major shareholder in General Motors Corp. said Friday that automakers Renault SA and Nissan Motor Co. are interested in purchasing a significant stake in GM and including the Detroit automaker in their alliance. Kerkorian's investment company Tracinda Corp. told GM Chairman and CEO Rick Wagoner in a letter that Renault and Nissan are receptive to the idea of including General Motors in their partnership and purchasing "a significant minority interest" in the automaker.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">The major shareholder of General Motors is Kirk Kerkorian.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="86" id="86" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 7</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Detroit — A federal judge upheld the right of a Pulitzer Prize-winning newspaper reporter to invoke the Fifth Amendment when he refused in court Tuesday to reveal his sources in a 2004 story about a terrorism prosecutor. David Ashenfelter of the Detroit Free Press appeared at the federal courthouse to be questioned in a deposition sought by Richard Convertino. The ex-prosecutor is suing the U.S. Justice Department over a leak that led to a Free Press story about an internal ethics investigation and he wants to know the reporter's sources.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">The Fifth Amendment is about terrorism.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Neutral</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="87" id="87" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 8</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">The exact figure is unknown although some estimate it to be in the thousands. This is despite the fact that Falun Gong is not officially allowed by the Vietnamese authorities. The regime clearly does not want Falun Gong to be another potential point of conflict in the already tangled bilateral relationship with China. But organising meetings is becoming easier and group meditation can now be seen in public locations. In Thong Nhat Park in central Hanoi a dozen men and women are united in a group breathing exercise their arms tracing arcs through the early morning mist. They look serene and undisturbed but it has not always been the case.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Falun Gong is a spiritual movement.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Neutral</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="88" id="88" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 9</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">The News of the World Britain's biggest-selling newspaper said the 26-year-old royal who is second in line to the throne unwittingly spoke to their reporter in a nightclub. The prince gives away little when speaking publicly. William also said his brother Prince Harry was missing his ex-lover Chelsy Davy while giving away no clues about whether he might marry his own girlfriend Kate Middleton. Harry 24 served with the British Army in Afghanistan for 77 days with the Household Cavalry regiment until a reporting embargo broke down in February 2008.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Prince Harry is 26 years old.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Contradiction</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="89" id="89" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 10</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">CASABLANCA Morocco This seaside city is known as a rich stockpile of art deco architecture the hub of Morocco's economic growth and the setting of an all-time classic movie starring Humphrey Bogart and Ingrid Bergman. But Casablanca is also the capital of a bleaker aspect of modern Morocco — sprawling slums where huge families are packed into shanties with tin roofs rusted by the ocean winds and goats and donkeys munch stray garbage. "It's as if we're eating straight from the gutter" said Mina Abujaman 48 describing the squalor.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Humphrey Bogart was 48 when starred in Casablanca.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Neutral</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="90" id="90" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 11</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Swampscott Almost as if leading parallel careers with the 19th-century Brontë sisters are the 21st-century Ephron sisters. While Charlotte Brontë wrote "Jane Eyre" Emily wrote "Wuthering Heights" and Anne wrote "Agnes Grey." In the Ephron family Nora wrote "Silkwood" "Heartburn" "When Harry Met Sally" and "Sleepless in Seattle" while Delia wrote "The Sisterhood of the Traveling Pants" and co-wrote "Michael" and "You've Got Mail" with Nora — all while Amy wrote six acclaimed novels. Amy Ephron's latest novel "One Sunday Morning" is a bestseller and film producer Jerry Bruckheimer recently bought her national bestseller "A Cup of Tea."</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">"Wuthering Heights" was written by Emily Brontë.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="91" id="91" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 12</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">BEIJING — China has rejected Coca-Cola Co.'s $2.3 billion bid to buy a major Chinese juice producer the Ministry of Commerce (MOC) announced Wednesday. The ruling is the first of its kind since China promulgated its anti-monopoly law last August.The proposed purchase was rejected on anti-monopoly grounds MOC said on its website. "The bid may harm competition...in China's beverage market." The purchase of China Huiyuan Juice Group the nation's largest juice maker would have been the biggest foreign acquisition of a Chinese company to date.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Coca-Cola buys Huiyuan Juice Group.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Contradiction</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="92" id="92" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 13</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">A SCUBA diver has died during a visit to a historic ship sunk off the Port Phillip Bay heads. The Geelong man 49 was with a group of six on a diving expedition to explore the SS Coogee shipwreck when he collapsed. The experienced diver who had explored the scuttled steamer 25 times before was teamed with two other divers when disaster struck. About 11am yesterday within minutes of entering the 13C water he floated to the surface. Police say that on reaching the shipwreck the two other divers did not immediately notice he was missing because of the poor visibility at that depth.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">The scuba diver who died in Port Phillip Bay was 25 years old.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Contradiction</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="93" id="93" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 14</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">A Japanese pop singer who was arrested for public indecency after being found drunk and naked in a Tokyo park has apologised for his "shameful" conduct. "I drank a lot and did not know what I was doing" Tsuyoshi Kusanagi said on Friday after being released by police. "I deeply apologise to fans for causing so much trouble and worry" he added. Kusanagi 34 shot to fame as a member of 1980s boy band SMAP. He has not been charged for the incident which took place in the early hours of Thursday.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Tsuyoshi Kusanagi is a pop star.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="94" id="94" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 15</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Dramatic footage obtained by the Guardian shows that the man who died at last week's G20 protests in London was attacked from behind and thrown to the ground by a baton-wielding police officer in riot gear. Moments after the assault on Ian Tomlinson was captured on video he suffered a heart attack and died. The Guardian has handed a dossier of evidence to the police complaints watchdog. It sheds new light on the events surrounding the death of the 47-year-old newspaper seller who had been on his way home from work when he was confronted by lines of riot police near the Bank of England.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Ian Tomlinson was a police officer.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Contradiction</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="95" id="95" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 16</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">MOSCOW (Reuters) Russian President Dmitry Medvedev said he alone rules Russia and not former President Vladimir Putin in unusually direct language during an interview with the BBC aired on Sunday. Analysts have been sceptical of Medvedev's ability to govern independently of Putin while polls show most Russians think the former President is still the real power in the country. "I am the leader of this state I am the head of this state and the division of power is based on this" Medvedev said. Medvedev made no direct reference to the so-called power tandem between himself and Putin now Russia's Prime Minister.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Putin was the President of Russia.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="96" id="96" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 17</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Mr Bouton has faced rising criticism ever since the bank said rogue trader Jerome Kerviel had lost 4.9bn euros ($6.5bn; £4.4bn) at the start of 2008. SocGen then needed a 1.7bn-euro loan from the government in December because of the impact of the credit crisis. Last month SocGen bosses gave up their annual bonuses following public anger. Mr Bouton who admitted that "like any manager I have certainly made mistakes" will now stand down on 6 May.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Daniel Bouton is the chairman of Societe Generale.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Neutral</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="97" id="97" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 18</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Early iterations of the 3D Internet have been a hit. Virtual world Second Life created by Linden Lab hosts 1 million users a month up from 544313 a year ago. Cooliris makes software that lets users view photos video and Web pages in 3D. "We solve the problem of navigating large amounts of content" says co-founder Austin Shoemaker 25 who is also among the Best Young Tech Entrepreneurs finalists. The free Cooliris iPhone app has been downloaded 800000 times since last fall. The company also makes versions for PC browsers. In March the Cooliris software was used to display baby pictures on the TV talk show Live with Regis and Kelly. Earlier this month Cooliris closed a $15.5 million round of funding headed by Kleiner Perkins.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Last year there were about 550 thousands players on Second Life.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="98" id="98" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 19</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">The Pritzker jury praised Mr. Zumthor's use of materials. "In Zumthor's skillful hands like those of the consummate craftsman materials from cedar shingles to sandblasted glass are used in a way that celebrates their own unique qualities all in the service of an architecture of permanence" the citation said adding "In paring down architecture to its barest yet most sumptuous essentials he has reaffirmed architecture's indispensable place in a fragile world." Mr. Zumthor said that his projects generally originated with materials. "I work a little bit like a sculptor" he said. "When I start my first idea for a building is with the material. I believe architecture is about that. It's not about paper it's not about forms. It's about space and material."</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">The Pritzker Prize is the highest recognition for an architect.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Neutral</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="99" id="99" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 20</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">A South Korean official expressed doubts over United Nations Secretary-General Kofi Annan's apparent support for a permanent Security Council seat for Japan and attention has been drawn to widespread mistrust of Japan by Chinese although the Chinese government has not commented directly against Japan.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">China won't receive money from Japan.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Neutral</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="100" id="100" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>

  <button type="submit" class="btn btn-info btn-raised btn-lg btn-block" id='submitButton'>Submit</button>
  
</form>
</section>
<script language='Javascript'>turkSetAssignmentID();</script>

     

</body>
</html>

<script src="https://code.jquery.com/jquery-3.3.1.slim.min.js" integrity="sha384-q8i/X+965DzO0rT7abK41JStQIAqVgRVzpbzo5smXKp4YfRvH+8abtTE1Pi6jizo" crossorigin="anonymous"></script>
<script src="https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/popper.js/1.14.6/umd/popper.min.js" integrity="sha384-wHAiFfRlMFy6i5SRaxvfOCifBUQy1xHdJ/yoi7FRNXMRBu5WHdZYu1hA6ZOblgut" crossorigin="anonymous"></script>
<script src="https://stackpath.bootstrapcdn.com/bootstrap/4.2.1/js/bootstrap.min.js" integrity="sha384-B0UglyR+jN6CkvvICOB2joaf5I4l3gm9GU6Hc1og6Ls7i6U/mkkaduKaBhlAXv9k" crossorigin="anonymous"></script>
]]>
</HTMLContent>
<FrameHeight>0</FrameHeight>
</HTMLQuestion>