<HTMLQuestion xmlns="http://mechanicalturk.amazonaws.com/AWSMechanicalTurkDataSchemas/2011-11-11/HTMLQuestion.xsd">
<HTMLContent><![CDATA[
<!DOCTYPE html>
<html>
<head>
<meta http-equiv='Content-Type' content='text/html; charset=UTF-8'/>
<script type='text/javascript' src='https://s3.amazonaws.com/mturk-public/externalHIT_v1.js'></script>
<script src="https://sdk.amazonaws.com/js/aws-sdk-2.142.0.min.js"></script>
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://stackpath.bootstrapcdn.com/bootstrap/4.2.1/css/bootstrap.min.css" integrity="sha384-GJzZqFGwb1QTTN6wy59ffF1BuGJpLSa9DkKMp0DgiMDm4iYMj70gZWKYbI706tWS" crossorigin="anonymous">
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://www.w3schools.com/w3css/4/w3.css">
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://unpkg.com/bootstrap-material-design@4.1.1/dist/css/bootstrap-material-design.min.css" integrity="sha384-wXznGJNEXNG1NFsbm0ugrLFMQPWswR3lds2VeinahP8N0zJw9VWSopbjv2x7WCvX" crossorigin="anonymous">
<style>
  dt{
    font-size: medium;
  }

  dd{
    margin-bottom: 1rem; 
    margin-left: 0;
  }
  
  .card-text{
    margin-bottom: 2rem;
  }

  h5{
    font-weight: bold;
  }
  .tablink{
    font-weight: 600;
  }

  .btn-lg{
    font-size: 2rem;
    line-height: 4rem;
  }
  h2{
    margin-top: 1rem;
  }
  p{
    font-size: 1rem;
  }
</style>
</head>

<body>
<section class="container mb-3 mt-3">
  <fieldset class="shadow bg-white mb-3">
<div class="w3-container">
  <h2 class="text-info" style="font-weight: bolder">Instructions and Examples</h2>
  <div id="Instructions" class="w3-container ins w3-animate-opacity" style="display:block">
    <h2>Instructions</h2>
    <p>Read the premise, hypothesis and realation, select a segment from premise that can determine the relation between premise and hypothesis.</p>
    <ul>
      <!-- We are adding a template variable below which we will replace with an actual link in our code later -->
      <li>Read the premise, hypothesis and the relation.</li>
      <li>On the basis of your own judgement, select a "sequential" segment from premise that can determine the relation between premise and hypothesis.</li>
      <li>The length is not restricted, as long as the segment provides sufficient informations.</li>
      <li>Copy the segment from premise and paste it into the following box.</li>
      <li><strong>SPAM and non-sequential segments will be rejected.</strong></li>
      </ul>
    <p>The following section is the definition of the three realations, which comes from the RTE-5 task guideline. If you are familiar with NLI tasks such as SNLI, MNLI, RTE, you can skip the section below.</p>
    <p>We define textual entailment as a directional relationship between a pair of text fragments, which we call the "Premise" and the "Hypothesis". We say that: </p>
    <p><strong><i>Premise entails Hypothesis, if a human reading premise would infer that hypothesis is most likely true. </i></strong></p>
    <p>For example, given assumed common background knowledge of the business news domain and the following premise: </p>
    <p style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><strong><i>Premise1 Internet media company Yahoo Inc. announced Monday it is buying Overture Services Inc. in a $1.63-billion (U.S.) cash-and-stock deal that will bolster its on-line search capabilities.</i></strong></p>
    <p>the following hypothesis is entailed:</p>
    <ul>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.1 Yahoo boutght Overture</i></p></li>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.2 Overture acquired by Yahoo</i></p></li>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.3 Overture was bought</i></p></li>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.4 Yahoo is an internet company</i></p></li>
    </ul>
    <p>For example, the following hypothesis are contradicted by Premise above:</p>
    <ul>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.5 Overture bought Yahoo</i></p></li>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.6 Yahoo sold Overture</i></p></li>
    </ul>
    <p>While the following ones cannot be judged on the basis of Premise above:</p>
    <ul>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.7 Yahoo manufatures cars</i></p></li>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.8 Overture shareholders will receive $4.75 cash and 0.6108 Yahoo stock for each of their shares.</i></p></li>
    </ul>
  </div>
  
</div>
</fieldset>
<fieldset class="shadow bg-white mb-3">
  <div id="Entailment" class="w3-container ins w3-animate-opacity">
    <h2>Entailment Example</h2>
    <p>Here is a pair of premise and hypothesis with entailment relation. The following is the Segment you need to respond, which we also emphasize in the premise.</p>
    <ul>
      <dt style="font-size: medium;">Premise</dt>
      <dd style='margin-bottom: 1rem; margin-left: 0;'>CNN) -- Malawians are rallying behind <strong class="w3-text-deep-orange">Madonna as she awaits a ruling Friday on whether she can adopt a girl from the southern African nation. The pop star, who has three children</strong>, adopted a son from Malawi in 2006. She is seeking to adopt Chifundo "Mercy" James, 4. "Ninety-nine percent of the people calling in are saying, 'let her take the baby,' " said Marilyn Segula, a presenter at Capital FM, which broadcasts in at least five cities, including the capital, Lilongwe.</t>
      <h>Madonna has three children.</dd>
      <dt>Hypothesis</dt>
      <dd>Madonna has three children.</dd>
      <dt>Relation</dt>
      <dd>Entailment</dd>
      <dt>Segment (Your response)</dt>
      <dd>Madonna as she awaits a ruling Friday on whether she can adopt a girl from the southern African nation. The pop star, who has three children</dd>
    </ul>
  </div>
</fieldset>
<fieldset class="shadow bg-white mb-3">
  <div id="Neutral" class="w3-container ins w3-animate-opacity">
    <h2>Neutral Example</h2>
    <p>Here is a pair of premise and hypothesis with neutral relation. The following is the Segment you need to respond, which we also emphasize in the premise.</p> 
    <ul>
      <dt>Premise</dt>
      <dd>Concerns have been raised that potential leads in the hunt for missing York woman <strong class="w3-text-deep-orange">Claudia Lawrence are not being followed up quickly enough. It comes after hotel staff in Malton contacted police</strong> after a stranger in the bar expressed satisfaction when asked if the chef was still missing. The incident happened more than three weeks ago and staff said detectives had not yet been in touch. Police said leads were being assessed in a methodical and structured way.</dd>
      <dt>Hypothesis</dt>
      <dd>Claudia Lawrence resides in Malton.</dd>
      <dt>Relation</dt>
      <dd>Neutral</dd>
      <dt>Segment (Your response)</dt>
      <dd>Claudia Lawrence are not being followed up quickly enough. It comes after hotel staff in Malton contacted police</dd>
    </ul>
  </div>
</fieldset>
<fieldset class="shadow bg-white mb-3">
  <div id="Contradiction" class="w3-container ins w3-animate-opacity">
    <h2>Contradiction Example</h2>
    <p>Here is a pair of premise and hypothesis with Contradiction relation. The following is the Segment you need to respond, which we also emphasize in the premise.</p> 
    <ul>
      <dt>Premise</dt>
      <dd>But an O2 insider said there had been problems with a companies trying to sell the pass codes. Some people were "bound to have been turned away" because of fraudulent tickets. <strong class="w3-text-deep-orange">Led Zeppelin, formed in 1968</strong>, were one of the most influential bands of the 1970s with songs such as Whole Lotta Love and Stairway To Heaven. They split in 1980 after the death of the drummer John Bonham. Kenneth Donnell, 25, who was not born in 1980, spent 83,000 on two tickets in a BBC Children in Need auction.</dd>
      <dt>Hypothesis</dt>
      <dd>The band Led Zeppelin was formed in 1980.</dd>
      <dt>Relation</dt>
      <dd>Contradiction</dd>
      <dt>Segment (Your response)</dt>
      <dd>Led Zeppelin, formed in 1968</dd>
    </ul>
  </div>
</fieldset>
</section>

<!-- Questions Section -->
<section class="container">
  <div class="alert alert-danger text-center shadow" role="alert" style="font-weight: bold; font-size: large">
  All answers will be manually checked, SPAM and blank answers will be definitely rejected.
  </div>  
  <form name='mturk_form' method='post' id='mturk_form' action='https://www.mturk.com/mturk/externalSubmit'><input type='hidden' value='' name='assignmentId' id='assignmentId'/>
    <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 1</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">On Wednesday American film director Steven Spielberg withdrew from his position as artistic adviser to the 2008 Summer Olympics in Beijing China. "Conscience will not allow me to continue with business as usual" he said. "Sudan's government bears the bulk of the responsibility for these ongoing crimes but the international community and particularly China should be doing more to end the continuing human suffering there" Spielberg's statement said. "China's economic military and diplomatic ties to the government of Sudan continue to provide it with the opportunity and obligation to press for change."</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Steven Spielberg is a resident of Beijing.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Neutral</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="321" id="321" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 2</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Human rights group Karapatan recorded more than 700 leftist activists farmers community organizers and journalists killed since Mrs. Arroyo came to power in 2001. The latest victim Dominador L. De Luna 51 an employee of the National Food Authority (NFA) in Samar was gunned down just when the necrological mass for Jose Maria Cui a professor at University of Eastern Philippines who was shot in front of his students was being held last January 29.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Dominador L. De Luna was killed in Samar.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Neutral</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="322" id="322" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 3</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Hunter Thompson the author of "Hey Rube: Blood Sport the Bush Doctrine and the Downward Spiral of Dumbness" once discussed on radio the possibility that he would be murdered to shut him up and that it would be made to look like a suicide. Paul William Roberts a friend of Thompson and a well known travel writer in an obituary played on this possibility for dramatic effect. Roberts related the fact that Thompson was working on a story relating to the World Trade Center demolition and did say he was going to be murdered and that the murder would be identified as a suicide. Roberts says in the second paragraph that Thompson did however commit suicide and was not murdered.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Hey Rube: Blood Sport the Bush Doctrine and the Downward Spiral of Dumbness was created by Paul William Roberts.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Contradiction</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="323" id="323" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 4</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Researchers from the University of Sydney University of Oxford and University of Cambridge have pinpointed a single neurochemical serotonin as the cause of an instinctive behavioural change from the locusts' solitarious phase to become gregarious and form disastrous swarms of millions. Serotonin (5-hydroxytryptamine or 5-HT) is a monoamine neurotransmitter synthesized in serotonergic neurons in the central nervous system (CNS) and enterochromaffin cells in the gastrointestinal tract of animals including humans. Serotonin is also found in many mushrooms and plants including fruits and vegetables.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">University of Sydney is not far from the University of Oxford.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Neutral</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="324" id="324" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 5</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Ramos Horta explained that "in the next days maybe already tomorrow morning they [the Australian Malaysian New Zealand and Portuguese forces] will do some coordination training in way to assure that the four forces know exactly what each one will do". "Since some are from the Army and the others [Portuguese Republican National Guard] are a specialized police and that they never worked together its useful to carry out some practical exercises" he added. In another subject Ramos Horta explained that the Australian soldiers that are in Maubisse next to a rebel group lead by major Reinado and in Gleno Ermera next to another group of "military opponents" are there "containing those elements"</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Ramos Horta lives in Maubisse.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Neutral</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="325" id="325" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 6</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">A supposed "pregnancy pact" at Gloucester High School in Gloucester Massachusetts has drawn international attention to the small Massachusetts fishing city which is considered to be one of the oldest settlements (1623) in the American continent. The story which was broken by TIME magazine and the Boston Globe involved the fact that 17 girls all sixteen years old or younger got themselves pregnant as part of a "pregnancy pact" so that the teenage mothers could raise their babies together.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Boston is in Massachusetts.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Neutral</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="326" id="326" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 7</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">The President of Indonesia Susilo Bambang Yudhoyono offered his condolences to the victims of the disaster. "On behalf of the government I express my condolences to the families of the dead victims and may their souls be accepted by God almighty" he said. Indonesia's Vice President Yusuf Kalla has visited the scene of the incident. "We will provide emergency help to the victims. For those whose homes were destroyed the government will help with the repairs" he told Metro TV.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Yusuf Kalla is the President of Indonesia.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Contradiction</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="327" id="327" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 8</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">When it comes to paying taxes to the state it doesn't count if you are dead of alive. One proof of that is Angelina Jolie's mother who died in 2007. Now after more then 2 years the state of California still fills a claim against Marcheline Bertrand and asks for $60000 in back taxes. Here is how they come out with this amount: she owes $43699 in back taxes plus $10924.75 in penalties and $8304.95 in interest for a grand total of $62928.70. One explication could be that somebody messed up the files filling taxes for the entire 2007 when she died in January.Also according to her will Jon Voight (Angelina's father) owns thousands of dollars in back child support. Marcheline trying to get that money through a lean on Voight's property and assets could be another explication.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Angelina Jolie's mother was born in California.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Neutral</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="328" id="328" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 9</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">The pilot who stole a light aircraft yesterday from Canada and landed in the central United States is now in custody. Adam Dylan Leon a 31-year-old Canadian citizen stole a Cessna 172 Skyhawk light aircraft from an airfield in Thunder Bay Ontario Canada. After taking off the airplane went off course toward the United States. The State Capitol in Madison Wisconsin was briefly evacuated but the aircraft went southwest of the city and personnel were allowed back in. Two F-16 fighters have been dispatched to follow the Cessna which later landed near US 60 in Ellsinore Missouri but NORAD spokesman Mike Kucharek said that the aircraft was not thought to be a terrorist threat.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Adam Dylan Leon is the owner of a Cessna 172 Skyhawk light aircraft.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Contradiction</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="329" id="329" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 10</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Scuderia Toro Rosso is part of the Red Bull stable and is considered the junior team' to Red Bull Sports Drink billionaire owner Dietrich Mateschitz' primary Red Bull Racing F1 team. They recently picked up an option on Bourdais for 2008 an encouraging sign that the Frenchman may finally achieve his life-long goal of driving in F1. Toro Rosso is based on the former Minardi F1 team a perennial back-marker but fan favorite. Minardi ex-owner Paul Stoddard now commandeers the new Team Minardi USA in Champ Car.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Red Bull Sports Drink belongs to Dietrich Mateschitz.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="330" id="330" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 11</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Managers at Central Wisconsin Airport in Mosinee Wisconsin earlier said the facility was preparing for a forced landing of the aircraft but the attempt to force it to land was scrubbed. The aircraft later crossed the border out of Wisconsin and passed over Illinois north of the city of St. Louis Missouri. It flew further south before landing in Ellsinore on Route 60 at which point the pilot fled on foot. Attempts to establish contact with or discern the intentions of the pilot were unsuccessful. The distance from Thunder Bay to Ellsinore is 795.1 miles (1279.6 kilometers) near the reported maximum range of a Cessna 172 but authorities say the aircraft had two hours of fuel left. Only Leon is believed to have been on board the aircraft.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Illinois borders on Wisconsin.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="331" id="331" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 12</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">New YorkAmerican manufacturing giant Proctor Gamble (PG) plans to acquire Gillette Co. for US$57 billion in stock. The purchase plan calls for PG to swap 0.975 shares of its stock per share of Gillete Co. PG also announced a stock buyback program in which they would purchase up to US$22 billion of shares over the next 18 months. Including the stock buyback program the merger is being financed by 60 percent stock and 40 percent cash. PG is known for brands such as Ariel and Tide washing powder Max Factor cosmetics Pringles potato crisps (chips) and Hugo Boss and Lacoste perfumes. Gillette known for brands such as Gillette razors Oral B dental care and Duracell batteries has had growing problems with the growth of private labels and price cuts demanded by large supermarkets.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Gillette manufactures toothpaste.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Neutral</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="332" id="332" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 13</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">According to a spokesman for NATO an attempted hijacking of a Norwegian tanker in the Gulf of Aden by Somali pirates has been thwarted by NATO forces. The MV Front Ardennes came under attack by pirates in a small skiff at about 6:00 PM on Saturday. Helicopters and a warship were dispatched to rescue the vessel and the pirates were apprehended seven hours after the initial hijacking. Officials said that pirates tried to flee in the dark but were caught by a Canadian vessel. Seven of the pirate gunmen were temporarily detained but were later released. NATO spokesman Lieutenant Commander Alexandre Santos Fernandes stated that since there was no Canadian law that could have prosecuted the pirates they had to be released.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Somali pirates attacked a Norwegian tanker.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="333" id="333" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 14</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Stock markets around the world particularly those in the United Kingdom have increased dramatically today. This is due to the ongoing events in the financial world including the United States government's announcement that it would buy billions of dollars of bad loans from US banks. The primary UK index the FTSE 100 rose in value by 8.04% which is 392.50 points to above the 5000 mark at 5272.50. The Dow Jones was up 3.10% at 14:58 UTC an increase of 330.89. The Dow Jones currently has a value of 11350.58 points. The NASDAQ index has risen by 2.53% to 2248.63 while the Dax was 5.06% higher than the start of the day as of 14:58 UTC.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">The NASDAQ index has risen to above the 2000 mark.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="334" id="334" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 15</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Greenpeace activists scattered schools of menhaden bait fish in the Chesapeake Bay on Tuesday when fishing ships belonging to Omega Protein Corp. were about to drop their sceine nets. The Omega fleet consisted of two spotter planes and four fishing boats with eight tenders. Greenpeace arrived with four fast moving out-board motor boats manned by thirteen activists who attempted to drive away the fish. The Coast Guard was called in and ended the confrontation peacefully.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Greenpeace headquarters are located in Chesapeake Bay.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Neutral</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="335" id="335" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 16</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Toronto Nearly a million commuters were immobilized and some businesses closed as Toronto Transit Commission workers walked off the job yesterday and formed picket lines outside subway stations bus terminals and other TTC facilities. None of their buses streetcars or subway trains were operational. Some service in the Greater Toronto Area continued through other transit services but was of limited use without a link to downtown Toronto. TTC workers said they'd been locked out but Toronto Mayor David Miller and the Ontario Labour Relations Board ruled yesterday afternoon that the walkout was illegal and ordered employees back to work. They complied with this order. They had not complied with a cease-and-desist order issued that morning.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">David Miller is an employee of the Toronto Transit Commission.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Contradiction</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="336" id="336" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 17</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">The march was organised by Swede Annie Börjesson's mother and her best friend Maria Jansson who between them campaigned for a fatal accident inquiry after Annie's body was found washed ashore at Prestwick in December 2005. Ms Jansson said the march was an event for people who felt let down by the legal system and not about individual cases saying "We are not here to judge each other or measure each other we are here because we are humans."</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Maria Jansson was friends with Annie Börjesson.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="337" id="337" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 18</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Friends of Mr. el-Nashar said he "was well-liked and showed no interest in politics." His friend Kadhem Al-Rawi a doctor in Islamic Principles at the European Institute of Human Sciences in Wales said "He had a great personality. You would never ever expect this kind of action from him. Impossible." This is a recurring theme heard from many of the suspected bombers families and friends. Many believed the suspects had little or no motive to carry out the attacks.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">European Institute of Human Sciences is the employer of Kadhem Al-Rawi.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="338" id="338" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 19</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Floods during the month of January have devastated Singapore. A major flood occurred from January 11 to January 12 2007 during which almost 24 cm of rain fell resulting in a landslide. A second major flood recently occurred at Kota Tinggi leaving 17 people and 12 monkeys dead. As of January 31 30000 people still reside in relief centers in w:Johor. Almost 24 cm of rain fell in two days in northern Singapore disrupting business operations in the area and triggering a landslide in Jalan Anak Bukit. The continuous rainfall over 18 hours on Thursday January 11 and Friday January 12 resulted in a landslide which caused the closure of a road that heads toward the Pan Island Expressway. The MacRitchie Reservoir station recorded 216.7 millimeters of rainfall during the 24 hour period accounting for 90 percent of the January average of 241 millimeters.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">The MacRitchie Reservoir station has been damaged by the flood.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Neutral</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="339" id="339" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 20</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Currently about 4% of South Africa's farm land is owned by blacks who number 42 million out of the nation's 47 million population. President Thabo Mbeki's government has set a target of transferring 30% of land to blacks by 2014. About 89% of the nearly 80000 claims have been settled so far and the government has spent some R2.5bn ($368m) purchasing farms from white owners. The National Land Claims Commission is entrusted with carrying out the transfers.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">The National Land Claims Commission was created by Thabo Mbeki.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Neutral</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="340" id="340" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>

  <button type="submit" class="btn btn-info btn-raised btn-lg btn-block" id='submitButton'>Submit</button>
  
</form>
</section>
<script language='Javascript'>turkSetAssignmentID();</script>

     

</body>
</html>

<script src="https://code.jquery.com/jquery-3.3.1.slim.min.js" integrity="sha384-q8i/X+965DzO0rT7abK41JStQIAqVgRVzpbzo5smXKp4YfRvH+8abtTE1Pi6jizo" crossorigin="anonymous"></script>
<script src="https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/popper.js/1.14.6/umd/popper.min.js" integrity="sha384-wHAiFfRlMFy6i5SRaxvfOCifBUQy1xHdJ/yoi7FRNXMRBu5WHdZYu1hA6ZOblgut" crossorigin="anonymous"></script>
<script src="https://stackpath.bootstrapcdn.com/bootstrap/4.2.1/js/bootstrap.min.js" integrity="sha384-B0UglyR+jN6CkvvICOB2joaf5I4l3gm9GU6Hc1og6Ls7i6U/mkkaduKaBhlAXv9k" crossorigin="anonymous"></script>
]]>
</HTMLContent>
<FrameHeight>0</FrameHeight>
</HTMLQuestion>