<HTMLQuestion xmlns="http://mechanicalturk.amazonaws.com/AWSMechanicalTurkDataSchemas/2011-11-11/HTMLQuestion.xsd">
<HTMLContent><![CDATA[
<!DOCTYPE html>
<html>
<head>
<meta http-equiv='Content-Type' content='text/html; charset=UTF-8'/>
<script type='text/javascript' src='https://s3.amazonaws.com/mturk-public/externalHIT_v1.js'></script>
<script src="https://sdk.amazonaws.com/js/aws-sdk-2.142.0.min.js"></script>
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://stackpath.bootstrapcdn.com/bootstrap/4.2.1/css/bootstrap.min.css" integrity="sha384-GJzZqFGwb1QTTN6wy59ffF1BuGJpLSa9DkKMp0DgiMDm4iYMj70gZWKYbI706tWS" crossorigin="anonymous">
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://www.w3schools.com/w3css/4/w3.css">
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://unpkg.com/bootstrap-material-design@4.1.1/dist/css/bootstrap-material-design.min.css" integrity="sha384-wXznGJNEXNG1NFsbm0ugrLFMQPWswR3lds2VeinahP8N0zJw9VWSopbjv2x7WCvX" crossorigin="anonymous">
<style>
  dt{
    font-size: medium;
  }

  dd{
    margin-bottom: 1rem; 
    margin-left: 0;
  }
  
  .card-text{
    margin-bottom: 2rem;
  }

  h5{
    font-weight: bold;
  }
  .tablink{
    font-weight: 600;
  }

  .btn-lg{
    font-size: 2rem;
    line-height: 4rem;
  }
  h2{
    margin-top: 1rem;
  }
  p{
    font-size: 1rem;
  }
</style>
</head>

<body>
<section class="container mb-3 mt-3">
  <fieldset class="shadow bg-white mb-3">
<div class="w3-container">
  <h2 class="text-info" style="font-weight: bolder">Instructions and Examples</h2>
  <div id="Instructions" class="w3-container ins w3-animate-opacity" style="display:block">
    <h2>Instructions</h2>
    <p>Read the premise, hypothesis and realation, select a segment from premise that can determine the relation between premise and hypothesis.</p>
    <ul>
      <!-- We are adding a template variable below which we will replace with an actual link in our code later -->
      <li>Read the premise, hypothesis and the relation.</li>
      <li>On the basis of your own judgement, select a "sequential" segment from premise that can determine the relation between premise and hypothesis.</li>
      <li>The length is not restricted, as long as the segment provides sufficient informations.</li>
      <li>Copy the segment from premise and paste it into the following box.</li>
      <li><strong>SPAM and non-sequential segments will be rejected.</strong></li>
      </ul>
    <p>The following section is the definition of the three realations, which comes from the RTE-5 task guideline. If you are familiar with NLI tasks such as SNLI, MNLI, RTE, you can skip the section below.</p>
    <p>We define textual entailment as a directional relationship between a pair of text fragments, which we call the "Premise" and the "Hypothesis". We say that: </p>
    <p><strong><i>Premise entails Hypothesis, if a human reading premise would infer that hypothesis is most likely true. </i></strong></p>
    <p>For example, given assumed common background knowledge of the business news domain and the following premise: </p>
    <p style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><strong><i>Premise1 Internet media company Yahoo Inc. announced Monday it is buying Overture Services Inc. in a $1.63-billion (U.S.) cash-and-stock deal that will bolster its on-line search capabilities.</i></strong></p>
    <p>the following hypothesis is entailed:</p>
    <ul>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.1 Yahoo boutght Overture</i></p></li>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.2 Overture acquired by Yahoo</i></p></li>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.3 Overture was bought</i></p></li>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.4 Yahoo is an internet company</i></p></li>
    </ul>
    <p>For example, the following hypothesis are contradicted by Premise above:</p>
    <ul>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.5 Overture bought Yahoo</i></p></li>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.6 Yahoo sold Overture</i></p></li>
    </ul>
    <p>While the following ones cannot be judged on the basis of Premise above:</p>
    <ul>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.7 Yahoo manufatures cars</i></p></li>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.8 Overture shareholders will receive $4.75 cash and 0.6108 Yahoo stock for each of their shares.</i></p></li>
    </ul>
  </div>
  
</div>
</fieldset>
<fieldset class="shadow bg-white mb-3">
  <div id="Entailment" class="w3-container ins w3-animate-opacity">
    <h2>Entailment Example</h2>
    <p>Here is a pair of premise and hypothesis with entailment relation. The following is the Segment you need to respond, which we also emphasize in the premise.</p>
    <ul>
      <dt style="font-size: medium;">Premise</dt>
      <dd style='margin-bottom: 1rem; margin-left: 0;'>CNN) -- Malawians are rallying behind <strong class="w3-text-deep-orange">Madonna as she awaits a ruling Friday on whether she can adopt a girl from the southern African nation. The pop star, who has three children</strong>, adopted a son from Malawi in 2006. She is seeking to adopt Chifundo "Mercy" James, 4. "Ninety-nine percent of the people calling in are saying, 'let her take the baby,' " said Marilyn Segula, a presenter at Capital FM, which broadcasts in at least five cities, including the capital, Lilongwe.</t>
      <h>Madonna has three children.</dd>
      <dt>Hypothesis</dt>
      <dd>Madonna has three children.</dd>
      <dt>Relation</dt>
      <dd>Entailment</dd>
      <dt>Segment (Your response)</dt>
      <dd>Madonna as she awaits a ruling Friday on whether she can adopt a girl from the southern African nation. The pop star, who has three children</dd>
    </ul>
  </div>
</fieldset>
<fieldset class="shadow bg-white mb-3">
  <div id="Neutral" class="w3-container ins w3-animate-opacity">
    <h2>Neutral Example</h2>
    <p>Here is a pair of premise and hypothesis with neutral relation. The following is the Segment you need to respond, which we also emphasize in the premise.</p> 
    <ul>
      <dt>Premise</dt>
      <dd>Concerns have been raised that potential leads in the hunt for missing York woman <strong class="w3-text-deep-orange">Claudia Lawrence are not being followed up quickly enough. It comes after hotel staff in Malton contacted police</strong> after a stranger in the bar expressed satisfaction when asked if the chef was still missing. The incident happened more than three weeks ago and staff said detectives had not yet been in touch. Police said leads were being assessed in a methodical and structured way.</dd>
      <dt>Hypothesis</dt>
      <dd>Claudia Lawrence resides in Malton.</dd>
      <dt>Relation</dt>
      <dd>Neutral</dd>
      <dt>Segment (Your response)</dt>
      <dd>Claudia Lawrence are not being followed up quickly enough. It comes after hotel staff in Malton contacted police</dd>
    </ul>
  </div>
</fieldset>
<fieldset class="shadow bg-white mb-3">
  <div id="Contradiction" class="w3-container ins w3-animate-opacity">
    <h2>Contradiction Example</h2>
    <p>Here is a pair of premise and hypothesis with Contradiction relation. The following is the Segment you need to respond, which we also emphasize in the premise.</p> 
    <ul>
      <dt>Premise</dt>
      <dd>But an O2 insider said there had been problems with a companies trying to sell the pass codes. Some people were "bound to have been turned away" because of fraudulent tickets. <strong class="w3-text-deep-orange">Led Zeppelin, formed in 1968</strong>, were one of the most influential bands of the 1970s with songs such as Whole Lotta Love and Stairway To Heaven. They split in 1980 after the death of the drummer John Bonham. Kenneth Donnell, 25, who was not born in 1980, spent 83,000 on two tickets in a BBC Children in Need auction.</dd>
      <dt>Hypothesis</dt>
      <dd>The band Led Zeppelin was formed in 1980.</dd>
      <dt>Relation</dt>
      <dd>Contradiction</dd>
      <dt>Segment (Your response)</dt>
      <dd>Led Zeppelin, formed in 1968</dd>
    </ul>
  </div>
</fieldset>
</section>

<!-- Questions Section -->
<section class="container">
  <div class="alert alert-danger text-center shadow" role="alert" style="font-weight: bold; font-size: large">
  All answers will be manually checked, SPAM and blank answers will be definitely rejected.
  </div>  
  <form name='mturk_form' method='post' id='mturk_form' action='https://www.mturk.com/mturk/externalSubmit'><input type='hidden' value='' name='assignmentId' id='assignmentId'/>
    <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 1</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">The first design for the Sydney Opera House was created by Utzon in 1957. Mr Utzon left Australia and returned to Denmark in 1966 due to disputes with the NSW government over cost blowouts and design differences. The building was finished 1973. Utzon never returned to Australia to see his building completed. Relations between New South Wales and Utzon improved in the late 1990s and in 1999 the Sydney Opera House Trust asked for Mr Utzon to advise on changing the building's interior to match his original design.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Sydney Opera House is situated in Sydney Australia.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="381" id="381" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 2</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">In his weekly open-air version of the popular Thailand Weekly show outspoken Government critic and founder of Manager Media Sondhi Limthongkul launched another series of stinging attacks against the country's Prime Minister. Thai PM Thaksin Shinawatra was accused of planning a cabinet reshuffle in an effort to deflect public attention away from allegations of wrongdoing and corruption. Sondhi alleged that politicians with poor public images would be recruited into the cabinet and that such was a scheme to overshadow accusations of corruption that have been levelled at the Prime Minister mainly by Sondhi himself.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Thaksin Shinawatra used to be Sondhi Limthongkul's best friend.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Neutral</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="382" id="382" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 3</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Reports say that 4 people including a paramedic and a retired firefighter have been killed after a gas station near Ghent West Virginia in Raleigh County blew up. At least 9 others have been critically injured. The explosion occurred at 10:50 a.m. [EST] at the Flat Top Little General Store and fire officials say that the cause may have been from a nearby propane tank that was leaking. The gas station was completely wiped out. Officials say that a full investigation will be launched to determine exactly what caused the blast. The company that stocks the tank with gas had sent out a representative who officials believe was killed in the explosion. Fire and rescue squads are continuing to search for victims.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">The Flat Top Little General Store was destroyed by an explosion.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="383" id="383" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 4</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">One of the crash victims Beverly Eckert of Stamford Connecticut and widow of 9/11 terror attack victim Buffalo native Sean Rooney was coming home for her husband's 58th birthday celebration. Her sister Sue Bourque noted to The Buffalo News "We know she was on that plane and now she's with him." Chris Kausner has said his sister Elise age 24 a law student was on board the plane. "I'm thinking about the fact that my mother has to fly home from Florida and what I'm going to tell my two sons" he said.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Elise Kausner had a brother called Chris.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="384" id="384" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 5</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Far-right and far-left activists clashed Sunday when the far-left were protesting Pope Benedict XVI's opposition to condoms a police source in Paris France said. A group of about 30 activists threw condoms on the ground outside Notre-Dame cathedral when attendants of the Sunday mass left the cathedral. The police arrested three people after the incident. About 20 youths some of whom were carrying signs reading "Leave my Pope alone" approached the protesters. One person was injured.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Pope Benedict XVI lives at the Notre-Dame cathedral.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Neutral</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="385" id="385" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 6</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Will the flood of celebs wanting second-hand babies never end? Yesterday it was Posh and today it's another talentless chick with absurd-looking boobs and no fashion sense Jessica Simpson. Yeah she wants to adopt too. And guess why? Because her dogs make her feel maternal. That's what she said. That taking care of her dogs has put her in the mood to have a baby. But says Jessica she's going to adopt before trying it the old-fashioned way.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Jessica Simpson intends to adopt a Korean baby.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Neutral</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="386" id="386" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 7</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Despite this around 30 people surrounded Megrahi's wife Aisha and their four sons Khalid Mohamed Ali and Moutasim to support them holding posters with Megrahi on them. The marchers travelled down the Royal Mile to the Scottish Parliament Building then held a candlelit vigil. Outside the building Mr al-Megrahi's lawyer Tony Kelly read a statement on behalf of Aisha. "My children and I are here today to give support to my husband Abdelbaset who is a victim of a miscarriage of justice and terminally ill and also to give support to all those other victims of miscarriages of justice" it said. "We are here for the sake of all these innocent souls who are suffering in silence. I would like to thank all those who continue to support him pray for him and express sympathy with him."</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Moutasim has a brother called Khalid.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="387" id="387" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 8</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">A 911 call that brought two police officers to a home where they were ambushed and where a third was also later killed during a four-hour siege was precipitated by a fight between the gunman and his mother over a dog urinating in the house. The Saturday argument between Margaret and Richard Poplawski escalated to the point that she threatened to kick him out and she called police to do it according to a 12-page criminal complaint and affidavit filed late Saturday. When officers Paul Sciullo and Stephen Mayhle arrived Margaret Poplawski opened the door and told them to come in and take her 23-year-old son apparently unaware he was standing behind her with a rifle the affidavit said. Hearing gunshots she spun around to see her son with the gun and ran to the basement. "What the hell have you done?" she shouted.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Margaret is the mother of Richard Poplawski.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="388" id="388" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 9</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">This year National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA) will beam high-definition images to the NASA website and television. By doing so NASA hopes to increase appreciation of global climate issues. There will also be a Washington exhibit relating to environmental issues viewed from space as well. At the NASA Marshall Space Flight Center activities will focus on their slogan for Earth Day 2009 "Just One Drop ... PRICELESS" and will demonstrate how the Environmental Control Life Support System operates as used on the International Space Staton (ISS). Amongst the many festivals WorldFest is a solar powered music celebration held in Los Angeles California. Buenos Aires will also feature its second Earth Day event featuring a music festival as well. "We are in a new era of energy innovation" said Daniel Yergin at a Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT) forum.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA) has its residence in Washington.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Neutral</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="389" id="389" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 10</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">After the bombing of a military recruiting station in New York City's Times Square police in Washington D.C. are investigating letters addressed to "members of Congress" which contain a picture of the recruiting station before the explosion and the message "Happy New Year We Did It". The letters arrived at Capitol Hill Thursday in manila envelopes according to an anonymous Democratic aide who is investigating the matter. The picture was accompanied by what seemed to be a 10 page manifesto against the Iraq War. Also included was a booklet which the aide says he cannot identify.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Times Square is part of New York City.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="390" id="390" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 11</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Human rights group Karapatan recorded more than 700 leftist activists farmers community organizers and journalists killed since Mrs. Arroyo came to power in 2001. The latest victim Dominador L. De Luna 51 an employee of the National Food Authority (NFA) in Samar was gunned down just when the necrological mass for Jose Maria Cui a professor at University of Eastern Philippines who was shot in front of his students was being held last January 29.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Mrs. Arroyo ordered the assassination of José Maria Cui.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Neutral</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="391" id="391" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 12</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">For a second time this week the southeastern Iranian city of Zahedan was rocked by a bombing. Like the previous bomb blast reported Tuesday it was relatively small and produced only three injuries and no fatalities. This is in stark contrast to bombs detonated over the weekend in Ahwaz and Tehran which produced a dozen fatalities and scores of injuries. The Ahwaz bomb went off in a fast-food restaurant at 7:50 PM local time.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">The city of Zahedan is next to Ahwaz.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Neutral</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="392" id="392" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 13</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">In a first ever effort in the United States to eliminate the presence of Zebra mussels in a large body of water the Virginia Department of Game and Inland Fisheries (VDGIF) announced on Monday that a private pond in Prince William County Virginia is undergoing water treatment using a chemical potash of potassium chloride in concentrations high enough to kill invasive and native shellfish species. The pond at the Millbrook Quarry will undergo treatment for three to four weeks in an effort to eliminate an infestation of zebra mussels a condition of its waters that was confirmed by state environmental officials in 2002. The treatment is not expected to pose a threat to non-molluscan aquatic wildlife vegetation or land-dwelling creatures at the site. Officials expect the one-time treatment process will provide protection from the possibility of future infestation for 33 years.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Prince William is a resident of Virginia.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Neutral</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="393" id="393" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 14</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Declan Ganley was the most successful Irish politician of 2008. He won the Lisbon Treaty referendum throwing the Government and opposition into chaotic confusion. He did this democratically. This irritated the losers particularly Dick Roche. As Minister for Europe Roche was significantly at fault for the defeat. He was well-versed in EU Lisbon Treaty intricacies so this was inexcusable. The campaign points made by Ganley throughout 2008 have been consistently ignored; instead personal attacks have been launched. Among actions taken was an unbalanced ill-researched and in my view malicious 'Prime Time' programme. The 'Irish Times' has published exclusively negative stories. There have been 'Village' magazine attacks the latest of these provoking legal action by Ganley now partly resolved.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Declan Ganley is the winner of the Lisbon Treaty referendum.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="394" id="394" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 15</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Earth Hour 2009 takes place Saturday March 28 2009 between 8:30 to 9:30 pm local time when communities will participate by turning out their lights starting in New Zealand and progressing along time zones around the world. Earth Hour began as a symbolic initiative against global warming by the World Wide Fund for Nature (WWF). "[It is] The largest demonstration of public concern about climate change ever attempted." Ban Ki-moon United Nations Secretary-General said. Earth Hour began in 2007 with around 2 million participating and increased to about 50 million in 2008. The Empire State Building Las Vegas Strip the Eiffel Tower Petronas Twin Towers the Peace Tower the Parliament Buildings the Christ the Redeemer statue Acropolis of Athens the Egyptian pyramids and the Colosseum are some notable landmarks which will honour Earth Hour Saturday evening.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">The Empire State Building joined the Earth Hour initiative.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="395" id="395" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 16</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">On September 6 soccer giants Thailand and Iran defeated Malaysia and Uzbekistan in shutouts of 11-0 and 9-0 respectively. Anothai Sathiyamat Somsak Thongdee Nares Numphakdee of Thailand all scored hat-tricks in the game against Uzbekistan. On the second day of competition a decisive battle in Group A between Japan and Iran was keenly watched by Thailand as one of the two teams would be their opponent in the finals. The game was scoreless in the first half with conservative tactics from both teams.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Iran soccer team won 9-0 against Uzbekistan.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="396" id="396" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 17</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Supermodel Christie Brinkley has divorced architect husband Peter Cook amidst allegations that he had extramarital sex with a teenage employee to whom he paid 'silence money' and had a '3500-a-month porn habit. Meanwhile poor Jo Wood wife of Rolling Stone Ronnie Wood has had to watch helplessly as her husband of 23 years fell off the wagon and took up with a 19 year-old waitress. So can you ever really know if your boyfriend is about to break your heart?</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Christie Brinkley has divorced Peter Cook.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="397" id="397" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 18</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Australian A-League football (soccer) club North Queensland Fury announced the signing of former Liverpool FC striker Robbie Fowler for their debut season. Fowler will be their marquee player-meaning his wages fall outside the salary cap-as announced at a press conference held by their owner and chairman Don Matheson. Fowler signed with the club on a two-season deal for undisclosed terms which will see him at the Fury until at least the end of the 2010-2011 season.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Robbie Fowler belongs to the North Queensland Fury football club.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="398" id="398" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 19</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Over fifty firefighters are damping down after a tanker exploded at an industrial unit in Salford in Greater Manchester. At one point thick smoke could be seen drifting across Manchester city centre. According to Greater Manchester Ambulance Service no one has been hurt as a result of the explosion. A fire service spokesman said a Heavy Goods Vehicle and a nearby building were engulfed in flames.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">The Greater Manchester Ambulance Service offices are located in Salford.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Neutral</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="399" id="399" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 20</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Rico Daniels is a British TV presenter living in France who is known for his two television series The Salvager whilst he still lived in the UK and then Le Salvager after he moved to France. Rico has been in a variety of jobs but his passion is now his profession he turns unwanted 'junk' into unusual pieces of furniture. Rico's creations and the methods used to fabricate them are the subject of the Salvager shows.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Rico Daniels lives in Britain.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Contradiction</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="400" id="400" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>

  <button type="submit" class="btn btn-info btn-raised btn-lg btn-block" id='submitButton'>Submit</button>
  
</form>
</section>
<script language='Javascript'>turkSetAssignmentID();</script>

     

</body>
</html>

<script src="https://code.jquery.com/jquery-3.3.1.slim.min.js" integrity="sha384-q8i/X+965DzO0rT7abK41JStQIAqVgRVzpbzo5smXKp4YfRvH+8abtTE1Pi6jizo" crossorigin="anonymous"></script>
<script src="https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/popper.js/1.14.6/umd/popper.min.js" integrity="sha384-wHAiFfRlMFy6i5SRaxvfOCifBUQy1xHdJ/yoi7FRNXMRBu5WHdZYu1hA6ZOblgut" crossorigin="anonymous"></script>
<script src="https://stackpath.bootstrapcdn.com/bootstrap/4.2.1/js/bootstrap.min.js" integrity="sha384-B0UglyR+jN6CkvvICOB2joaf5I4l3gm9GU6Hc1og6Ls7i6U/mkkaduKaBhlAXv9k" crossorigin="anonymous"></script>
]]>
</HTMLContent>
<FrameHeight>0</FrameHeight>
</HTMLQuestion>