<HTMLQuestion xmlns="http://mechanicalturk.amazonaws.com/AWSMechanicalTurkDataSchemas/2011-11-11/HTMLQuestion.xsd">
<HTMLContent><![CDATA[
<!DOCTYPE html>
<html>
<head>
<meta http-equiv='Content-Type' content='text/html; charset=UTF-8'/>
<script type='text/javascript' src='https://s3.amazonaws.com/mturk-public/externalHIT_v1.js'></script>
<script src="https://sdk.amazonaws.com/js/aws-sdk-2.142.0.min.js"></script>
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://stackpath.bootstrapcdn.com/bootstrap/4.2.1/css/bootstrap.min.css" integrity="sha384-GJzZqFGwb1QTTN6wy59ffF1BuGJpLSa9DkKMp0DgiMDm4iYMj70gZWKYbI706tWS" crossorigin="anonymous">
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://www.w3schools.com/w3css/4/w3.css">
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://unpkg.com/bootstrap-material-design@4.1.1/dist/css/bootstrap-material-design.min.css" integrity="sha384-wXznGJNEXNG1NFsbm0ugrLFMQPWswR3lds2VeinahP8N0zJw9VWSopbjv2x7WCvX" crossorigin="anonymous">
<style>
  dt{
    font-size: medium;
  }

  dd{
    margin-bottom: 1rem; 
    margin-left: 0;
  }
  
  .card-text{
    margin-bottom: 2rem;
  }

  h5{
    font-weight: bold;
  }
  .tablink{
    font-weight: 600;
  }

  .btn-lg{
    font-size: 2rem;
    line-height: 4rem;
  }
  h2{
    margin-top: 1rem;
  }
  p{
    font-size: 1rem;
  }
</style>
</head>

<body>
<section class="container mb-3 mt-3">
  <fieldset class="shadow bg-white mb-3">
<div class="w3-container">
  <h2 class="text-info" style="font-weight: bolder">Instructions and Examples</h2>
  <div id="Instructions" class="w3-container ins w3-animate-opacity" style="display:block">
    <h2>Instructions</h2>
    <p>Read the premise, hypothesis and realation, select a segment from premise that can determine the relation between premise and hypothesis.</p>
    <ul>
      <!-- We are adding a template variable below which we will replace with an actual link in our code later -->
      <li>Read the premise, hypothesis and the relation.</li>
      <li>On the basis of your own judgement, select a "sequential" segment from premise that can determine the relation between premise and hypothesis.</li>
      <li>The length is not restricted, as long as the segment provides sufficient informations.</li>
      <li>Copy the segment from premise and paste it into the following box.</li>
      <li><strong>SPAM and non-sequential segments will be rejected.</strong></li>
      </ul>
    <p>The following section is the definition of the three realations, which comes from the RTE-5 task guideline. If you are familiar with NLI tasks such as SNLI, MNLI, RTE, you can skip the section below.</p>
    <p>We define textual entailment as a directional relationship between a pair of text fragments, which we call the "Premise" and the "Hypothesis". We say that: </p>
    <p><strong><i>Premise entails Hypothesis, if a human reading premise would infer that hypothesis is most likely true. </i></strong></p>
    <p>For example, given assumed common background knowledge of the business news domain and the following premise: </p>
    <p style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><strong><i>Premise1 Internet media company Yahoo Inc. announced Monday it is buying Overture Services Inc. in a $1.63-billion (U.S.) cash-and-stock deal that will bolster its on-line search capabilities.</i></strong></p>
    <p>the following hypothesis is entailed:</p>
    <ul>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.1 Yahoo boutght Overture</i></p></li>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.2 Overture acquired by Yahoo</i></p></li>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.3 Overture was bought</i></p></li>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.4 Yahoo is an internet company</i></p></li>
    </ul>
    <p>For example, the following hypothesis are contradicted by Premise above:</p>
    <ul>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.5 Overture bought Yahoo</i></p></li>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.6 Yahoo sold Overture</i></p></li>
    </ul>
    <p>While the following ones cannot be judged on the basis of Premise above:</p>
    <ul>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.7 Yahoo manufatures cars</i></p></li>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.8 Overture shareholders will receive $4.75 cash and 0.6108 Yahoo stock for each of their shares.</i></p></li>
    </ul>
  </div>
  
</div>
</fieldset>
<fieldset class="shadow bg-white mb-3">
  <div id="Entailment" class="w3-container ins w3-animate-opacity">
    <h2>Entailment Example</h2>
    <p>Here is a pair of premise and hypothesis with entailment relation. The following is the Segment you need to respond, which we also emphasize in the premise.</p>
    <ul>
      <dt style="font-size: medium;">Premise</dt>
      <dd style='margin-bottom: 1rem; margin-left: 0;'>CNN) -- Malawians are rallying behind <strong class="w3-text-deep-orange">Madonna as she awaits a ruling Friday on whether she can adopt a girl from the southern African nation. The pop star, who has three children</strong>, adopted a son from Malawi in 2006. She is seeking to adopt Chifundo "Mercy" James, 4. "Ninety-nine percent of the people calling in are saying, 'let her take the baby,' " said Marilyn Segula, a presenter at Capital FM, which broadcasts in at least five cities, including the capital, Lilongwe.</t>
      <h>Madonna has three children.</dd>
      <dt>Hypothesis</dt>
      <dd>Madonna has three children.</dd>
      <dt>Relation</dt>
      <dd>Entailment</dd>
      <dt>Segment (Your response)</dt>
      <dd>Madonna as she awaits a ruling Friday on whether she can adopt a girl from the southern African nation. The pop star, who has three children</dd>
    </ul>
  </div>
</fieldset>
<fieldset class="shadow bg-white mb-3">
  <div id="Neutral" class="w3-container ins w3-animate-opacity">
    <h2>Neutral Example</h2>
    <p>Here is a pair of premise and hypothesis with neutral relation. The following is the Segment you need to respond, which we also emphasize in the premise.</p> 
    <ul>
      <dt>Premise</dt>
      <dd>Concerns have been raised that potential leads in the hunt for missing York woman <strong class="w3-text-deep-orange">Claudia Lawrence are not being followed up quickly enough. It comes after hotel staff in Malton contacted police</strong> after a stranger in the bar expressed satisfaction when asked if the chef was still missing. The incident happened more than three weeks ago and staff said detectives had not yet been in touch. Police said leads were being assessed in a methodical and structured way.</dd>
      <dt>Hypothesis</dt>
      <dd>Claudia Lawrence resides in Malton.</dd>
      <dt>Relation</dt>
      <dd>Neutral</dd>
      <dt>Segment (Your response)</dt>
      <dd>Claudia Lawrence are not being followed up quickly enough. It comes after hotel staff in Malton contacted police</dd>
    </ul>
  </div>
</fieldset>
<fieldset class="shadow bg-white mb-3">
  <div id="Contradiction" class="w3-container ins w3-animate-opacity">
    <h2>Contradiction Example</h2>
    <p>Here is a pair of premise and hypothesis with Contradiction relation. The following is the Segment you need to respond, which we also emphasize in the premise.</p> 
    <ul>
      <dt>Premise</dt>
      <dd>But an O2 insider said there had been problems with a companies trying to sell the pass codes. Some people were "bound to have been turned away" because of fraudulent tickets. <strong class="w3-text-deep-orange">Led Zeppelin, formed in 1968</strong>, were one of the most influential bands of the 1970s with songs such as Whole Lotta Love and Stairway To Heaven. They split in 1980 after the death of the drummer John Bonham. Kenneth Donnell, 25, who was not born in 1980, spent 83,000 on two tickets in a BBC Children in Need auction.</dd>
      <dt>Hypothesis</dt>
      <dd>The band Led Zeppelin was formed in 1980.</dd>
      <dt>Relation</dt>
      <dd>Contradiction</dd>
      <dt>Segment (Your response)</dt>
      <dd>Led Zeppelin, formed in 1968</dd>
    </ul>
  </div>
</fieldset>
</section>

<!-- Questions Section -->
<section class="container">
  <div class="alert alert-danger text-center shadow" role="alert" style="font-weight: bold; font-size: large">
  All answers will be manually checked, SPAM and blank answers will be definitely rejected.
  </div>  
  <form name='mturk_form' method='post' id='mturk_form' action='https://www.mturk.com/mturk/externalSubmit'><input type='hidden' value='' name='assignmentId' id='assignmentId'/>
    <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 1</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">GORDONVILLE Pa. On a frosty March morning with the stubble of last year's corn still in the fields thousands of bargain-hunters flooded yesterday into a crossroads a mile from Paradise. For one day the village of Gordonville (population: a couple of hundred) became maybe the biggest town in Pennsylvania's Amish country. Hundreds of Amish men in straw hats and Amish women in white head coverings joined thousands of "English" from as far as Texas in the bidding for a panoply of items including birdhouses antique desks farm implements quilts bathtubs horses and mules.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">The biggest Amish community is in Pennsylvania.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Neutral</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="141" id="141" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 2</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Mr. Berlusconi promises to rebuild Onna again as it was rebuilt after being overrun by the Nazis. Onna has become a symbol of the destruction wrought by the April 6 earthquake that killed 296 people in the central Abruzzo region. About 40 of Onna's 300 residents died. Mr. Berlusconi said on Saturday that Italians should remember with respect the partisans who fought Fascism but also those who died fighting on "the wrong side." Liberation Day marks the 1945 start of an anti-Nazi partisan uprising that ended with Italy's Fascist dictator Benito Mussolini being shot.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Onna is an Italian village destroyed by the earthquake in April.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="142" id="142" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 3</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">India has higher rates of malnourished children than sub-Saharan Africa despite having the money to tackle the problem according to a survey that raises grave questions about the country's economic rise Almost 46 per cent of Indian children under the age of 3 suffer from malnutrition according to the survey by the Indian Health Ministry in conjunction with Unicef the United Nations children's agency. That compares with about 35 per cent in sub-Saharan Africa and only 8 per cent in China whose economic growth India strives to emulate. It also represents only a slight decrease since the last National Family Health Survey in India seven years ago showed that 47 per cent of its children were mal-nourished.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">India has higher malnutrition rates than China.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="143" id="143" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 4</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">The UN human rights rapporteur John Dugard a South African legal scholar has compared the situation in the Occupied Territories to Apartheid. His successor Richard Falk an American Jew and a leading authority on International law called the situation a "prelude to genocide". Gaza he said was "slouching towards a holocaust" insofar as the situation expressed vividly "a deliberate intention on the part of Israel and its allies to subject an entire human community to life-endangering conditions of utmost cruelty". Falk accused Israel of bringing Gaza to the "brink of collective starvation" imposing "a sub-human existence" on a people "repeatedly and systematically" victimized.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Richard Falk has compared the situation in Gaza to the Holocaust.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="144" id="144" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 5</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">If 20 multiple sclerosis patients were in a room all would exhibit different symptoms she says. "The disease is not clear and not set. It's highly unpredictable." In particular in the relapsing-remitting stage there are symptoms such as fatigue blurry vision numbness or tingling that the patient feels but are not noticeable to others. As a result outsiders may not be aware of the extent of the patient's suffering. "Sometimes they think if you're not in a wheelchair M.S. must not be that bad. That's not true" Caesar observed. In Florida 20000 individuals have been diagnosed with the disease. Nationwide that number is 400000. Although it is still in the basic research stage stem cell therapy shows promise says Caesar. The research focuses on getting stem cells to regenerate the nerve-insulating myelin.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Stem cells could be useful to treat multiple sclerosis.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="145" id="145" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 6</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">A Northern Ireland teenager has been charged with the murder of PSNI constable Stephen Carroll earlier this month. The 17-year-old appeared at Lisburn magistrates court shortly before 11am today where he faced four charges including murder possessing of an AKM assault rifle and 26 rounds of ammunition gathering intelligence likely to be of use to terrorists and membership of the Continuity IRA. The youth who cannot be named because of his age denied all the charges according to his solicitor.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">A teenager is accused of the death of Constable Stephen Carroll.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="146" id="146" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 7</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">December 29 United States According to NASA's Near Earth Object Program 2004 MN4's assessed risk has been corrected downward to zero on the Torino scale. The Torino scale is the current method by which astronomers classify the likelihood of an impact with a near-Earth object.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">MN4 is an asteroid.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Neutral</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="147" id="147" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 8</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">ASUNCION Paraguay — Paraguay's president was hit with another paternity claim Monday just a week after the former Roman Catholic bishop acknowledged fathering a different illegitimate child while still subject to his vows of chastity. Lugo 57 did not confirm nor deny fathering the 6-year-old boy but read a brief statement promising to "act always in line with the truth and subject myself to all the requirements presented by the justice system." He also appealed for privacy referring all questions about paternity claims to his lawyer. Two of Lugo's cabinet ministers said they were initiating judicial proceedings against their boss on the latest woman's behalf and vowed to order DNA tests if Lugo doesn't recognize paternity.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Fernando Lugo is the President of Paraguay.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="148" id="148" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 9</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">The protest which was also held by Falun Gong members in major cities around the world marked the 10th anniversary of Falun Gong's protest against China's persecution as Beijing cracked down on the group and declared it a cult in 1999. "We hold this rally to call on the world's people to urge China to halt its suppression of Falun Gong and persecution of Falun Gong members" Chang Ching-hsi head of the Taiwan branch of Falun Gong said. He said Falun Gong members will keep up the peaceful protest until China has ended its crackdown.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Falun Gong is a spiritual meditation group seeking world harmony.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Neutral</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="149" id="149" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 10</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">GlaxoSmithKline is nearing a deal to acquire Stiefel Laboratories a large maker of dermatology products for as much as $3 billion people with knowledge of the talks said Sunday. These people cautioned that the talks were continuing and could still fall apart. If a deal is reached it would be the latest round of consolidation among drug makers who have sought to acquire product lines in the face of pressure from rivals making generic products. So far this year Pfizer agreed to buy Wyeth for $68 billion; Merck agreed to acquire Schering-Plough for $41 billion; and Roche struck a $46.8 billion deal for the 44 percent of Genentech it did not already own.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">GlaxoSmithKline is a British drug company.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Neutral</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="150" id="150" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 11</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">SUVA Fiji President President Ratu Josefa Iloilo repealed the country's constitution on Friday appointed himself head of state and set a 2014 election deadline. He said he had also sacked all the judges and established a "new legal order" following Thursday's Court of Appeal ruling that the country's military regime was illegally appointed following the 2006 coup. "I will soon be inviting suitable individuals to join or rejoin the bench under the new order" Mr Iloilo said in an address to the nation. The self-appointed head of state said a "soon-to-be-appointed interim government" would prepare the country for democratic elections in September 2014 at the latest.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">The President of Fiji is Ratu Josefa Iloilo.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="151" id="151" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 12</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">MANILA Philippines Fishermen in the Philippines accidentally caught and later ate a megamouth shark one of the rarest fishes in the world with only 40 others recorded to have been encountered the World Wildlife Fund said Tuesday. The 1100-pound 13-foot-long megamouth died while struggling in the fishermen's net on March 30 off Burias island in the central Philippines. It was taken to nearby Donsol in Sorsogon province where it was butchered and eaten said Gregg Yan spokesman for WWF-Philippines.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">A megamouth is a rare species of shark.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="152" id="152" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 13</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">China has rejected Coca-Cola's planned $2.4 billion acquisition of top juice maker Huiyuan Juice saying the deal would have been bad for competition. The acquisition by Coca-Cola would have been the largest-ever takeover of a Chinese company by a foreign rival and is the latest rebuff for an overseas buyer of a Chinese company. "This just shows that China is still not open to allowing the takeover of a national brand" said Jeffery Lau an analyst with Polaris Capital. "But this is not exactly a huge surprise to the market protectionism has been on the rise everywhere this year. This also explains why the stock has been trading at a nearly 20 percent discount to the takeover price" he said.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">China refused Coca-Cola's bid to take over a juice company to protect its market.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="153" id="153" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 14</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">It contained "a great number of inadmissible concepts" he wrote and did not acknowledge the calls for better Cuba-US ties. "Who is now demanding our exclusion? Perhaps they don't understand that times of exclusionary agreements against our people have been left far behind" he wrote. US President Barack Obama has taken a less confrontational approach to the communist nation than his predecessor George W Bush our correspondent adds. But his administration continues to insist that there must be progress towards democracy and on human rights before the trade embargo can be lifted. The US began imposing restrictions on Cuba after Mr Castro took power in 1959 making it the only Communist state in the Americas and a Cold War flashpoint.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Castro took power in Cuba in 1959.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="154" id="154" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 15</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">HONG KONG (Reuters) Eating two and a half ounces of baby broccoli daily for two months may protect against a common stomach bug that is linked to gastritis ulcers and even stomach cancer a study in Japan has found. Fresh broccoli sprouts contain plenty of sulforaphane a natural biochemical that appears to trigger the production of enzymes in the gut that protect against oxygen radicals DNA-damaging chemicals and inflammation. In an article published in the journal Cancer Prevention Research scientists found that eating two and a half ounces of baby broccoli daily may help stave off some serious health problems.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Eating broccoli may protect against ulcers and stomach cancer.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="155" id="155" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 16</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Israel was stung by the 2001 Durban conference. Despite successful pressure to remove any reference to Israel from the official closing statement the international NGO forum could not be so easily tamed. It issued a strongly worded declaration that equated Zionism with racism. It also described Israel's occupation of Palestinian land as "Israel's brand of Apartheid" and accused Israel of perpetrating war crimes and crimes against humanity. It was perhaps the loudest criticism so far by the international community of Israeli practices against the Palestinians. As such it was attacked by Western governments and the then UN High Commissioner for Human Rights Mary Robinson as anti-Semitic.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">NGO forum charged Israel with war crimes against Palestinians.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="156" id="156" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 17</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Slumdog Millionaire director Danny Boyle will be the leading member of the jury at the Shanghai Film Festival. The Oscar-winner filmmaker told the Xinhua news agency that he had never been on a fest jury before. Boyle also revealed his plans to make a flick in China. "When you have a city that is full of people and stories like Mumbai Beijing or Shanghai it's just so much excitement and potential for a filmmaker. It's like a dream come true" Variety magazine quoted him as saying.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">The movie "Slumdog Millionaire" has been directed by Danny Boyle.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="157" id="157" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 18</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">This slight 93-year-old with white hair who is now largely confined to a wheelchair was formally recognised last week as one of the tiny handful of people to have survived not one but both of the American atomic bombs dropped on the Japanese cities of Hiroshima and Nagasaki in August 1945 bringing to an end to World War II. Known in Japan as one of the hibakusha literally 'the explosion affected people' Mr Yamaguchi had long been recognised as a survivor of the nuclear explosion in his home town of Nagasaki. But now officials there have certified formally that he also survived the Hiroshima blast three days earlier where he'd suffered severe burns to his upper body and temporary blindness.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Americans dropped nuclear bombs on Japan in 1945.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="158" id="158" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 19</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">For sale: Six-room two-flat in Chicago's Park Manor neighborhood; ornate tile work; impressive brick exterior; an underground cellar big enough to hide some cash or ditch a tommy gun. The home at 7244 S. Prairie Ave. once owned by mobster Al Capone and his family has hit the market for $450000. It's a hefty sum considering similar two-flats in that working-class South Side neighborhood are selling for $180000 to $230000. But no other home in Chicago can match the history of the modest brick house that has had just two owners since Capone's mother died in 1952.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Al Capone was a gangster.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="159" id="159" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 20</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">"I have of these issues a clear conscience" a relaxed-looking de Klerk told reporters in Cape Town less than a week after a South African newspaper said he had been implicated in apartheid atrocities. "I'm standing here to state my case not in a defensive spirit but in a spirit that I am owed a fair deal in my own country." De Klerk was South Africa's last white president and shared the 1993 Nobel Peace prize with Nelson Mandela for fostering racial unity and securing the country's smooth transition from apartheid to the first all-race poll in 1994.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">F. W. de Klerk was the President of South Africa.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="160" id="160" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>

  <button type="submit" class="btn btn-info btn-raised btn-lg btn-block" id='submitButton'>Submit</button>
  
</form>
</section>
<script language='Javascript'>turkSetAssignmentID();</script>

     

</body>
</html>

<script src="https://code.jquery.com/jquery-3.3.1.slim.min.js" integrity="sha384-q8i/X+965DzO0rT7abK41JStQIAqVgRVzpbzo5smXKp4YfRvH+8abtTE1Pi6jizo" crossorigin="anonymous"></script>
<script src="https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/popper.js/1.14.6/umd/popper.min.js" integrity="sha384-wHAiFfRlMFy6i5SRaxvfOCifBUQy1xHdJ/yoi7FRNXMRBu5WHdZYu1hA6ZOblgut" crossorigin="anonymous"></script>
<script src="https://stackpath.bootstrapcdn.com/bootstrap/4.2.1/js/bootstrap.min.js" integrity="sha384-B0UglyR+jN6CkvvICOB2joaf5I4l3gm9GU6Hc1og6Ls7i6U/mkkaduKaBhlAXv9k" crossorigin="anonymous"></script>
]]>
</HTMLContent>
<FrameHeight>0</FrameHeight>
</HTMLQuestion>