<HTMLQuestion xmlns="http://mechanicalturk.amazonaws.com/AWSMechanicalTurkDataSchemas/2011-11-11/HTMLQuestion.xsd">
<HTMLContent><![CDATA[
<!DOCTYPE html>
<html>
<head>
<meta http-equiv='Content-Type' content='text/html; charset=UTF-8'/>
<script type='text/javascript' src='https://s3.amazonaws.com/mturk-public/externalHIT_v1.js'></script>
<script src="https://sdk.amazonaws.com/js/aws-sdk-2.142.0.min.js"></script>
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://stackpath.bootstrapcdn.com/bootstrap/4.2.1/css/bootstrap.min.css" integrity="sha384-GJzZqFGwb1QTTN6wy59ffF1BuGJpLSa9DkKMp0DgiMDm4iYMj70gZWKYbI706tWS" crossorigin="anonymous">
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://www.w3schools.com/w3css/4/w3.css">
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://unpkg.com/bootstrap-material-design@4.1.1/dist/css/bootstrap-material-design.min.css" integrity="sha384-wXznGJNEXNG1NFsbm0ugrLFMQPWswR3lds2VeinahP8N0zJw9VWSopbjv2x7WCvX" crossorigin="anonymous">
<style>
  dt{
    font-size: medium;
  }

  dd{
    margin-bottom: 1rem; 
    margin-left: 0;
  }
  
  .card-text{
    margin-bottom: 2rem;
  }

  h5{
    font-weight: bold;
  }
  .tablink{
    font-weight: 600;
  }

  .btn-lg{
    font-size: 2rem;
    line-height: 4rem;
  }
  h2{
    margin-top: 1rem;
  }
  p{
    font-size: 1rem;
  }
</style>
</head>

<body>
<section class="container mb-3 mt-3">
  <fieldset class="shadow bg-white mb-3">
<div class="w3-container">
  <h2 class="text-info" style="font-weight: bolder">Instructions and Examples</h2>
  <div id="Instructions" class="w3-container ins w3-animate-opacity" style="display:block">
    <h2>Instructions</h2>
    <p>Read the premise, hypothesis and realation, select a segment from premise that can determine the relation between premise and hypothesis.</p>
    <ul>
      <!-- We are adding a template variable below which we will replace with an actual link in our code later -->
      <li>Read the premise, hypothesis and the relation.</li>
      <li>On the basis of your own judgement, select a "sequential" segment from premise that can determine the relation between premise and hypothesis.</li>
      <li>The length is not restricted, as long as the segment provides sufficient informations.</li>
      <li>Copy the segment from premise and paste it into the following box.</li>
      <li><strong>SPAM and non-sequential segments will be rejected.</strong></li>
      </ul>
    <p>The following section is the definition of the three realations, which comes from the RTE-5 task guideline. If you are familiar with NLI tasks such as SNLI, MNLI, RTE, you can skip the section below.</p>
    <p>We define textual entailment as a directional relationship between a pair of text fragments, which we call the "Premise" and the "Hypothesis". We say that: </p>
    <p><strong><i>Premise entails Hypothesis, if a human reading premise would infer that hypothesis is most likely true. </i></strong></p>
    <p>For example, given assumed common background knowledge of the business news domain and the following premise: </p>
    <p style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><strong><i>Premise1 Internet media company Yahoo Inc. announced Monday it is buying Overture Services Inc. in a $1.63-billion (U.S.) cash-and-stock deal that will bolster its on-line search capabilities.</i></strong></p>
    <p>the following hypothesis is entailed:</p>
    <ul>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.1 Yahoo boutght Overture</i></p></li>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.2 Overture acquired by Yahoo</i></p></li>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.3 Overture was bought</i></p></li>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.4 Yahoo is an internet company</i></p></li>
    </ul>
    <p>For example, the following hypothesis are contradicted by Premise above:</p>
    <ul>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.5 Overture bought Yahoo</i></p></li>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.6 Yahoo sold Overture</i></p></li>
    </ul>
    <p>While the following ones cannot be judged on the basis of Premise above:</p>
    <ul>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.7 Yahoo manufatures cars</i></p></li>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.8 Overture shareholders will receive $4.75 cash and 0.6108 Yahoo stock for each of their shares.</i></p></li>
    </ul>
  </div>
  
</div>
</fieldset>
<fieldset class="shadow bg-white mb-3">
  <div id="Entailment" class="w3-container ins w3-animate-opacity">
    <h2>Entailment Example</h2>
    <p>Here is a pair of premise and hypothesis with entailment relation. The following is the Segment you need to respond, which we also emphasize in the premise.</p>
    <ul>
      <dt style="font-size: medium;">Premise</dt>
      <dd style='margin-bottom: 1rem; margin-left: 0;'>CNN) -- Malawians are rallying behind <strong class="w3-text-deep-orange">Madonna as she awaits a ruling Friday on whether she can adopt a girl from the southern African nation. The pop star, who has three children</strong>, adopted a son from Malawi in 2006. She is seeking to adopt Chifundo "Mercy" James, 4. "Ninety-nine percent of the people calling in are saying, 'let her take the baby,' " said Marilyn Segula, a presenter at Capital FM, which broadcasts in at least five cities, including the capital, Lilongwe.</t>
      <h>Madonna has three children.</dd>
      <dt>Hypothesis</dt>
      <dd>Madonna has three children.</dd>
      <dt>Relation</dt>
      <dd>Entailment</dd>
      <dt>Segment (Your response)</dt>
      <dd>Madonna as she awaits a ruling Friday on whether she can adopt a girl from the southern African nation. The pop star, who has three children</dd>
    </ul>
  </div>
</fieldset>
<fieldset class="shadow bg-white mb-3">
  <div id="Neutral" class="w3-container ins w3-animate-opacity">
    <h2>Neutral Example</h2>
    <p>Here is a pair of premise and hypothesis with neutral relation. The following is the Segment you need to respond, which we also emphasize in the premise.</p> 
    <ul>
      <dt>Premise</dt>
      <dd>Concerns have been raised that potential leads in the hunt for missing York woman <strong class="w3-text-deep-orange">Claudia Lawrence are not being followed up quickly enough. It comes after hotel staff in Malton contacted police</strong> after a stranger in the bar expressed satisfaction when asked if the chef was still missing. The incident happened more than three weeks ago and staff said detectives had not yet been in touch. Police said leads were being assessed in a methodical and structured way.</dd>
      <dt>Hypothesis</dt>
      <dd>Claudia Lawrence resides in Malton.</dd>
      <dt>Relation</dt>
      <dd>Neutral</dd>
      <dt>Segment (Your response)</dt>
      <dd>Claudia Lawrence are not being followed up quickly enough. It comes after hotel staff in Malton contacted police</dd>
    </ul>
  </div>
</fieldset>
<fieldset class="shadow bg-white mb-3">
  <div id="Contradiction" class="w3-container ins w3-animate-opacity">
    <h2>Contradiction Example</h2>
    <p>Here is a pair of premise and hypothesis with Contradiction relation. The following is the Segment you need to respond, which we also emphasize in the premise.</p> 
    <ul>
      <dt>Premise</dt>
      <dd>But an O2 insider said there had been problems with a companies trying to sell the pass codes. Some people were "bound to have been turned away" because of fraudulent tickets. <strong class="w3-text-deep-orange">Led Zeppelin, formed in 1968</strong>, were one of the most influential bands of the 1970s with songs such as Whole Lotta Love and Stairway To Heaven. They split in 1980 after the death of the drummer John Bonham. Kenneth Donnell, 25, who was not born in 1980, spent 83,000 on two tickets in a BBC Children in Need auction.</dd>
      <dt>Hypothesis</dt>
      <dd>The band Led Zeppelin was formed in 1980.</dd>
      <dt>Relation</dt>
      <dd>Contradiction</dd>
      <dt>Segment (Your response)</dt>
      <dd>Led Zeppelin, formed in 1968</dd>
    </ul>
  </div>
</fieldset>
</section>

<!-- Questions Section -->
<section class="container">
  <div class="alert alert-danger text-center shadow" role="alert" style="font-weight: bold; font-size: large">
  All answers will be manually checked, SPAM and blank answers will be definitely rejected.
  </div>  
  <form name='mturk_form' method='post' id='mturk_form' action='https://www.mturk.com/mturk/externalSubmit'><input type='hidden' value='' name='assignmentId' id='assignmentId'/>
    <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 1</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">After being contacted by Barton the school's resource officer interviewed Portillo about the incident. According to police spokeswoman Michelle Steele the teacher said Alex had been sent to the office earlier that day and when he came back to class Portillo asked the students if they were ready for him to return. She allegedly had told her class that the vote was part of a lesson on tallying. Portillo who has taught in St. Lucie County for 12 years has been reassigned out of the classroom at the district offices for the time being. Alex's mother believes that Portillo has "no business being near children at all" and should be fired calling her reassignment "just a slap in the face". The school board has advised Portillo not to speak with the press.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Michelle Steele is friends with Portillo.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Neutral</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="221" id="221" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 2</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">It's seven a.m. and I'm on a mini-bus heading east on the M4 motorway from Cardiff toward London. I'm riding with seventeen members of the Cardiff Socialist Party of which Saunders is branch secretary for the Cardiff West branch; they're going to participate in a march that's part of the protests against the G-20 meeting. Before we boarded the minibus Saunders made a speech outlining the reasons for the march. He said they were "fighting for jobs for young people fighting for free education fighting for our share of the wealth which we create." His anger is directed at the government's response to the economic downturn: "Now that the recession is underway they've been trying to shoulder more of the burden onto the people and onto the young people...they're expecting us to pay for it."</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Saunders belongs to the Socialist Party.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="222" id="222" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 3</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Two brothers aged 10 and 11 were accused Tuesday of the attempted murder of two other boys — becoming some of the youngest people ever charged with such a serious crime in Britain. The victims 11 and nine say they were robbed and beaten in an area of fields and woodland in Edlington northern England on Saturday. Neighbours said the younger victim was found wandering a road covered in blood. The older boy was discovered semiconscious in a wooded ravine nearby. Neighbours who found them told the British media that they appeared to have been beaten slashed and burned with cigarettes. The 11-year-old victim was in intensive care with serious head injuries. The nine-hear-old needed surgery on his arm. Crown Prosecution Service spokesman Chris Hartley said each suspect faced two charges of attempted murder and two of robbery. They are accused of stealing a mobile phone and five pounds from the victims.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Edlington is in the north of England.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="223" id="223" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 4</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Secretary of State of the Vatican City Cardinal Tarcisio said that the Pope apologized for the way his remarks made during a speech at the University of Regensburg in Germany on September 12 2006 were interpreted saying "the Holy Father is very sorry that some passages of his speech may have appeared offensive to Muslims and were interpreted in a way he hadn't intended them to be. [The speech was supposed to reflect] the relationship between religion and violence in general and to conclude with a clear and radical rejection of the religious motivation for violence from whatever side it may come."</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">The Pope works with Cardinal Tarcisio.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="224" id="224" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 5</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">The police requested the arrest of four suspects. Two are the alleged gunfighters Eduardo and Fogoió one is a man called Tato who supposedly contacted the gunfighters and the other one is a farmer Vítor Miro Bastos de Moura known as Bida who is believed to have contracted the assassins. The Brazilian police also found a body of another man 500 meters from the place were they found the body of the nun. The murdered man was identified as the peasant Adalberto Xavier Leal known as the Cabeludo or the Hairy Man. He was working for a farmer who had already invaded the area of the PDS maintained by sister Dorothy.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Vítor Miro Bastos de Moura is the employer of Adalberto Xavier Leal.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Neutral</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="225" id="225" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 6</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Residents and business owners in the Elmwood Avenue neighborhood and surrounding area in Buffalo heard a competing proposal for development in their neighborhood at the February 22 meeting held at the Burchfield-Penney Art Gallery at Buffalo State College. The meeting attended by at least 140 was originally to consider the Elmwood Village Hotel but also included a new revitalization proposal from Rocco Termini which would increase retail space but involves less demolition and no hotel.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Elmwood Avenue is in Buffalo.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="226" id="226" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 7</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">On Thursday in Canada the Society Promoting Environmental Conservation (SPEC) and the Western Canada Wilderness Committee delivered petitions with over 10000 signatorys to the Premier of British Columbia's office. The petitions ask that the government cancel the Gateway Program's highway expansions components and invest more in transit instead. The Gateway Program is a transportation infrastructure project that includes over 260 km of new highway lanes. Over a dozen activists rallied outside the office in downtown Vancouver including two dressed as polar bears. The premier's office initially declined to accept the invitations. After the activists attempted to enter the nearby convention centre where the premier was speaking staff working with the Premier agreed to accept the petitions.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">The Society Promoting Environmental Conservation is against the Gateway Program.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="227" id="227" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 8</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">On Friday August 4 bride-to-be Julianna Redd's parents Lemeul and Julia Redd told her that she was going on a shopping trip but instead she was driven 390 km (240 miles) from Provo Utah to Grand Junction Colorado by her parents trying to talk her out of getting married. Her now husband Perry Myers called the police when Julianna and her parents did not attend the pre-wedding dinner. The Redds spent the night in Colorado before going to Provo the day the couple were supposed to be married at The Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints Temple in Salt Lake City Utah.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Julia Redd has a daughter called Julianna.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="228" id="228" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 9</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Akwasi Osei-Adjei is Ghana's foreign minister. He tells VOA reporter Peter Clottey that President Kufuor is concerned about the tensions in Kenya. "Basically the president has been invited to Kenya to see for himself the situation and offer advise as to how the two leaders can come together to stop what is happening in Kenya. As you know people are being killed and there are a lot of disturbances in Kenya and Kenya is like a pillar of a democratic country is now blowing up in our faces. And I don't think it is for any African country to stand by and more so the chair of the AU (Africa Union) to sit by for such a thing to happen to Kenya. He (president Kufuor) is going there to offer advice" Osei-Adjei noted.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Peter Clottey is employed by President Kufuor.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Contradiction</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="229" id="229" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 10</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Last year gave local vendors plenty to think about. Dr. Conway reported the total impact on the local economy at $2.5 million. Regardless of the actual figure the local Kwik-E-Mart started taking furry fandom seriously when shelves started coming up bare. This year vendors thought themselves better-prepared. The Steel City Diner printed 100 shirts celebrating the convention only to run out on Friday afternoon. The diner met their weekly sales target by Wednesday and doubled that by Friday night working through Sunday to keep up with demand.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">The Steel City Diner belongs to Dr. Conway.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Neutral</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="230" id="230" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 11</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Cancer survivors who were a mean age of 4.6 years when first diagnosed often had more physical visual and hearing disability impairments as complications of treatment but they did not have a higher rate of grade repetition. Indeed the rates between the cancer and non-cancer groups were similar at about 22 per cent. Another positive finding was that there were no significant differences in achievements on Grade 12 provincial exams between the study groups. Lead investigator Mary McBride and radiation oncologist Dr. Karen Goddard said in an interview that radiation treatment has helped improve childhood survival outcomes (to 80 per cent in the past decade) but it is also a leading culprit as far as educational difficulties go.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Cancer survivors often suffer from visual impairments after treatment.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="231" id="231" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 12</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Ed Stelmach has won the race to lead Alberta's governing Progressive Conservative party beating out former Treasurer Jim Dinning and Ted Morton. Stelmach now premier-Designate of Alberta will be sworn in as Premier of the Canadian province once outgoing leader Ralph Klein leaves office later this month. Stelmach placed third on the first ballot of the party's leadership election last Saturday behind Dinning the favourite who was in first place and former university professor Morton who was in second place. The top three contenders in the eight candidate race proceeded to the second ballot vote which occurred yesterday.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">The leader of the Progressive Conservative party in Alberta is Ed Stelmach.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="232" id="232" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 13</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Authorities were unaware of Bush's identity until after his arrest and booking when they observed his Florida Driver License. Governor Bush appearing with his wife at a Miami museum reception bristled at reporters' questions Friday evening when the issue was mentioned saying "I'm not going to discuss it on the public square with 30 cameras." Several members of the Bush family have received considerable press coverage for perceived or abusive use of alcohol and other substances including George W. Bush's DUI Jenna and Barbara Bush's underage drinking and Jebby's sister Noelle arrest for forging a Xanax prescription.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Jenna Bush is a relative of Governor Bush.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="233" id="233" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 14</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Google has not complied with the request prompting US Attorney General Alberto Gonzales to request a court order from a federal judge in California. Google has nevertheless stated that it would fight the order. Nicole Wong the associate general counsel for Google said "Google is not a party to this lawsuit and their demand for information overreaches" and that "We had lengthy discussions with them to try to resolve this but were not able to and we intend to resist their motion vigorously."</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Alberto Gonzales was engaged to Nicole Wong.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Neutral</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="234" id="234" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 15</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Sweden has plans to open a virtual embassy in Second Life the virtual world home to thousands of netizens. Companies like Dell are already selling computers via the virtual world but Sweden would become the first country to have a cyber-embassy in Second Life. The embassy would not provide visa or perform diplomatic tasks but would provide information on how and where to get these documents in the real world as well as giving cultural and tourist information about the country. Visitors will also be able to chat with embassy personnel. A spokesperson explained that it would be an easy and cheap way to reach young people. The idea came from The Swedish Institute an agency of the Foreign Affairs Ministry of Sweden with providing information about Sweden as a key purpose.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">The Swedish Institute has purchased Dell computers.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Neutral</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="235" id="235" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 16</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Local president Ramzan Kadyrov son of former Chechen leader Akhmad Kadyrov who died in a bomb blast in 2004 in Grozny is satisfied with the situation. He is now expecting more foreign investment and a better economic growth in the area. He declared April 16 as a future holiday in Chechnya. Human rights organisations on the other hand accuse him of letting his own militia torture and kill his opponents. In the meantime the local president Ramzan Kadyrov has informed the heads of the regional administration about the end of the operation and advised them yesterday to let the former militants return to a peaceful civilian life Vesti.ru reports. But at the same time he settled that the rule should not apply to those rebels who had become extremists. These people — according to Kadyrov mostly living in the mountains — would not deserve any amnesty and not any public pardon Kadyrov said.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Akhmad Kadyrov is the father of president Ramzan Kadyrov.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="236" id="236" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 17</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">The Royal Canadian Mounted Police bungled the case of Maher Arar leading to an innocent man being tortured in Syria following his deportation from the United States according to the findings of the federal inquiry into the affair. Justice Dennis O'Connor's report released yesterday reveals that the RCMP erroneously told the United States that Arar was linked to Al Qaeda and wrongly described him as an "Islamic extremist individual". "The potential consequences of labelling someone an Islamic extremist in post-9/11 are enormous" wrote O'Connor. Based on information received from the RCMP Arar was detained on September 16 2002 during a stopover at JFK Airport in New York City. After being held in the US for two weeks he was deported to Syria under the US policy of "extraordinary rendition" and was detained in a Damascus prison for a year without charges and tortured before being returned to Canada.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Al Qaeda is connected to the United States.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Neutral</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="237" id="237" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 18</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">The Australian federal and New South Wales governments will not be selling their shares in Snowy Hydro Limited (the owner and operator of the Snowy Mountains Hydro-Electric Scheme). Snowy Hydro Limited's major shareholder is the NSW government with a 58 percent shareholding. The Victorian government owns 29 percent and the federal government has a 13 percent stake. NSW Premier Morris Iemma announced in December 2005 that he wished to sell the state's share in Snowy Hydro that caused the federal and Victorian governments to follow. The proposed sale has attracted immense criticism by those who believed that the sale would affect the environment and water supplies along the Snowy River this was reinforced yesterday when 58 eminent Australians presented a petition to the government opposing the sale.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Morris Iemma is the prime minister of New South Wales.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="238" id="238" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 19</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Krasnov said the new spacecraft will be capable of carrying a crew of six and a payload of 500 kilograms to orbit around the Earth. The Soyuz can only carry a crew of three. Krasnov told reporters last week that the new spaceship should also be capable of delivering a crew of four to lunar orbit. "We want the new ship to be a step into the future not just a scaled up version of the Soyuz" he said. Russia plans to start construction next year of Vostochny a new space launch facility in the far eastern Amur region near China. The new cosmodrome is expected to host launches of unmanned spacecraft beginning in 2015 and the first manned missions starting in 2018. Russia currently uses the Soviet-built Baikonur cosmodrome in Kazakhstan for all of its manned space missions and most important commercial launches.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">The Soyuz spacecraft is built in China.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Neutral</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="239" id="239" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 20</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">A lack of thorough and consistent measures to pick the White House press corps members has led many to question the reason a little-known conservative reporter had access to sensitive documents and the President of the United States. Jeff Gannon whose real name is James Guckert has been operating under an assumed name while attending White House press briefings. Gannon/Guckert was a reporter for the news service Talon News a website believed by some to be a branch of the GOPUSA up until his recent resignation due to the incidents surrounding him.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Talon News paid James Guckert's salary.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="240" id="240" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>

  <button type="submit" class="btn btn-info btn-raised btn-lg btn-block" id='submitButton'>Submit</button>
  
</form>
</section>
<script language='Javascript'>turkSetAssignmentID();</script>

     

</body>
</html>

<script src="https://code.jquery.com/jquery-3.3.1.slim.min.js" integrity="sha384-q8i/X+965DzO0rT7abK41JStQIAqVgRVzpbzo5smXKp4YfRvH+8abtTE1Pi6jizo" crossorigin="anonymous"></script>
<script src="https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/popper.js/1.14.6/umd/popper.min.js" integrity="sha384-wHAiFfRlMFy6i5SRaxvfOCifBUQy1xHdJ/yoi7FRNXMRBu5WHdZYu1hA6ZOblgut" crossorigin="anonymous"></script>
<script src="https://stackpath.bootstrapcdn.com/bootstrap/4.2.1/js/bootstrap.min.js" integrity="sha384-B0UglyR+jN6CkvvICOB2joaf5I4l3gm9GU6Hc1og6Ls7i6U/mkkaduKaBhlAXv9k" crossorigin="anonymous"></script>
]]>
</HTMLContent>
<FrameHeight>0</FrameHeight>
</HTMLQuestion>