<HTMLQuestion xmlns="http://mechanicalturk.amazonaws.com/AWSMechanicalTurkDataSchemas/2011-11-11/HTMLQuestion.xsd">
<HTMLContent><![CDATA[
<!DOCTYPE html>
<html>
<head>
<meta http-equiv='Content-Type' content='text/html; charset=UTF-8'/>
<script type='text/javascript' src='https://s3.amazonaws.com/mturk-public/externalHIT_v1.js'></script>
<script src="https://sdk.amazonaws.com/js/aws-sdk-2.142.0.min.js"></script>
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://stackpath.bootstrapcdn.com/bootstrap/4.2.1/css/bootstrap.min.css" integrity="sha384-GJzZqFGwb1QTTN6wy59ffF1BuGJpLSa9DkKMp0DgiMDm4iYMj70gZWKYbI706tWS" crossorigin="anonymous">
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://www.w3schools.com/w3css/4/w3.css">
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://unpkg.com/bootstrap-material-design@4.1.1/dist/css/bootstrap-material-design.min.css" integrity="sha384-wXznGJNEXNG1NFsbm0ugrLFMQPWswR3lds2VeinahP8N0zJw9VWSopbjv2x7WCvX" crossorigin="anonymous">
<style>
  dt{
    font-size: medium;
  }

  dd{
    margin-bottom: 1rem; 
    margin-left: 0;
  }
  
  .card-text{
    margin-bottom: 2rem;
  }

  h5{
    font-weight: bold;
  }
  .tablink{
    font-weight: 600;
  }

  .btn-lg{
    font-size: 2rem;
    line-height: 4rem;
  }
  h2{
    margin-top: 1rem;
  }
  p{
    font-size: 1rem;
  }
</style>
</head>

<body>
<section class="container mb-3 mt-3">
  <fieldset class="shadow bg-white mb-3">
<div class="w3-container">
  <h2 class="text-info" style="font-weight: bolder">Instructions and Examples</h2>
  <div id="Instructions" class="w3-container ins w3-animate-opacity" style="display:block">
    <h2>Instructions</h2>
    <p>Read the premise, hypothesis and realation, select a segment from premise that can determine the relation between premise and hypothesis.</p>
    <ul>
      <!-- We are adding a template variable below which we will replace with an actual link in our code later -->
      <li>Read the premise, hypothesis and the relation.</li>
      <li>On the basis of your own judgement, select a "sequential" segment from premise that can determine the relation between premise and hypothesis.</li>
      <li>The length is not restricted, as long as the segment provides sufficient informations.</li>
      <li>Copy the segment from premise and paste it into the following box.</li>
      <li><strong>SPAM and non-sequential segments will be rejected.</strong></li>
      </ul>
    <p>The following section is the definition of the three realations, which comes from the RTE-5 task guideline. If you are familiar with NLI tasks such as SNLI, MNLI, RTE, you can skip the section below.</p>
    <p>We define textual entailment as a directional relationship between a pair of text fragments, which we call the "Premise" and the "Hypothesis". We say that: </p>
    <p><strong><i>Premise entails Hypothesis, if a human reading premise would infer that hypothesis is most likely true. </i></strong></p>
    <p>For example, given assumed common background knowledge of the business news domain and the following premise: </p>
    <p style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><strong><i>Premise1 Internet media company Yahoo Inc. announced Monday it is buying Overture Services Inc. in a $1.63-billion (U.S.) cash-and-stock deal that will bolster its on-line search capabilities.</i></strong></p>
    <p>the following hypothesis is entailed:</p>
    <ul>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.1 Yahoo boutght Overture</i></p></li>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.2 Overture acquired by Yahoo</i></p></li>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.3 Overture was bought</i></p></li>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.4 Yahoo is an internet company</i></p></li>
    </ul>
    <p>For example, the following hypothesis are contradicted by Premise above:</p>
    <ul>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.5 Overture bought Yahoo</i></p></li>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.6 Yahoo sold Overture</i></p></li>
    </ul>
    <p>While the following ones cannot be judged on the basis of Premise above:</p>
    <ul>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.7 Yahoo manufatures cars</i></p></li>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.8 Overture shareholders will receive $4.75 cash and 0.6108 Yahoo stock for each of their shares.</i></p></li>
    </ul>
  </div>
  
</div>
</fieldset>
<fieldset class="shadow bg-white mb-3">
  <div id="Entailment" class="w3-container ins w3-animate-opacity">
    <h2>Entailment Example</h2>
    <p>Here is a pair of premise and hypothesis with entailment relation. The following is the Segment you need to respond, which we also emphasize in the premise.</p>
    <ul>
      <dt style="font-size: medium;">Premise</dt>
      <dd style='margin-bottom: 1rem; margin-left: 0;'>CNN) -- Malawians are rallying behind <strong class="w3-text-deep-orange">Madonna as she awaits a ruling Friday on whether she can adopt a girl from the southern African nation. The pop star, who has three children</strong>, adopted a son from Malawi in 2006. She is seeking to adopt Chifundo "Mercy" James, 4. "Ninety-nine percent of the people calling in are saying, 'let her take the baby,' " said Marilyn Segula, a presenter at Capital FM, which broadcasts in at least five cities, including the capital, Lilongwe.</t>
      <h>Madonna has three children.</dd>
      <dt>Hypothesis</dt>
      <dd>Madonna has three children.</dd>
      <dt>Relation</dt>
      <dd>Entailment</dd>
      <dt>Segment (Your response)</dt>
      <dd>Madonna as she awaits a ruling Friday on whether she can adopt a girl from the southern African nation. The pop star, who has three children</dd>
    </ul>
  </div>
</fieldset>
<fieldset class="shadow bg-white mb-3">
  <div id="Neutral" class="w3-container ins w3-animate-opacity">
    <h2>Neutral Example</h2>
    <p>Here is a pair of premise and hypothesis with neutral relation. The following is the Segment you need to respond, which we also emphasize in the premise.</p> 
    <ul>
      <dt>Premise</dt>
      <dd>Concerns have been raised that potential leads in the hunt for missing York woman <strong class="w3-text-deep-orange">Claudia Lawrence are not being followed up quickly enough. It comes after hotel staff in Malton contacted police</strong> after a stranger in the bar expressed satisfaction when asked if the chef was still missing. The incident happened more than three weeks ago and staff said detectives had not yet been in touch. Police said leads were being assessed in a methodical and structured way.</dd>
      <dt>Hypothesis</dt>
      <dd>Claudia Lawrence resides in Malton.</dd>
      <dt>Relation</dt>
      <dd>Neutral</dd>
      <dt>Segment (Your response)</dt>
      <dd>Claudia Lawrence are not being followed up quickly enough. It comes after hotel staff in Malton contacted police</dd>
    </ul>
  </div>
</fieldset>
<fieldset class="shadow bg-white mb-3">
  <div id="Contradiction" class="w3-container ins w3-animate-opacity">
    <h2>Contradiction Example</h2>
    <p>Here is a pair of premise and hypothesis with Contradiction relation. The following is the Segment you need to respond, which we also emphasize in the premise.</p> 
    <ul>
      <dt>Premise</dt>
      <dd>But an O2 insider said there had been problems with a companies trying to sell the pass codes. Some people were "bound to have been turned away" because of fraudulent tickets. <strong class="w3-text-deep-orange">Led Zeppelin, formed in 1968</strong>, were one of the most influential bands of the 1970s with songs such as Whole Lotta Love and Stairway To Heaven. They split in 1980 after the death of the drummer John Bonham. Kenneth Donnell, 25, who was not born in 1980, spent 83,000 on two tickets in a BBC Children in Need auction.</dd>
      <dt>Hypothesis</dt>
      <dd>The band Led Zeppelin was formed in 1980.</dd>
      <dt>Relation</dt>
      <dd>Contradiction</dd>
      <dt>Segment (Your response)</dt>
      <dd>Led Zeppelin, formed in 1968</dd>
    </ul>
  </div>
</fieldset>
</section>

<!-- Questions Section -->
<section class="container">
  <div class="alert alert-danger text-center shadow" role="alert" style="font-weight: bold; font-size: large">
  All answers will be manually checked, SPAM and blank answers will be definitely rejected.
  </div>  
  <form name='mturk_form' method='post' id='mturk_form' action='https://www.mturk.com/mturk/externalSubmit'><input type='hidden' value='' name='assignmentId' id='assignmentId'/>
    <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 1</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">A train driver from the United Kingdom has had his conviction for manslaughter over a head-on rail collision in 1989 quashed. A train operated by Robert Morgan 64 passed a red signal at Purley and struck an oncoming service on March 4 1989 killing five and injuring 80 more. Morgan's train had been destined for London Victoria having left Littlehampton but after passing through the red light struck a Horsham-to-Victoria train at 60mph.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Robert Morgan killed 5 people.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="401" id="401" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 2</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">This latest round of voting was to replace the results of the second run-off election held on November 21 2004. After the November vote many international observers criticized the vote as fraudulent and some regions saw voter turnout listed in excess of 100% prompting the opposition including Mr. Yushchenko to assert that the results were invalid. Supporters of the opposition pursued legal channels such as appealing to the country's parliament and its Supreme Court as well as maintained a blocade of key government buildings in an effort to force a new election.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Yushchenko is a banker.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Neutral</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="402" id="402" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 3</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">It is possible that it could help McCain earn the support of conservatives who have not always viewed him as aligning with the party on certain issues. At the same time it could help to align McCain with former President Ronald Reagan who attracted Republican and Democratic voters.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Ronald Reagan endorsed McCain.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Neutral</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="403" id="403" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 4</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">New South Wales Police say a 21-year-old woman has been charged in relation to the riots at Sydney's Cronulla Beach last year. She is the first woman to be arrested over reprisals from the December 11 race-fuelled riot. The woman was charged with affray assaulting police resisting arrest and disobeying police direction. She was refused bail. Police said the charges related to the violent and anti-social behaviour of a large number of people who gathered at Brighton-le-Sands on the night of the Cronulla riot.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">A woman has been arrested in the Cronulla riot case.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="404" id="404" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 5</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Others such as Yves Engler expect famines and massive starvation to continue in the region as long as the IMF continues to influence economic policies in the region. Yves Engler has claimed consistently with Amartya Sen's analysis that the IMF is responsible for worsening or actually creating famine in Malawi (2002) Ethiopia (2003) and Niger (2005). The present drought has been said to be getting worse by the day and the total figure for those who need food from the World Food Program could rise from today's 1.2 million to exceed 2.5 million people according to United Nations (UN) spokesman Stephane Dujarric at the organisation's New York headquarters.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Kenya is in need of food.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Neutral</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="405" id="405" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 6</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Encyclopaedia Britannica (EB) the authoritative reference book first published in 1768 is planning to let readers edit its entries Jorge Cauz its president said Friday as it battles to keep pace with online Internet encyclopedia projects like Wikipedia. Starting next week readers visitors and contributing experts to EB's free online version Britannica.com will be allowed to submit proposed changes and contributions to Britannica editors who will then review the edits and make the necessary alterations. This move is meant to let readers help keep the reference work up-to-date by collaboration. In expanding and maintaining entries online users whose editorial suggestions are accepted and published entirely or in part will be credited by name in the section of the article that lists contributors.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">EB users will be able to edit its content.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="406" id="406" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 7</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Venus Williams triumphed over Marion Bartoli of France 6-4 6-1 yesterday to win the Women's Singles event at the 2007 Wimbledon Championships. For the first time an American and Frenchwoman were matched up to compete for the British women's singles title. A Wimbledon champion in 2000 2001 and 2005 Williams was not the favorite to win the title again this year. Currently ranked 23rd in the world she entered the tournament in the shadow of her sister Serena Williams.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Venus Williams was defeated by Marion Bartoli at the 2007 Wimbledon Championships.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Contradiction</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="407" id="407" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 8</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">British writer Doris Lessing recipient of the 2007 Nobel Prize in Literature has said in an interview that the terrorist attack on September 11 "wasn't that terrible" when compared to attacks the Irish Republican Army (IRA) made on Britain. "September 11 was terrible but if one re-examines the history of the IRA what happened in the United States wasn't so bad" Lessing told leading Spanish daily publication El Pais. "Some Americans believe I'm crazy. Many people died two prominent buildings fell but it was neither as terrible nor so extraordinary as they think.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Doris Lessing won the Nobel Prize in Literature in 2007.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="408" id="408" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 9</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">"While we appreciate Ms. Sierra's past efforts to support US troops including performing for them in Iraq on Independence Day it is quite obvious that Ms. Sierra needs to devote a great deal of time to putting her life back together. That effort must take place in private and not in the limelight of the public eye or on the stage." said a statement by retired Air Force Lieutenant Colonel Buzz Patterson concerning the event. Patterson said Move America Forward who is organizing the concert had received comments from patrons who were concerned about her participation. John Fitzgibbons attorney for Jessica refused to comment.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Jessica Sierra once reached the finals of "American Idol".</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Neutral</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="409" id="409" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 10</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">After having a meeting in Bari Italy on the 13th of March the President of Russia Vladimir Putin and the Prime Minister of Italy Romano Prodi gave a press-conference summarizing the results of their conversations. The main point the two leaders agreed on was that only diplomatic means should be used in solving such international conflicts as in Afghanistan Iraq and especially Iran with its nuclear program issue.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Russia and Italy agree diplomacy is the way to solve international conflicts.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="410" id="410" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 11</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Copyright is a kind of monopoly that is granted to the creator so that they may get the revenue that they need enough to incentivise (sic) them to make the initial work. So copyright is a trade-off between the interests of us the public the audience human beings who need culture to survive and thrive and artists who in order to make this culture need an incentive. In the law it is said that for a certain length of time you have the rights to exploit this cultural product that has come from your loins and after that it enters the public domain and everyone enjoys it without restrictions.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">A copyright is a kind of monopoly.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="411" id="411" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 12</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">In November 2006 Pensacola Florida evangelist Kent Hovind and his wife Jo were found guilty on 58 federal counts of "willful failure" to payroll taxes structuring bank withdrawals and obstructing federal agents. On January 19 2007 Hovind was given ten years in federal prison ordered to pay $640000 in owed funds to the Internal Revenue Service pay prosecution's court costs of $7078 and serve three years parole once released. Originally in November Hovind was ordered to forfeit $430400 and faced a maximum of 288 years in prison.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Hovind was found guilty on 59 federal counts.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Contradiction</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="412" id="412" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 13</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">A 13km section of road between Macclesfield and Buxton known as the Cat and Fiddle Road has been named as Britain's most dangerous road. The single-carriageway road has been the scene of 43 fatal or serious collisions since 2001 nearly three-quarters of them involving motorcyclists. When collisions involving motorcyclists are removed from the analysis this 13km stretch moves from the highest risk road in the country to one of the safest. Overall if motorcyclist collisions are removed from the league table the A61 road between Barnsley and Wakefield is revealed as the most dangerous road in Britain.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">The Cat and Fiddle Road is Britain's most dangerous road.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="413" id="413" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 14</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">On February 24th the Swedish Royal Court announced that the Crown Princess Victoria was to be married in 2010 to her boyfriend and former fitness trainer Daniel Westling. Victoria 31 and Daniel 35 have been in an relationship for 7 years. Since the wedding is to be held in the summer of 2010 it gives the court 18 months to prepare contemplate the wedding dress of Victoria and complete the guest-list which will include Europe and the world's most prominent guests.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Princess Victoria will get married in 2010.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="414" id="414" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 15</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Former Republican governor Carroll Campbell will lie in state today on the second floor of the Statehouse in Columbia SC. He suffered from a fatal heart attack on Wednesday. He was 65. He was a native of Greenville. There will be a funeral at Trinity Episcopal Church in Columbia at 10:30 a.m. local time on Saturday and there will be an additional funeral service and burial at All Saints Episcopal Church in Pawleys Island.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Governor Carroll Campbell died on Wednesday.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="415" id="415" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 16</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Despite legislation enacted by Congress and signed into law by President Barack Obama on Wednesday more than one-third of television stations in the United States are planning to move ahead with the transition to digital television according to reports. The transition which was scheduled for February 17 has been pushed back to June 12 2009 per the DTV Delay Act enacted on Wednesday. However it left a loophole for broadcasters allowing them to make the switch anytime between February 17 and June 12.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">TV stations are going to switch to digital.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="416" id="416" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 17</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Around 15:00 the first train had stopped at the station of Roccasecca and was just to restart its journey when the second train came at high speed on the same rail slamming into the back of it. The locomotive of the second train was pushed over the first train and landed on the last carriage of that train. The injured were taken to local hospitals for treatment.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">A railway disaster caused a fire.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Neutral</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="417" id="417" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 18</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">A message posted on the Virginia Tech web page said that classes will be canceled today and tomorrow. Faculty and students have been told to evacuate the campus. All 23 schools in Montgomery County VA are on lockdown. President George W. Bush was made aware of the shootings and according to the White House said "thoughts and prayers for those who are dealing with this." Senate majority and minority leaders Harry Reid and Mitch McConnell led a prayer service and moment of silence for the faculty students and everyone at Virginia Tech during the Senate floor session. House speaker Nancy Pelosi led a prayer and moment of silence on the House floor.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">A student used a gun at school.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Neutral</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="418" id="418" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 19</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Apple have released several re-designs of their popular iPod range. In addition to the iPod Classic Nano and Shuffle they have announced the brand new iPod touch a media player which mimics the iPhone's touch-screen capabilities. The new iPod Classic design features a larger memory space of up to 160GB or 40000 songs and has a new all-metal design. The iPod nano is now smaller and squarer adding video playback to its features for the first time. The 4GB model is cheaper than its predecessor at $149/£99 but the 8GB is available in five colours at $199/£129. The iPod Shuffle is identical in design to the previous model but is now available in a new range of five colours with the same price of $79/£49.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Apple is the producer of the iPod.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="419" id="419" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 20</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">England and Australia are set to showdown for the 2018 FIFA World Cup. Other interested countries are China Japan Mexico the Netherlands Qatar and  Russia. FIFA President has encourage Spain to bid for the 2018 World Cup. The final decision to decide the host nation(s) will be in 2011.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">A European qualifies for the World Cup.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Neutral</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="420" id="420" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>

  <button type="submit" class="btn btn-info btn-raised btn-lg btn-block" id='submitButton'>Submit</button>
  
</form>
</section>
<script language='Javascript'>turkSetAssignmentID();</script>

     

</body>
</html>

<script src="https://code.jquery.com/jquery-3.3.1.slim.min.js" integrity="sha384-q8i/X+965DzO0rT7abK41JStQIAqVgRVzpbzo5smXKp4YfRvH+8abtTE1Pi6jizo" crossorigin="anonymous"></script>
<script src="https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/popper.js/1.14.6/umd/popper.min.js" integrity="sha384-wHAiFfRlMFy6i5SRaxvfOCifBUQy1xHdJ/yoi7FRNXMRBu5WHdZYu1hA6ZOblgut" crossorigin="anonymous"></script>
<script src="https://stackpath.bootstrapcdn.com/bootstrap/4.2.1/js/bootstrap.min.js" integrity="sha384-B0UglyR+jN6CkvvICOB2joaf5I4l3gm9GU6Hc1og6Ls7i6U/mkkaduKaBhlAXv9k" crossorigin="anonymous"></script>
]]>
</HTMLContent>
<FrameHeight>0</FrameHeight>
</HTMLQuestion>