<HTMLQuestion xmlns="http://mechanicalturk.amazonaws.com/AWSMechanicalTurkDataSchemas/2011-11-11/HTMLQuestion.xsd">
<HTMLContent><![CDATA[
<!DOCTYPE html>
<html>
<head>
<meta http-equiv='Content-Type' content='text/html; charset=UTF-8'/>
<script type='text/javascript' src='https://s3.amazonaws.com/mturk-public/externalHIT_v1.js'></script>
<script src="https://sdk.amazonaws.com/js/aws-sdk-2.142.0.min.js"></script>
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://stackpath.bootstrapcdn.com/bootstrap/4.2.1/css/bootstrap.min.css" integrity="sha384-GJzZqFGwb1QTTN6wy59ffF1BuGJpLSa9DkKMp0DgiMDm4iYMj70gZWKYbI706tWS" crossorigin="anonymous">
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://www.w3schools.com/w3css/4/w3.css">
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://unpkg.com/bootstrap-material-design@4.1.1/dist/css/bootstrap-material-design.min.css" integrity="sha384-wXznGJNEXNG1NFsbm0ugrLFMQPWswR3lds2VeinahP8N0zJw9VWSopbjv2x7WCvX" crossorigin="anonymous">
<style>
  dt{
    font-size: medium;
  }

  dd{
    margin-bottom: 1rem; 
    margin-left: 0;
  }
  
  .card-text{
    margin-bottom: 2rem;
  }

  h5{
    font-weight: bold;
  }
  .tablink{
    font-weight: 600;
  }

  .btn-lg{
    font-size: 2rem;
    line-height: 4rem;
  }
  h2{
    margin-top: 1rem;
  }
  p{
    font-size: 1rem;
  }
</style>
</head>

<body>
<section class="container mb-3 mt-3">
  <fieldset class="shadow bg-white mb-3">
<div class="w3-container">
  <h2 class="text-info" style="font-weight: bolder">Instructions and Examples</h2>
  <div id="Instructions" class="w3-container ins w3-animate-opacity" style="display:block">
    <h2>Instructions</h2>
    <p>Read the premise, hypothesis and realation, select a segment from premise that can determine the relation between premise and hypothesis.</p>
    <ul>
      <!-- We are adding a template variable below which we will replace with an actual link in our code later -->
      <li>Read the premise, hypothesis and the relation.</li>
      <li>On the basis of your own judgement, select a "sequential" segment from premise that can determine the relation between premise and hypothesis.</li>
      <li>The length is not restricted, as long as the segment provides sufficient informations.</li>
      <li>Copy the segment from premise and paste it into the following box.</li>
      <li><strong>SPAM and non-sequential segments will be rejected.</strong></li>
      </ul>
    <p>The following section is the definition of the three realations, which comes from the RTE-5 task guideline. If you are familiar with NLI tasks such as SNLI, MNLI, RTE, you can skip the section below.</p>
    <p>We define textual entailment as a directional relationship between a pair of text fragments, which we call the "Premise" and the "Hypothesis". We say that: </p>
    <p><strong><i>Premise entails Hypothesis, if a human reading premise would infer that hypothesis is most likely true. </i></strong></p>
    <p>For example, given assumed common background knowledge of the business news domain and the following premise: </p>
    <p style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><strong><i>Premise1 Internet media company Yahoo Inc. announced Monday it is buying Overture Services Inc. in a $1.63-billion (U.S.) cash-and-stock deal that will bolster its on-line search capabilities.</i></strong></p>
    <p>the following hypothesis is entailed:</p>
    <ul>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.1 Yahoo boutght Overture</i></p></li>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.2 Overture acquired by Yahoo</i></p></li>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.3 Overture was bought</i></p></li>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.4 Yahoo is an internet company</i></p></li>
    </ul>
    <p>For example, the following hypothesis are contradicted by Premise above:</p>
    <ul>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.5 Overture bought Yahoo</i></p></li>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.6 Yahoo sold Overture</i></p></li>
    </ul>
    <p>While the following ones cannot be judged on the basis of Premise above:</p>
    <ul>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.7 Yahoo manufatures cars</i></p></li>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.8 Overture shareholders will receive $4.75 cash and 0.6108 Yahoo stock for each of their shares.</i></p></li>
    </ul>
  </div>
  
</div>
</fieldset>
<fieldset class="shadow bg-white mb-3">
  <div id="Entailment" class="w3-container ins w3-animate-opacity">
    <h2>Entailment Example</h2>
    <p>Here is a pair of premise and hypothesis with entailment relation. The following is the Segment you need to respond, which we also emphasize in the premise.</p>
    <ul>
      <dt style="font-size: medium;">Premise</dt>
      <dd style='margin-bottom: 1rem; margin-left: 0;'>CNN) -- Malawians are rallying behind <strong class="w3-text-deep-orange">Madonna as she awaits a ruling Friday on whether she can adopt a girl from the southern African nation. The pop star, who has three children</strong>, adopted a son from Malawi in 2006. She is seeking to adopt Chifundo "Mercy" James, 4. "Ninety-nine percent of the people calling in are saying, 'let her take the baby,' " said Marilyn Segula, a presenter at Capital FM, which broadcasts in at least five cities, including the capital, Lilongwe.</t>
      <h>Madonna has three children.</dd>
      <dt>Hypothesis</dt>
      <dd>Madonna has three children.</dd>
      <dt>Relation</dt>
      <dd>Entailment</dd>
      <dt>Segment (Your response)</dt>
      <dd>Madonna as she awaits a ruling Friday on whether she can adopt a girl from the southern African nation. The pop star, who has three children</dd>
    </ul>
  </div>
</fieldset>
<fieldset class="shadow bg-white mb-3">
  <div id="Neutral" class="w3-container ins w3-animate-opacity">
    <h2>Neutral Example</h2>
    <p>Here is a pair of premise and hypothesis with neutral relation. The following is the Segment you need to respond, which we also emphasize in the premise.</p> 
    <ul>
      <dt>Premise</dt>
      <dd>Concerns have been raised that potential leads in the hunt for missing York woman <strong class="w3-text-deep-orange">Claudia Lawrence are not being followed up quickly enough. It comes after hotel staff in Malton contacted police</strong> after a stranger in the bar expressed satisfaction when asked if the chef was still missing. The incident happened more than three weeks ago and staff said detectives had not yet been in touch. Police said leads were being assessed in a methodical and structured way.</dd>
      <dt>Hypothesis</dt>
      <dd>Claudia Lawrence resides in Malton.</dd>
      <dt>Relation</dt>
      <dd>Neutral</dd>
      <dt>Segment (Your response)</dt>
      <dd>Claudia Lawrence are not being followed up quickly enough. It comes after hotel staff in Malton contacted police</dd>
    </ul>
  </div>
</fieldset>
<fieldset class="shadow bg-white mb-3">
  <div id="Contradiction" class="w3-container ins w3-animate-opacity">
    <h2>Contradiction Example</h2>
    <p>Here is a pair of premise and hypothesis with Contradiction relation. The following is the Segment you need to respond, which we also emphasize in the premise.</p> 
    <ul>
      <dt>Premise</dt>
      <dd>But an O2 insider said there had been problems with a companies trying to sell the pass codes. Some people were "bound to have been turned away" because of fraudulent tickets. <strong class="w3-text-deep-orange">Led Zeppelin, formed in 1968</strong>, were one of the most influential bands of the 1970s with songs such as Whole Lotta Love and Stairway To Heaven. They split in 1980 after the death of the drummer John Bonham. Kenneth Donnell, 25, who was not born in 1980, spent 83,000 on two tickets in a BBC Children in Need auction.</dd>
      <dt>Hypothesis</dt>
      <dd>The band Led Zeppelin was formed in 1980.</dd>
      <dt>Relation</dt>
      <dd>Contradiction</dd>
      <dt>Segment (Your response)</dt>
      <dd>Led Zeppelin, formed in 1968</dd>
    </ul>
  </div>
</fieldset>
</section>

<!-- Questions Section -->
<section class="container">
  <div class="alert alert-danger text-center shadow" role="alert" style="font-weight: bold; font-size: large">
  All answers will be manually checked, SPAM and blank answers will be definitely rejected.
  </div>  
  <form name='mturk_form' method='post' id='mturk_form' action='https://www.mturk.com/mturk/externalSubmit'><input type='hidden' value='' name='assignmentId' id='assignmentId'/>
    <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 1</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">The two primes were announced by GIMPS on September 16. Before these two discoveries the two previously largest known prime numbers were discovered by UCMO professors Curtis Cooper and Steven Boone in Missouri United States and their record lasted almost three years. Historically prime numbers discovered by GIMPS are larger than the one previously found. The only other exception was when the 29th Mersenne prime was discovered after the 30th and 31st were found. Founded by M.I.T. graduate George Woltman in 1996 GIMPS has found 12 Mersenne primes or about one per year on average. Volunteers who wish to help find primes can download a program called Prime95 which runs in the background. Smaller prime numbers such as those with a few hundred digits are often used in cryptography.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">GIMPS was founded by George Woltman.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="301" id="301" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 2</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Barack Obama is due to end his first overseas trip as US President today. Mr Obama has attended a series of engagements in Europe over the past week including the G20 summit in London a NATO meeting in Strasbourg and a conference of EU leaders in Prague. He is currently in Turkey where he has been seeking to reach out a hand to the Islamic world. Mr Obama is due to head back to the US this afternoon after visiting two of Istanbul's most historic buildings the Blue Mosque and the Hagia Sophia Church.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Barack Obama is an EU leader.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Contradiction</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="302" id="302" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 3</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Despite international appeals North Korea has gone ahead with a long publicised rocket launch. Authorities from the United States Japan and South Korea confirm that the rocket lifted off at 11.32 local time (02.32 GMT) on Sunday April 5 2009. "A short time ago a flying object appeared to have been launched from North Korea" read a statement by the Japanese government. The rocket seems to have passed over the Japanese capital of Tokyo and headed over the Pacific Ocean. Two parts of the rocket the first and second stages fell either side of the Japanese home islands falling into the Sea of Japan and the Pacific. A statement by the North Korean official news agency said that the rocket had successfully launched a satellite which is now broadcasting "data" and North Korean propaganda songs.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Tokyo is the capital of Japan.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="303" id="303" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 4</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Friends have said Poplawski was concerned about his weapons being seized during Barack Obama's presidency and friends said he owned several handguns and an AK-47 assault rifle. Three officers killed. Autopsies show Sciullo 37 died of wounds to the head and torso. Mayhle 29 was shot in the head. A witness awakened by two gunshots told investigators of seeing the gunman standing in the home's front doorway and firing two to three shots into one officer who was already down. Sciullo was later found dead in the home's living room and Mayhle near the front stoop police said. A third officer Eric Kelly 41 was killed as he arrived to assist the first two officers. Kelly was in uniform but on his way home when he responded and was gunned down in the street. Kelly's radio call for help summoned other officers including a SWAT team.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Sciullo was killed by Poplawski.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="304" id="304" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 5</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">While hybrid vehicles have found considerable popularity in the United States since their introduction one difficulty associated with the rollout of a fully electric car has been the comparably high price and poor performance compared to an internal combustion engine-driven car of similar size. Tesla Motors claims that their Model S a sedan which runs solely on electricity will be more affordable. Tesla first entered the automobile market in 2006 with a prototype of an electric vehicle designed on the roadster style. While the car whose exterior design was based on the Lotus Elise accelerated well and had considerable range its cost of US$109000 was prohibitive for many and to date only 300 have been sold with a thousand more ordered.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Model S is produced by Tesla Motors.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="305" id="305" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 6</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Mount Redoubt a volcano in Alaska erupted on Saturday sending out clouds of ash thousands of feet high. According to the Federal Aviation Administration the Ted Stevens Anchorage International Airport was shut down after ash reached the airport. Jeremy Lindseth a spokesman for the airport said that only small amount of ash reached the airport but was significant enough to disrupt operations as ash can cause engine problems for aircraft. He said that he was uncertain of how many flights were affected due to the eruption. The eruption happened at around 1:30 PM local time the United States Geological Survey reported. The volcano had erupted four times on Friday billowing ash up to 51000 feet up into the air. These are the latest in a series of eruptions from Mount Redoubt which started on March 22. The volcano had not erupted since a four-month period in 1989-90.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Mount Redoubt is in Alaska.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="306" id="306" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 7</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">EW reports at least two characters will be killed during this season which ends in May 2009. During a January interview with New York magazine Mitchell said of the Shakespearean roots in her name " I'm certain it's not random because they're never random. It does seem to me that she's pretty much destined for tragedy whichever way she goes no matter how hard she tries to fight against it."</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Shakespeare is a relative of Mitchell.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Neutral</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="307" id="307" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 8</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">The "House of Sweden" as it will be called will be modelled on the new Swedish embassy in Washington with the same name. The opening is expected in a few weeks. Second life has over 3 million registered accounts. On an average day the maximum of people logged in at the same time peaks at 25000. In September 2006 Second Life was reported to have a gross domestic product of $64 million. Some schools in the United States and Canada have virtual classrooms on the site. People like Ailin Graef a.k.a. Anshe Chung have developed virtual businesses in Second Life and earn thousands of real dollars there.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Ailin Graef is a Swedish citizen.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Neutral</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="308" id="308" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 9</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">The wife and children of Abdel Baset Ali al-Megrahi a Libyan man convicted of the bombing of Pan Am Flight 103 were amongst other relatives and friends of prisoners protesting against alleged miscarriages of justice in Edinburgh yesterday. The airliner came down over Lockerbie Scotland in December 1988 killing 270 people. Megrahi is due an appeal against his conviction next year. Also present at the unprecidented "Silent Walk For Justice" was the family of Jason MacIntyre a champion cyclist killed when Robert McTaggart ran him down in a van in January for which he received a six month driving ban after conviction of careless driving. MacIntyre's wife said McTaggert should have instead been charged with causing death by dangerous driving.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Robert McTaggart killed Jason MacIntyre.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="309" id="309" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 10</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">The names of 77 reporters photographers and broadcasters were added to a memorial to honor slain journalists in the Newseum in Washington D.C. "These 77 individuals were brought together in a fellowship that none of them would have chosen a fellowship created by their commitment their courage and ultimately their sacrifice" said Chris Wells vice president of the Freedom Forum which runs the Newseum. The Newseum Journalist's Memorial contains the names of 1913 journalists dating back to 1837. Thirteen of the names added Monday were journalists killed in Iraq in 2008 which has been the most dangerous country for journalists since the Iraq War began in 2003. Mexico was the second deadliest country for journalists last year with five journalists being killed due to drug violence. According to Newseum records Mexico had not been so dangerous for journalists in at least five years.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">The Newseum was founded in 1837.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Neutral</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="310" id="310" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 11</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Grey's Anatomy star Katherine Heigl and her musician hubby Josh Kelley are adopting a baby from Korea so says the National Enquirer. The Emmy-winning bombshell 29 has decided that instead getting "Knocked Up" she and Josh will start their family with an adopted bundle of joy. "They've finally decided adoption is the best option for them right now. Katherine's got several movie projects in the pipeline and a pregnancy would bring her career to a halt for a while." Welcoming a baby from Korea holds special meaning for Katherine whose doting big sister Meg was adopted from the country more than 30 years ago. "Meg has had a profound impact on Katherine's life which is why she and Josh are trying to adopt a Korean child."</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">A Korean child is going to be adopted by the "Grey's Anatomy" movie.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Contradiction</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="311" id="311" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 12</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Violence has erupted in Guadeloupe after a month-long general strike protesting the high costs of food and fuel. A union official Jacques Bino has been reported killed by armed youths at a barricade in Pointe-à-Pitre the largest city. Three police officers were injured when they tried to reach the scene. "He was killed at a roadblock held by rioters a group of youth who were mostly wearing masks" Prefect Nicolas Desforges told France Info. "He wasn't killed in a confrontation with police." Guadeloupe is an overseas department of France. The French government urged calm and called for a meeting between the disputing parties. Workers in Guadeloupe are seeking a $250 per month pay raise. French Interior Minister Michèle Alliot-Marie said that France is sending 260 National Gendarmerie officers to quell the violence.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Guadeloupe is a French region.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="312" id="312" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 13</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">A man has come forward to say he is the owner of a Thai ship that was being hijacked by pirates then sunk by the Indian navy. The incident took place in the Gulf of Aden off the coast of the African nation of Somalia on November 18. The owner Wicharn Sirichaiekawat says that the boat was a fishing trawler but the pirates had just got on board the vessel when it was fired upon.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">The Gulf of Aden is near the coast of Somalia.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="313" id="313" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 14</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">On October 14 2008 Canadians will be heading to the polls for the federal election. Christian Heritage Party candidate Ron Gray is standing for election in the riding of Langley. Wikinews contacted Ron Gray to talk about the issues facing Canadians and what they and their party would do to address them. Wikinews is in the process of contacting every candidate in every riding across the country no matter their political stripe. All interviews are conducted over e-mail and interviews are published unedited allowing candidates to impart their full message to our readers uninterrupted. Mr. Gray has been leader of the Christian Heritage Party since 1995. He first ran for office in 1988.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">The Christian Heritage Party supports Ron Gray's candidacy.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="314" id="314" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 15</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">The upcoming 2006 Brampton municipal election to be held November 13 features an array of candidates looking to represent their wards in city council or the council of the Peel Region. Wikinews contributor Nick Moreau contacted many of the candidates including Mathew Njenga asking them to answer common questions sent in an email. This ward's incumbent is John A. Hutton; also challenging Hutton is Derrick Coke Navdeep Gill Jim Howell Joyce Rodriguez and Doug Whillans.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Joyce Rodriguez is a resident of Brampton.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="315" id="315" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 16</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Yigal Amir the student who assassinated Israeli Prime Minister Yitzhak Rabin began a hunger strike on June 28th in protest against "the basic human rights abuse by Israel's prison authorities" as he describes it. According to the prison service he's not in a proper hunger strike because he drinks 5 liters of sweet raspberry-flavoured drink (otherwise known as "petel") every day. Disputing that (according to updates from Larisa Trembovler journal) Yigal Amir in a phone conversation insists that it is a lie and he is not given anything near 5 liters of drinks a day. Also regardless of prison service definitions he continues with the hunger strike. The issue of contention is denial of recognition of his marriage to Larisa Trembovler by Israeli Prisons Service.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Yitzhak Rabin was killed by Yigal Amir.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="316" id="316" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 17</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">The seemingly eternal flame of the American soap opera Guiding Light has been extinguished. CBS the network which airs the serial drama in the United States has announced its cancellation after 72 years. Guiding Light which entered the Guinness Book of World Records as the longest-running dramatic series in the world started on radio in 1937 as a series of stories about faith in which characters beset with troubles would talk to trusted Reverend Ruthledge the keeper of "the guiding light" which shone from his window. Over the years the theme of "the guiding light" became more muted and the series shifted focus to a middle-class German immigrant family the Bauers. The show has been produced on television and seen nearly every weekday since June 30 1952.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">CBS is an American TV network.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="317" id="317" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 18</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">The Egyptian Health Ministry reported on Sunday that a six-year-old Egyptian boy contracted bird flu the sixth such incident in a month. The child was hospitalised on March 28 reported to be in critical condition after treatment and is breathing with an artificial respirator. The state news agency MENA revealed that the boy's name was Ali Mahmoud Ali Somaa and that he was from Qalyubia a province located along the Nile Delta located about forty kilometres north of Egypt's capital of Cairo. The death toll of the cases of the bird flu virus in humans in Egypt is 23 with the first incident reported in March 2006. Statistics from the World Health Organisation's (WHO) website say that 413 people in fifteen countries have been infected with the H5N1 virus; out of those 256 have died.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Qalyubia is an Egyptian province.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="318" id="318" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 19</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Miriam Stucky' is running for the Green Party of Ontario in the Ontario provincial election in the Peterborough riding. Wikinews' Nick Moreau interviewed her regarding her values her experience and her campaign. Stay tuned for further interviews; every candidate from every party is eligible and will be contacted. Expect interviews from Liberals Progressive Conservatives New Democratic Party members Ontario Greens as well as members from the Family Coalition Freedom Communist Libertarian and Confederation of Regions parties as well as independents.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Miriam Stucky is a member of the Green Party of Ontario.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="319" id="319" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 20</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">The campaign offices for 2008 United States presidential candidate John McCain in Centennial Colorado and Manchester New Hampshire have been evacuated after receiving letter threats in the U.S. mail. Office staff state that the Centennial envelope contained an unknown white powder. "We immediately notified local and federal law enforcement agencies and are looking to cooperate with them. We have put all of our offices on highest alert. They're looking for anything suspicious and all staff has been quarantined as of right now" said Jeff Sadosky a spokesman for the McCain campaign.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Centennial is a part of New Hampshire.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Contradiction</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="320" id="320" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>

  <button type="submit" class="btn btn-info btn-raised btn-lg btn-block" id='submitButton'>Submit</button>
  
</form>
</section>
<script language='Javascript'>turkSetAssignmentID();</script>

     

</body>
</html>

<script src="https://code.jquery.com/jquery-3.3.1.slim.min.js" integrity="sha384-q8i/X+965DzO0rT7abK41JStQIAqVgRVzpbzo5smXKp4YfRvH+8abtTE1Pi6jizo" crossorigin="anonymous"></script>
<script src="https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/popper.js/1.14.6/umd/popper.min.js" integrity="sha384-wHAiFfRlMFy6i5SRaxvfOCifBUQy1xHdJ/yoi7FRNXMRBu5WHdZYu1hA6ZOblgut" crossorigin="anonymous"></script>
<script src="https://stackpath.bootstrapcdn.com/bootstrap/4.2.1/js/bootstrap.min.js" integrity="sha384-B0UglyR+jN6CkvvICOB2joaf5I4l3gm9GU6Hc1og6Ls7i6U/mkkaduKaBhlAXv9k" crossorigin="anonymous"></script>
]]>
</HTMLContent>
<FrameHeight>0</FrameHeight>
</HTMLQuestion>