<HTMLQuestion xmlns="http://mechanicalturk.amazonaws.com/AWSMechanicalTurkDataSchemas/2011-11-11/HTMLQuestion.xsd">
<HTMLContent><![CDATA[
<!DOCTYPE html>
<html>
<head>
<meta http-equiv='Content-Type' content='text/html; charset=UTF-8'/>
<script type='text/javascript' src='https://s3.amazonaws.com/mturk-public/externalHIT_v1.js'></script>
<script src="https://sdk.amazonaws.com/js/aws-sdk-2.142.0.min.js"></script>
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://stackpath.bootstrapcdn.com/bootstrap/4.2.1/css/bootstrap.min.css" integrity="sha384-GJzZqFGwb1QTTN6wy59ffF1BuGJpLSa9DkKMp0DgiMDm4iYMj70gZWKYbI706tWS" crossorigin="anonymous">
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://www.w3schools.com/w3css/4/w3.css">
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://unpkg.com/bootstrap-material-design@4.1.1/dist/css/bootstrap-material-design.min.css" integrity="sha384-wXznGJNEXNG1NFsbm0ugrLFMQPWswR3lds2VeinahP8N0zJw9VWSopbjv2x7WCvX" crossorigin="anonymous">
<style>
  dt{
    font-size: medium;
  }

  dd{
    margin-bottom: 1rem; 
    margin-left: 0;
  }
  
  .card-text{
    margin-bottom: 2rem;
  }

  h5{
    font-weight: bold;
  }
  .tablink{
    font-weight: 600;
  }

  .btn-lg{
    font-size: 2rem;
    line-height: 4rem;
  }
  h2{
    margin-top: 1rem;
  }
  p{
    font-size: 1rem;
  }
</style>
</head>

<body>
<section class="container mb-3 mt-3">
  <fieldset class="shadow bg-white mb-3">
<div class="w3-container">
  <h2 class="text-info" style="font-weight: bolder">Instructions and Examples</h2>
  <div id="Instructions" class="w3-container ins w3-animate-opacity" style="display:block">
    <h2>Instructions</h2>
    <p>Read the premise, hypothesis and realation, select a segment from premise that can determine the relation between premise and hypothesis.</p>
    <ul>
      <!-- We are adding a template variable below which we will replace with an actual link in our code later -->
      <li>Read the premise, hypothesis and the relation.</li>
      <li>On the basis of your own judgement, select a "sequential" segment from premise that can determine the relation between premise and hypothesis.</li>
      <li>The length is not restricted, as long as the segment provides sufficient informations.</li>
      <li>Copy the segment from premise and paste it into the following box.</li>
      <li><strong>SPAM and non-sequential segments will be rejected.</strong></li>
      </ul>
    <p>The following section is the definition of the three realations, which comes from the RTE-5 task guideline. If you are familiar with NLI tasks such as SNLI, MNLI, RTE, you can skip the section below.</p>
    <p>We define textual entailment as a directional relationship between a pair of text fragments, which we call the "Premise" and the "Hypothesis". We say that: </p>
    <p><strong><i>Premise entails Hypothesis, if a human reading premise would infer that hypothesis is most likely true. </i></strong></p>
    <p>For example, given assumed common background knowledge of the business news domain and the following premise: </p>
    <p style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><strong><i>Premise1 Internet media company Yahoo Inc. announced Monday it is buying Overture Services Inc. in a $1.63-billion (U.S.) cash-and-stock deal that will bolster its on-line search capabilities.</i></strong></p>
    <p>the following hypothesis is entailed:</p>
    <ul>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.1 Yahoo boutght Overture</i></p></li>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.2 Overture acquired by Yahoo</i></p></li>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.3 Overture was bought</i></p></li>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.4 Yahoo is an internet company</i></p></li>
    </ul>
    <p>For example, the following hypothesis are contradicted by Premise above:</p>
    <ul>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.5 Overture bought Yahoo</i></p></li>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.6 Yahoo sold Overture</i></p></li>
    </ul>
    <p>While the following ones cannot be judged on the basis of Premise above:</p>
    <ul>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.7 Yahoo manufatures cars</i></p></li>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.8 Overture shareholders will receive $4.75 cash and 0.6108 Yahoo stock for each of their shares.</i></p></li>
    </ul>
  </div>
  
</div>
</fieldset>
<fieldset class="shadow bg-white mb-3">
  <div id="Entailment" class="w3-container ins w3-animate-opacity">
    <h2>Entailment Example</h2>
    <p>Here is a pair of premise and hypothesis with entailment relation. The following is the Segment you need to respond, which we also emphasize in the premise.</p>
    <ul>
      <dt style="font-size: medium;">Premise</dt>
      <dd style='margin-bottom: 1rem; margin-left: 0;'>CNN) -- Malawians are rallying behind <strong class="w3-text-deep-orange">Madonna as she awaits a ruling Friday on whether she can adopt a girl from the southern African nation. The pop star, who has three children</strong>, adopted a son from Malawi in 2006. She is seeking to adopt Chifundo "Mercy" James, 4. "Ninety-nine percent of the people calling in are saying, 'let her take the baby,' " said Marilyn Segula, a presenter at Capital FM, which broadcasts in at least five cities, including the capital, Lilongwe.</t>
      <h>Madonna has three children.</dd>
      <dt>Hypothesis</dt>
      <dd>Madonna has three children.</dd>
      <dt>Relation</dt>
      <dd>Entailment</dd>
      <dt>Segment (Your response)</dt>
      <dd>Madonna as she awaits a ruling Friday on whether she can adopt a girl from the southern African nation. The pop star, who has three children</dd>
    </ul>
  </div>
</fieldset>
<fieldset class="shadow bg-white mb-3">
  <div id="Neutral" class="w3-container ins w3-animate-opacity">
    <h2>Neutral Example</h2>
    <p>Here is a pair of premise and hypothesis with neutral relation. The following is the Segment you need to respond, which we also emphasize in the premise.</p> 
    <ul>
      <dt>Premise</dt>
      <dd>Concerns have been raised that potential leads in the hunt for missing York woman <strong class="w3-text-deep-orange">Claudia Lawrence are not being followed up quickly enough. It comes after hotel staff in Malton contacted police</strong> after a stranger in the bar expressed satisfaction when asked if the chef was still missing. The incident happened more than three weeks ago and staff said detectives had not yet been in touch. Police said leads were being assessed in a methodical and structured way.</dd>
      <dt>Hypothesis</dt>
      <dd>Claudia Lawrence resides in Malton.</dd>
      <dt>Relation</dt>
      <dd>Neutral</dd>
      <dt>Segment (Your response)</dt>
      <dd>Claudia Lawrence are not being followed up quickly enough. It comes after hotel staff in Malton contacted police</dd>
    </ul>
  </div>
</fieldset>
<fieldset class="shadow bg-white mb-3">
  <div id="Contradiction" class="w3-container ins w3-animate-opacity">
    <h2>Contradiction Example</h2>
    <p>Here is a pair of premise and hypothesis with Contradiction relation. The following is the Segment you need to respond, which we also emphasize in the premise.</p> 
    <ul>
      <dt>Premise</dt>
      <dd>But an O2 insider said there had been problems with a companies trying to sell the pass codes. Some people were "bound to have been turned away" because of fraudulent tickets. <strong class="w3-text-deep-orange">Led Zeppelin, formed in 1968</strong>, were one of the most influential bands of the 1970s with songs such as Whole Lotta Love and Stairway To Heaven. They split in 1980 after the death of the drummer John Bonham. Kenneth Donnell, 25, who was not born in 1980, spent 83,000 on two tickets in a BBC Children in Need auction.</dd>
      <dt>Hypothesis</dt>
      <dd>The band Led Zeppelin was formed in 1980.</dd>
      <dt>Relation</dt>
      <dd>Contradiction</dd>
      <dt>Segment (Your response)</dt>
      <dd>Led Zeppelin, formed in 1968</dd>
    </ul>
  </div>
</fieldset>
</section>

<!-- Questions Section -->
<section class="container">
  <div class="alert alert-danger text-center shadow" role="alert" style="font-weight: bold; font-size: large">
  All answers will be manually checked, SPAM and blank answers will be definitely rejected.
  </div>  
  <form name='mturk_form' method='post' id='mturk_form' action='https://www.mturk.com/mturk/externalSubmit'><input type='hidden' value='' name='assignmentId' id='assignmentId'/>
    <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 1</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Shown on a test run with President Obama in the White House on March 15 2009 the black-and-white Portuguese water dog is a gift to President Obama's daughters Malia and Sasha from Senator Edward M. Kennedy who also owns Portuguese water dogs. Despite their lapdog looks Portuguese water dogs are classified as working dogs. That means the pups seem to enjoy being given jobs that allow them to display their intelligence strength and stamina. "This breed possesses a lot of energy so without training or a job to do the dog may entertain itself by running full-speed down the West Wing or barking at Republicans" said animal behaviorist Mary Burch of the American Kennel Club.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Bo is the new dog of President Obama.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Neutral</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="121" id="121" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 2</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">In a sense Italy has never lost the art of la dolce vita: that is why millions of tourists go there every year to discover (or rediscover) the leisurely lunch and the contemplation of beauty. But Mr Petrini who founded Slow Food in 1986 as a reaction to the arrival of McDonald's near the Spanish Steps in Rome began his campaign out of fear that the Mediterranean way of life was being eroded by alien habits such as a sandwich at the desk instead of lunch. "We are enslaved by speed and have all succumbed to the same insidious virus: Fast Life which disrupts our habits invades the privacy of our homes and forces us to eat Fast Foods" he wrote.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Petrini is the founder of McDonalds.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Contradiction</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="122" id="122" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 3</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">(CBS/AP) A middle-aged volunteer church worker with the voice of an angel is Britain's latest unlikely showbiz star. Susan Boyle 47 wowed judges and audience alike when she performed on the television contest "Britain's Got Talent." When Boyle stepped on stage she told the show's judges "I'm nearly 48 currently unemployed but still looking..." But not likely unemployed for much longer reports CBS News correspondent Mark Phillips. By Wednesday morning a video clip of Boyle's performance on YouTube had been viewed more than 5 million times.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Susan Boyle is a contestant on "Britain's Got Talent".</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="123" id="123" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 4</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">MOSCOW — Authorities in Dubai said Sunday that they believed the murder of Sulim B. Yamadayev a former Chechen general had been planned by a member of Russia's lower house of Parliament who is a well-known ally of the Chechen president. At a news conference Dubai's chief of police Lt. Gen. Dahi Khalfan bin Tamim said that he would ask Interpol to arrest the member of Parliament Adam S. Delimkhanov and that it was "Russia's responsibility in front of the world to control these killers from Chechnya."</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Sulim B. Yamadayev was a Chechen general.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="124" id="124" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 5</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Mexico's new president Felipe Calderon seems to be doing all the right things in cracking down on Mexico's drug traffickers. He's appointed new people to key military and criminal justice positions deployed troops to quell drug violence reasserted federal police power extradited a few major traffickers to the United States and given a green light to legislation clarifying Mexico's drug laws. But all this provides little reason to hope that Mexico has really turned a corner in its efforts to control the illegal drug trade. For a guide to what's in store one need only look at past sexenios (the six year terms of Mexican presidents).</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Felipe Calderon is the outgoing President of Mexico.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Contradiction</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="125" id="125" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 6</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">DETROIT — The Treasury Department is directing Chrysler to prepare a Chapter 11 bankruptcy filing as soon as next week people with direct knowledge of the talks said Thursday. The company faces a deadline of April 30 to come up with a viable business plan supported by its creditors the United Automobile Workers union and Fiat the Italian car company that wants to acquire a stake in Chrysler. The Obama administration has told Chrysler it will provide up to $6 billion in new financing on top of the $4 billion in loans it has already given the company if Chrysler can complete a deal by next Thursday with a cost structure that gives it a chance of survival. The creditors have so far balked at the terms suggested by the Treasury.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Fiat wants to gain possession of a stake in Chrysler.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="126" id="126" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 7</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Updated The Senate confirmation of Governor Kathleen Sebelius — who would be the final member to join the Obama Cabinet as secretary of Health and Human Services — hit more snags on Thursday because of Republican opposition. It's increasingly likely that her nomination will face a procedural hurdle requiring 60 votes before final approval at the earliest next week. The Majority Leader Senator Harry Reid Democrat of Nevada tried unsuccessfully to get unanimous consent to confirm Ms. Sebelius. But after a 15-8 vote out of the Senate Finance Committee earlier this week it had already been pretty clear that a smooth path to confirmation wasn't likely.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Kathleen Sebelius comes from Nevada.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Neutral</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="127" id="127" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 8</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Prince Charles and his wife Camilla and their 10-member staff are visiting Rome and Venic and t Berlin before they return to Britain. The plane is said to contain a master suite and private bathroom and costs more than $116000 to charter. Prince Charles and his wife met today with the Pope Benedict XVI at the Vatican to talk about the environment. The prince's spokesperson at Clarence House told ABC News that the prince was scheduled to fly on a Royale Air Force jet for his European tour but the plane suddenly became "unserviceable" Friday the day before the trip was to start and he was .</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Benedict XVI is the current Pope.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="128" id="128" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 9</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Americans however aren't the only ones who began 2009 with a landmark inauguration. Iceland swore in Johanna Sigurdardottir on Sunday as not only the country's first female prime minister but also the world's first openly queer head of government. It is difficult to make a perfect comparison between Iceland's situation and our own; Iceland's population is less than a one-hundredth of ours and because of their parliamentary system Sigurdardottir was never popularly elected. But that doesn't mean we can't ask in a return to our initial speculation "What's coming next for America?" One of the best places to begin to unravel this puzzle is interestingly with the Republican Party. Since the 1960s the Republican Party has catered to an almost exclusively white base and has incorporated relatively few politicians from minority backgrounds.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Johanna Sigurdardottir is Republican.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Neutral</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="129" id="129" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 10</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">A reward of $2m (£1.37m) each will be paid to informers who help arrest Mexico's 24 most-wanted drug gang chiefs the attorney general has said. Correspondents say the most-wanted list is a public challenge to the cartels. Some 8000 people have died in the past two years as drug gangs fight for territory amid government crackdowns. US and Mexican agencies are increasing their co-operation as the gang violence spills over the border where kidnaps and killings are on the rise.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">The reward for informers in Mexico is 2 million dollars.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="130" id="130" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 11</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">PORT-AU-PRINCE Haiti — Paul Collier a leading poverty guru spent a recent morning here waxing positive about how the world's economic freefall might prove the perfect moment for Haiti to sell more exports like T-shirts and mangoes to Americans. His improbable enthusiasm coincided with appearances by a bevy of luminaries descending on Haiti this month including Ban Ki-moon the United Nations secretary general and the entire Security Council. All of them came to stress that this destitute nation stands at a crossroads between salvation and "the darkness" as Mr. Ban put it.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Paul Collier is the United Nations Secretary General.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Contradiction</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="131" id="131" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 12</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">It was one of the most gruesome crimes this northern Colorado farming town has seen. The man accused of killing Ms. Zapata Allen R. Andrade 32 told the police that he had attacked her upon discovering that she was biologically a man after the two met on the Internet and had a sexual encounter. In a chilling arrest affidavit Mr. Andrade said he thought he had "killed it" after striking Ms. Zapata in the head until she stopped breathing. Now Mr. Andrade stands accused of first-degree murder in what national gay rights groups say is the first trial in which a hate-crime statute has been used to prosecute the killing of a transgender person.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Angie Zapata has been killed with a fire extinguisher.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Neutral</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="132" id="132" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 13</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">WEARE N.H. — The black flies were swarming outside Justice David H. Souter's house on a dirt road here last week and the house itself — with peeling paint rotting wood and tattered shades pulled low — looked only slightly more seductive than a mud hut. Yet to Justice Souter who told President Obama last week that he would retire from the Supreme Court in June and return to rural New Hampshire at the relatively young age of 69 this is apparently heaven. In this town of stone walls and bumpy roads he can climb nearby mountains jog unnoticed and one can imagine read by candlelight amid the piles of books said to dominate his house.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">President Obama has a house in New Hampshire.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Neutral</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="133" id="133" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 14</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">VATICAN CITY When Pope Benedict XVI embarks on his first trip to Africa as pontiff on Tuesday traveling to Cameroon and Angola he will be visiting the future of the Roman Catholic Church if not its present. With one of the world's largest Catholic populations estimated at 158 million Africa is the continent where the church is at once strong in terms of sheer numbers and devotional vitality and weak inevitably touched by the poverty corruption conflict and disease afflicting the larger society.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Africa is estimated to have a 158-million Catholic population.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="134" id="134" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 15</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">EVERLY HILLS Calif. — Here's a new economic indicator: the diminishing level of glamour on Paris Hilton's reality TV show. Contestants in season two of "Paris Hilton's My New BFF" are living in a mansion that costs half as much as the home the show rented last season. Trips to New York and Tokyo are out this year as the show's production budget has been cut 10 percent. With the recession eating into advertising revenue at TV networks a popular solution has emerged — even cheaper reality TV.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Paris Hilton is an heiress.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Neutral</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="135" id="135" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 16</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">First runner-up Carrie Prejean (Miss California) was asked about legalizing same-sex marriage from judge Perez Hilton the Internet blogger behind perezhilton.com. "I believe that a marriage should be between a man and a woman. No offense to anybody there. But that's how I was raised and that's how I think it should be" Prejean said during Sunday night's live telecast. Hilton was visibly upset and there was a mixed reaction from the live audience. Prejean ultimately came up short losing the title to Miss North Carolina Kristen Dalton.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Carrie Prejean was a contestant in Miss USA.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Neutral</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="136" id="136" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 17</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Hours after the North's announcement the International Atomic Energy Agency (IAEA) said its inspectors had been ordered out. North Korea "informed IAEA inspectors in the Yongbyon facility that it is immediately ceasing all cooperation with the IAEA" Marc Vidricaire spokesman for the UN nuclear watchdog told reporters. "It has requested the removal of all containment and surveillance equipment following which IAEA inspectors will no longer be provided access to the facility. The inspectors have also been asked to leave the DPRK at the earliest possible time."</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">North Korea expelled international nuclear inspectors.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="137" id="137" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 18</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">The trial against Swedish file-sharing website The Pirate Bay is coming to an end with the four defendents saying they're "confident we are going to win". Co-founder Peter Sunde is on trial with three co-defendents charged with "assisting in making available copyright material." A higher charge of "assisting copyright infringement" was dropped on the second day of the trial. But even if they are found guilty it won't have any consequences for the operation of the site and its millions of users.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">The site thepiratebay.org is one of the most visited BitTorrent destinations in the world.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Neutral</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="138" id="138" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 19</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Panetta told agency employees in an e-mail Thursday that the secret prisons are no longer used and the CIA is making plans to permanently shutter them. But the CIA can still hold prisoners temporarily. Panetta says if more prisoners are taken they will be interrogated by agency employees and handed over quickly to their home country or a country with a legal claim. The Washington Post reported in November 2005 that the CIA has maintained secret prisons also known as "black sites" in at least eight foreign countries since shortly after the 9/11 attacks.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Panetta is the director of the CIA.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Neutral</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="139" id="139" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 20</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">NEW YORK (MYFOX NATIONAL) New York City's Tompkins Square Park was the site of immigrant unemployment protests and labor conflict in the late 1800s . Now it's going to be the host of the Unemployment Olympics . The brainchild of laid-off computer programmer Nick Goddard the event will take place on Tuesday afternoon and feature unemployed "athletes" participating in events such as the Fax Machine Toss the "You're Fired" race and Pin the Blame on the Bosses. The 40 participants must show proof of unemployment — an unemployment card a letter from the employer or an unemployment packet.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">The Unemployment Olympics will take place in New York City.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="140" id="140" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>

  <button type="submit" class="btn btn-info btn-raised btn-lg btn-block" id='submitButton'>Submit</button>
  
</form>
</section>
<script language='Javascript'>turkSetAssignmentID();</script>

     

</body>
</html>

<script src="https://code.jquery.com/jquery-3.3.1.slim.min.js" integrity="sha384-q8i/X+965DzO0rT7abK41JStQIAqVgRVzpbzo5smXKp4YfRvH+8abtTE1Pi6jizo" crossorigin="anonymous"></script>
<script src="https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/popper.js/1.14.6/umd/popper.min.js" integrity="sha384-wHAiFfRlMFy6i5SRaxvfOCifBUQy1xHdJ/yoi7FRNXMRBu5WHdZYu1hA6ZOblgut" crossorigin="anonymous"></script>
<script src="https://stackpath.bootstrapcdn.com/bootstrap/4.2.1/js/bootstrap.min.js" integrity="sha384-B0UglyR+jN6CkvvICOB2joaf5I4l3gm9GU6Hc1og6Ls7i6U/mkkaduKaBhlAXv9k" crossorigin="anonymous"></script>
]]>
</HTMLContent>
<FrameHeight>0</FrameHeight>
</HTMLQuestion>