<HTMLQuestion xmlns="http://mechanicalturk.amazonaws.com/AWSMechanicalTurkDataSchemas/2011-11-11/HTMLQuestion.xsd">
<HTMLContent><![CDATA[
<!DOCTYPE html>
<html>
<head>
<meta http-equiv='Content-Type' content='text/html; charset=UTF-8'/>
<script type='text/javascript' src='https://s3.amazonaws.com/mturk-public/externalHIT_v1.js'></script>
<script src="https://sdk.amazonaws.com/js/aws-sdk-2.142.0.min.js"></script>
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://stackpath.bootstrapcdn.com/bootstrap/4.2.1/css/bootstrap.min.css" integrity="sha384-GJzZqFGwb1QTTN6wy59ffF1BuGJpLSa9DkKMp0DgiMDm4iYMj70gZWKYbI706tWS" crossorigin="anonymous">
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://www.w3schools.com/w3css/4/w3.css">
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://unpkg.com/bootstrap-material-design@4.1.1/dist/css/bootstrap-material-design.min.css" integrity="sha384-wXznGJNEXNG1NFsbm0ugrLFMQPWswR3lds2VeinahP8N0zJw9VWSopbjv2x7WCvX" crossorigin="anonymous">
<style>
  dt{
    font-size: medium;
  }

  dd{
    margin-bottom: 1rem; 
    margin-left: 0;
  }
  
  .card-text{
    margin-bottom: 2rem;
  }

  h5{
    font-weight: bold;
  }
  .tablink{
    font-weight: 600;
  }

  .btn-lg{
    font-size: 2rem;
    line-height: 4rem;
  }
  h2{
    margin-top: 1rem;
  }
  p{
    font-size: 1rem;
  }
</style>
</head>

<body>
<section class="container mb-3 mt-3">
  <fieldset class="shadow bg-white mb-3">
<div class="w3-container">
  <h2 class="text-info" style="font-weight: bolder">Instructions and Examples</h2>
  <div id="Instructions" class="w3-container ins w3-animate-opacity" style="display:block">
    <h2>Instructions</h2>
    <p>Read the premise, hypothesis and realation, select a segment from premise that can determine the relation between premise and hypothesis.</p>
    <ul>
      <!-- We are adding a template variable below which we will replace with an actual link in our code later -->
      <li>Read the premise, hypothesis and the relation.</li>
      <li>On the basis of your own judgement, select a "sequential" segment from premise that can determine the relation between premise and hypothesis.</li>
      <li>The length is not restricted, as long as the segment provides sufficient informations.</li>
      <li>Copy the segment from premise and paste it into the following box.</li>
      <li><strong>SPAM and non-sequential segments will be rejected.</strong></li>
      </ul>
    <p>The following section is the definition of the three realations, which comes from the RTE-5 task guideline. If you are familiar with NLI tasks such as SNLI, MNLI, RTE, you can skip the section below.</p>
    <p>We define textual entailment as a directional relationship between a pair of text fragments, which we call the "Premise" and the "Hypothesis". We say that: </p>
    <p><strong><i>Premise entails Hypothesis, if a human reading premise would infer that hypothesis is most likely true. </i></strong></p>
    <p>For example, given assumed common background knowledge of the business news domain and the following premise: </p>
    <p style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><strong><i>Premise1 Internet media company Yahoo Inc. announced Monday it is buying Overture Services Inc. in a $1.63-billion (U.S.) cash-and-stock deal that will bolster its on-line search capabilities.</i></strong></p>
    <p>the following hypothesis is entailed:</p>
    <ul>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.1 Yahoo boutght Overture</i></p></li>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.2 Overture acquired by Yahoo</i></p></li>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.3 Overture was bought</i></p></li>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.4 Yahoo is an internet company</i></p></li>
    </ul>
    <p>For example, the following hypothesis are contradicted by Premise above:</p>
    <ul>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.5 Overture bought Yahoo</i></p></li>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.6 Yahoo sold Overture</i></p></li>
    </ul>
    <p>While the following ones cannot be judged on the basis of Premise above:</p>
    <ul>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.7 Yahoo manufatures cars</i></p></li>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.8 Overture shareholders will receive $4.75 cash and 0.6108 Yahoo stock for each of their shares.</i></p></li>
    </ul>
  </div>
  
</div>
</fieldset>
<fieldset class="shadow bg-white mb-3">
  <div id="Entailment" class="w3-container ins w3-animate-opacity">
    <h2>Entailment Example</h2>
    <p>Here is a pair of premise and hypothesis with entailment relation. The following is the Segment you need to respond, which we also emphasize in the premise.</p>
    <ul>
      <dt style="font-size: medium;">Premise</dt>
      <dd style='margin-bottom: 1rem; margin-left: 0;'>CNN) -- Malawians are rallying behind <strong class="w3-text-deep-orange">Madonna as she awaits a ruling Friday on whether she can adopt a girl from the southern African nation. The pop star, who has three children</strong>, adopted a son from Malawi in 2006. She is seeking to adopt Chifundo "Mercy" James, 4. "Ninety-nine percent of the people calling in are saying, 'let her take the baby,' " said Marilyn Segula, a presenter at Capital FM, which broadcasts in at least five cities, including the capital, Lilongwe.</t>
      <h>Madonna has three children.</dd>
      <dt>Hypothesis</dt>
      <dd>Madonna has three children.</dd>
      <dt>Relation</dt>
      <dd>Entailment</dd>
      <dt>Segment (Your response)</dt>
      <dd>Madonna as she awaits a ruling Friday on whether she can adopt a girl from the southern African nation. The pop star, who has three children</dd>
    </ul>
  </div>
</fieldset>
<fieldset class="shadow bg-white mb-3">
  <div id="Neutral" class="w3-container ins w3-animate-opacity">
    <h2>Neutral Example</h2>
    <p>Here is a pair of premise and hypothesis with neutral relation. The following is the Segment you need to respond, which we also emphasize in the premise.</p> 
    <ul>
      <dt>Premise</dt>
      <dd>Concerns have been raised that potential leads in the hunt for missing York woman <strong class="w3-text-deep-orange">Claudia Lawrence are not being followed up quickly enough. It comes after hotel staff in Malton contacted police</strong> after a stranger in the bar expressed satisfaction when asked if the chef was still missing. The incident happened more than three weeks ago and staff said detectives had not yet been in touch. Police said leads were being assessed in a methodical and structured way.</dd>
      <dt>Hypothesis</dt>
      <dd>Claudia Lawrence resides in Malton.</dd>
      <dt>Relation</dt>
      <dd>Neutral</dd>
      <dt>Segment (Your response)</dt>
      <dd>Claudia Lawrence are not being followed up quickly enough. It comes after hotel staff in Malton contacted police</dd>
    </ul>
  </div>
</fieldset>
<fieldset class="shadow bg-white mb-3">
  <div id="Contradiction" class="w3-container ins w3-animate-opacity">
    <h2>Contradiction Example</h2>
    <p>Here is a pair of premise and hypothesis with Contradiction relation. The following is the Segment you need to respond, which we also emphasize in the premise.</p> 
    <ul>
      <dt>Premise</dt>
      <dd>But an O2 insider said there had been problems with a companies trying to sell the pass codes. Some people were "bound to have been turned away" because of fraudulent tickets. <strong class="w3-text-deep-orange">Led Zeppelin, formed in 1968</strong>, were one of the most influential bands of the 1970s with songs such as Whole Lotta Love and Stairway To Heaven. They split in 1980 after the death of the drummer John Bonham. Kenneth Donnell, 25, who was not born in 1980, spent 83,000 on two tickets in a BBC Children in Need auction.</dd>
      <dt>Hypothesis</dt>
      <dd>The band Led Zeppelin was formed in 1980.</dd>
      <dt>Relation</dt>
      <dd>Contradiction</dd>
      <dt>Segment (Your response)</dt>
      <dd>Led Zeppelin, formed in 1968</dd>
    </ul>
  </div>
</fieldset>
</section>

<!-- Questions Section -->
<section class="container">
  <div class="alert alert-danger text-center shadow" role="alert" style="font-weight: bold; font-size: large">
  All answers will be manually checked, SPAM and blank answers will be definitely rejected.
  </div>  
  <form name='mturk_form' method='post' id='mturk_form' action='https://www.mturk.com/mturk/externalSubmit'><input type='hidden' value='' name='assignmentId' id='assignmentId'/>
    <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 1</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">I was nearly charged with petty theft for pilfering coffee at the illustrious Hippodrome Building. But lest I be judged too quickly I must convey the sublimity of the fourth floor's coffee machine. Harry Houdini performed at the Hippodrome at 1120 Avenue of the Americas near 44th Street. Many of the best and most famous performers of the time appeared there. It was one of the biggest and most successful theaters of its time capable of accommodating 5200 people.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Harry Houdini was a magician.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Neutral</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="21" id="21" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 2</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">The Grapes of Wrath published exactly 70 years ago can be seen as a prophetic novel rooted in the tragedies of the Great Depression but speaking directly to the harsh realities of 2009 writes Steinbeck scholar Robert DeMott. Steinbeck's epic novel which traces harrowing exodus of Tom Joad and his family from blighted Oklahoma (where they are evicted from their farm) across the rugged American south-west via Highway 66 and on to what they mistakenly hope will be a more promising future in California is considered by many readers to be the quintessential Depression-era story and an ironic reversal of the rags-to-riches tale favoured by many optimistic Americans.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">"The Grapes of Wrath" was written by Steinbeck.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="22" id="22" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 3</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">When a mosquito drinks the blood an infected person the insect also swallows the malaria parasite which then must incubate and multiply before migrating into the insect's saliva. The process can take weeks. And because mosquitoes are small-bodied and cold-blooded outside temperatures make a big difference in how long it takes before they can transmit the disease. If it happens too slowly the insects die before they can infect anyone. In general the malaria parasite does better at warmer temperatures which is why the disease occurs most often in tropical environments. But with mathematical models Thomas has found that even when conditions are warm highly fluctuating temperatures over the course of a day slow down the rate of parasite incubation and larval development in the mosquito.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Warm weather facilitates the spreading of malaria.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="23" id="23" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 4</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">At home in New Hampshire V. Gene Robinson is by his own description "just the bishop." As the head of an Episcopal diocese of 16000 he spends his days counseling priests and their families visiting parishes performing baptisms attending confirmations and coordinating such projects as overseas missions and a campaign against the death penalty. What he does is important he says but not "anything particularly special." But when he leaves the diocese Robinson becomes what he calls "this bigger-than-life thing." His mere appearance inspires misty eyes and standing ovations from some. To others he is a pariah whose very identity makes him too tainted to share a pew or theological discussion. One person looks at him and sees the future of the church; another its demise.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Nearly six years ago Robinson became the first openly gay Episcopal bishop.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Neutral</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="24" id="24" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 5</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">At least 14 people have been killed in a suicide bomb attack in southern Sri Lanka police say. The telecoms minister was among about 35 people injured in the blast at the town of Akuressa 160km (100 miles) south of the capital Colombo. Government officials were attending a function at a mosque to celebrate an Islamic holiday at the time. The defence ministry said the blast was carried out by Tamil Tiger rebels but no-one has yet admitted responsibility. The Sri Lankan government has strongly condemned the attack. It urged people to remain calm and not to be provoked.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">49 people were hit by a suicide bomber in Akuressa.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="25" id="25" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 6</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">A U.S. judge ordered el Gharani released in January dismissing as unreliable the military's allegations that he was part of al-Qaida and had worked for the Taliban in Afghanistan. He is held in a section of Guantanamo where prisoners are permitted more privileges while he awaits release. El Gharani was arrested in Pakistan in 2001 at a mosque by local police and turned over to U.S. forces in 2002. He was one of the first Guantanamo Bay detainees and one of the youngest. The U.S. holds about 240 men at the U.S. base in Cuba most on suspicion of terrorism or links to al-Qaida and the Taliban.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">About 240 people are detained in Guantanamo.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="26" id="26" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 7</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">The word most often associated with West Papua is remote. An area of thick jungle and mountains roughly the size of Spain Papua is the eastern-most outpost of the Indonesian archipelago some 3200km (2000 miles) from the government in Jakarta. Culturally it feels even further. Papua became part of Indonesia in 1969 after a controversial and very limited vote. Ever since there have been calls from some Papuans for independence and for decades a low-level armed resistance has been rumbling on largely unnoticed by the outside.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">In 1969 Papua became part of Indonesia.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="27" id="27" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 8</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">The BBC has seen documents alleging that a former rebel leader indicted for war crimes is playing a leading role in a mission involving the UN in DR Congo. The documents appear to prove that Gen Bosco Ntaganda is taking an active part in the mission's chain of command a BBC correspondent in the country says. The UN-Congolese force is fighting Hutu rebels in the eastern DR Congo. The force says Congolese authorities have given assurances that Gen Ntaganda was not involved in joint operations.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Bosco Ntaganda was a rebel leader.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="28" id="28" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 9</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Bout who is generally believed to be a model for the arms dealer portrayed by Nicolas Cage in the 2005 movie 'Lord of War' has repeatedly denied any involvement in illicit activities. At a hearing earlier this month he angrily accused the United States of framing him and pressuring Thailand to extradite him. He has long been linked to some of the world's most notorious conflicts allegedly supplying arms to former Liberian dictator Charles Taylor and Libyan leader Colonel Gaddafi.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Gaddafi is the Liberian dictator.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Contradiction</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="29" id="29" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 10</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">A man has hijacked a passenger plane in the Jamaican resort of Montego Bay and is still holding five crew members hostage reports say. More than 150 passengers were on board when the man forced his way on board the Canada-bound charter plane but all have now been released. The man breached security and boarded as the plane was about to take off at around 2230 local time (0330 GMT). Negotiations for the release of the hostages are said to be taking place.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">A plane crashed in the Jamaican resort of Montego Bay.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Contradiction</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="30" id="30" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 11</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">When it comes to the recession tactful New Yorkers may refrain from complaining too loudly about their misfortunes knowing that the chances are there is someone else out there who has it worse. But try explaining to a 6-year-old no matter how worldly and well mannered that budget cuts may prevent him from spending quality time with a penguin. The Wildlife Conservation Society which manages the city's zoos and the New York Aquarium in Coney Island is among the many organizations in the city facing steep budget cuts.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">The New York Aquarium is located in Coney Island.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="31" id="31" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 12</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">The Czech Republic has allowed at least 94 prisoners over the past decade to be surgically castrated. It is the only country in Europe that uses the procedure for sex offenders. Czech psychiatrists supervising the treatment a one-hour operation that involves removal of the tissue that produces testosterone insist that it is the most foolproof way to tame sexual urges in dangerous predators suffering from extreme sexual disorders. Surgical castration has been a means of social control for centuries. In ancient China eunuchs were trusted to serve the imperial family inside the palace grounds; in Italy several centuries ago youthful male choir members were castrated to preserve their high singing voices.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">In China sex offenders have to be treated with surgical castration.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Neutral</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="32" id="32" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 13</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">North Adams A seven-minute film written and directed by a MCLA freshman will make its debut next week at the Boston International Film Festival which features a line-up of independent films starring the likes of Kate Beckinsale Matt Dillon Angela Bassett and Ethan Hawke. "Initially when I shot the film it was not my intention to enter it in any festivals so I'm very excited and honored" Cody Romano 18 of Cambridge said Friday. "The film was made because of my personal interest in the poetry of Pablo Neruda a Chilean poet and it was a tribute to his work. I wasn't sure anyone else would like it. My concern was that it would only appeal to literary people and people who were fans of the poetry but I'm happy that it apparently appeals to a broader audience as well."</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Pablo Neruda came from Chile.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="33" id="33" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 14</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Speaking after he discovered that he would not face criminal charges Mr Green disclosed that the officers who arrested him last November warned him that he could be given the longest possible sentence. "They said 'Do you realise that this offence could lead to life imprisonment?'" Mr Green told BBC Newsnight. I just thought this was absurd. "I assume it's because it's a common law offence therefore because there is no law on the statute book which I was alleged to have broken then presumably there is no set sentence for it."</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Mr. Green is the shadow immigration minister of the UK.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Neutral</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="34" id="34" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 15</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">In San Sebastián in the Basque country dozens of supporters celebrated De Juana's release. He has never expressed any remorse. In a letter written after one Eta killing he said of the victims: "Their tears are our smiles and in the end we will roar with laughter." He now faces a bill for €8m in compensation for his victims and an investigation into his assets. The release came 40 years to the day after Eta carried out its first deadly attack killing a civil guard officer. The organisation which is fighting for an independent Basque country in north-west Spain and south-west France has killed more than 800 people since 1968.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">ETA started their activities in the 60s.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="35" id="35" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 16</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">The U.S. State Department said Thursday that the United States is working to dissuade North Korea from going ahead with its plan to launch a satellite next month. U.S. officials say the launch is a disguised long-range missile test and would be destabilizing. State Department officials give no credence to the notion that the launch would be for scientific purposes and they say the United States is working diplomatically to try to prevent a North Korean action that they say would be provocative destabilizing and unhelpful.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">The U.S. fears that the North Korean satellite is a ruse to hide the testing of a missile.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="36" id="36" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 17</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Governments around the world have been hurrying to contain the spread of a new swine flu virus after outbreaks were reported in Mexico the US and Canada. At least 100 people are now suspected to have died of the disease in Mexico. The UN has warned the virus has the potential to become a pandemic but said the world was better prepared than ever to deal with the threat. Stocks of anti-viral medicines are being readied and travellers are being screened at some airports for symptoms.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">At least 100 people are thought to have died of swine flu in Mexico.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="37" id="37" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 18</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">The hurricane caused severe destruction across the entire Mississippi coast and into Alabama as far as 100 miles (160 km) from the storm's center. Katrina was the eleventh tropical storm fifth hurricane third major hurricane and second Category 5 hurricane of the 2005 Atlantic season. It formed over the Bahamas on August 23 2005 and crossed southern Florida as a moderate Category 1 hurricane causing some deaths and flooding there before strengthening rapidly in the Gulf of Mexico and becoming one of the strongest hurricanes on record while at sea.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Hurricane Katrina formed in August 2005 in the Gulf of Mexico.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Contradiction</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="38" id="38" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 19</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">"International adoption can actually exacerbate the problem it hopes to solve" said Dominic Nutt Save the Children's UK spokesman. "The very existence of orphanages encourages poor parents to abandon children in the hope that they will have a better life." While no one accuses Madonna of doing anything illegal in adopting the 4-year-old girl reportedly named Mercy there are questions nonetheless about how Madonna is able to navigate Malawi's 18-to-24 month vetting period in just a matter of days or weeks. But the larger issue child-rights advocates say is whether international adoptions are in the best interests of the child.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Madonna is 50 years old.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Neutral</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="39" id="39" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 20</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">North Korea's rubber-stamp parliament has re-elected Kim Jong-il as chairman of the National Defence Commission the country's most powerful position. Mr Kim's re-election comes days after a rocket launch that was lauded at home but criticised at the UN. Analysts say the move will help cement Mr Kim's position after rumours he lost some of his grip on power after suffering a stroke in August. Observers have expressed concern about the apparent lack of a succession plan.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Kim Jong-il is the chairman of the UN.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Contradiction</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="40" id="40" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>

  <button type="submit" class="btn btn-info btn-raised btn-lg btn-block" id='submitButton'>Submit</button>
  
</form>
</section>
<script language='Javascript'>turkSetAssignmentID();</script>

     

</body>
</html>

<script src="https://code.jquery.com/jquery-3.3.1.slim.min.js" integrity="sha384-q8i/X+965DzO0rT7abK41JStQIAqVgRVzpbzo5smXKp4YfRvH+8abtTE1Pi6jizo" crossorigin="anonymous"></script>
<script src="https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/popper.js/1.14.6/umd/popper.min.js" integrity="sha384-wHAiFfRlMFy6i5SRaxvfOCifBUQy1xHdJ/yoi7FRNXMRBu5WHdZYu1hA6ZOblgut" crossorigin="anonymous"></script>
<script src="https://stackpath.bootstrapcdn.com/bootstrap/4.2.1/js/bootstrap.min.js" integrity="sha384-B0UglyR+jN6CkvvICOB2joaf5I4l3gm9GU6Hc1og6Ls7i6U/mkkaduKaBhlAXv9k" crossorigin="anonymous"></script>
]]>
</HTMLContent>
<FrameHeight>0</FrameHeight>
</HTMLQuestion>