<HTMLQuestion xmlns="http://mechanicalturk.amazonaws.com/AWSMechanicalTurkDataSchemas/2011-11-11/HTMLQuestion.xsd">
<HTMLContent><![CDATA[
<!DOCTYPE html>
<html>
<head>
<meta http-equiv='Content-Type' content='text/html; charset=UTF-8'/>
<script type='text/javascript' src='https://s3.amazonaws.com/mturk-public/externalHIT_v1.js'></script>
<script src="https://sdk.amazonaws.com/js/aws-sdk-2.142.0.min.js"></script>
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://stackpath.bootstrapcdn.com/bootstrap/4.2.1/css/bootstrap.min.css" integrity="sha384-GJzZqFGwb1QTTN6wy59ffF1BuGJpLSa9DkKMp0DgiMDm4iYMj70gZWKYbI706tWS" crossorigin="anonymous">
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://www.w3schools.com/w3css/4/w3.css">
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://unpkg.com/bootstrap-material-design@4.1.1/dist/css/bootstrap-material-design.min.css" integrity="sha384-wXznGJNEXNG1NFsbm0ugrLFMQPWswR3lds2VeinahP8N0zJw9VWSopbjv2x7WCvX" crossorigin="anonymous">
<style>
  dt{
    font-size: medium;
  }

  dd{
    margin-bottom: 1rem; 
    margin-left: 0;
  }
  
  .card-text{
    margin-bottom: 2rem;
  }

  h5{
    font-weight: bold;
  }
  .tablink{
    font-weight: 600;
  }

  .btn-lg{
    font-size: 2rem;
    line-height: 4rem;
  }
  h2{
    margin-top: 1rem;
  }
  p{
    font-size: 1rem;
  }
</style>
</head>

<body>
<section class="container mb-3 mt-3">
  <fieldset class="shadow bg-white mb-3">
<div class="w3-container">
  <h2 class="text-info" style="font-weight: bolder">Instructions and Examples</h2>
  <div id="Instructions" class="w3-container ins w3-animate-opacity" style="display:block">
    <h2>Instructions</h2>
    <p>Read the premise, hypothesis and realation, select a segment from premise that can determine the relation between premise and hypothesis.</p>
    <ul>
      <!-- We are adding a template variable below which we will replace with an actual link in our code later -->
      <li>Read the premise, hypothesis and the relation.</li>
      <li>On the basis of your own judgement, select a "sequential" segment from premise that can determine the relation between premise and hypothesis.</li>
      <li>The length is not restricted, as long as the segment provides sufficient informations.</li>
      <li>Copy the segment from premise and paste it into the following box.</li>
      <li><strong>SPAM and non-sequential segments will be rejected.</strong></li>
      </ul>
    <p>The following section is the definition of the three realations, which comes from the RTE-5 task guideline. If you are familiar with NLI tasks such as SNLI, MNLI, RTE, you can skip the section below.</p>
    <p>We define textual entailment as a directional relationship between a pair of text fragments, which we call the "Premise" and the "Hypothesis". We say that: </p>
    <p><strong><i>Premise entails Hypothesis, if a human reading premise would infer that hypothesis is most likely true. </i></strong></p>
    <p>For example, given assumed common background knowledge of the business news domain and the following premise: </p>
    <p style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><strong><i>Premise1 Internet media company Yahoo Inc. announced Monday it is buying Overture Services Inc. in a $1.63-billion (U.S.) cash-and-stock deal that will bolster its on-line search capabilities.</i></strong></p>
    <p>the following hypothesis is entailed:</p>
    <ul>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.1 Yahoo boutght Overture</i></p></li>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.2 Overture acquired by Yahoo</i></p></li>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.3 Overture was bought</i></p></li>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.4 Yahoo is an internet company</i></p></li>
    </ul>
    <p>For example, the following hypothesis are contradicted by Premise above:</p>
    <ul>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.5 Overture bought Yahoo</i></p></li>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.6 Yahoo sold Overture</i></p></li>
    </ul>
    <p>While the following ones cannot be judged on the basis of Premise above:</p>
    <ul>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.7 Yahoo manufatures cars</i></p></li>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.8 Overture shareholders will receive $4.75 cash and 0.6108 Yahoo stock for each of their shares.</i></p></li>
    </ul>
  </div>
  
</div>
</fieldset>
<fieldset class="shadow bg-white mb-3">
  <div id="Entailment" class="w3-container ins w3-animate-opacity">
    <h2>Entailment Example</h2>
    <p>Here is a pair of premise and hypothesis with entailment relation. The following is the Segment you need to respond, which we also emphasize in the premise.</p>
    <ul>
      <dt style="font-size: medium;">Premise</dt>
      <dd style='margin-bottom: 1rem; margin-left: 0;'>CNN) -- Malawians are rallying behind <strong class="w3-text-deep-orange">Madonna as she awaits a ruling Friday on whether she can adopt a girl from the southern African nation. The pop star, who has three children</strong>, adopted a son from Malawi in 2006. She is seeking to adopt Chifundo "Mercy" James, 4. "Ninety-nine percent of the people calling in are saying, 'let her take the baby,' " said Marilyn Segula, a presenter at Capital FM, which broadcasts in at least five cities, including the capital, Lilongwe.</t>
      <h>Madonna has three children.</dd>
      <dt>Hypothesis</dt>
      <dd>Madonna has three children.</dd>
      <dt>Relation</dt>
      <dd>Entailment</dd>
      <dt>Segment (Your response)</dt>
      <dd>Madonna as she awaits a ruling Friday on whether she can adopt a girl from the southern African nation. The pop star, who has three children</dd>
    </ul>
  </div>
</fieldset>
<fieldset class="shadow bg-white mb-3">
  <div id="Neutral" class="w3-container ins w3-animate-opacity">
    <h2>Neutral Example</h2>
    <p>Here is a pair of premise and hypothesis with neutral relation. The following is the Segment you need to respond, which we also emphasize in the premise.</p> 
    <ul>
      <dt>Premise</dt>
      <dd>Concerns have been raised that potential leads in the hunt for missing York woman <strong class="w3-text-deep-orange">Claudia Lawrence are not being followed up quickly enough. It comes after hotel staff in Malton contacted police</strong> after a stranger in the bar expressed satisfaction when asked if the chef was still missing. The incident happened more than three weeks ago and staff said detectives had not yet been in touch. Police said leads were being assessed in a methodical and structured way.</dd>
      <dt>Hypothesis</dt>
      <dd>Claudia Lawrence resides in Malton.</dd>
      <dt>Relation</dt>
      <dd>Neutral</dd>
      <dt>Segment (Your response)</dt>
      <dd>Claudia Lawrence are not being followed up quickly enough. It comes after hotel staff in Malton contacted police</dd>
    </ul>
  </div>
</fieldset>
<fieldset class="shadow bg-white mb-3">
  <div id="Contradiction" class="w3-container ins w3-animate-opacity">
    <h2>Contradiction Example</h2>
    <p>Here is a pair of premise and hypothesis with Contradiction relation. The following is the Segment you need to respond, which we also emphasize in the premise.</p> 
    <ul>
      <dt>Premise</dt>
      <dd>But an O2 insider said there had been problems with a companies trying to sell the pass codes. Some people were "bound to have been turned away" because of fraudulent tickets. <strong class="w3-text-deep-orange">Led Zeppelin, formed in 1968</strong>, were one of the most influential bands of the 1970s with songs such as Whole Lotta Love and Stairway To Heaven. They split in 1980 after the death of the drummer John Bonham. Kenneth Donnell, 25, who was not born in 1980, spent 83,000 on two tickets in a BBC Children in Need auction.</dd>
      <dt>Hypothesis</dt>
      <dd>The band Led Zeppelin was formed in 1980.</dd>
      <dt>Relation</dt>
      <dd>Contradiction</dd>
      <dt>Segment (Your response)</dt>
      <dd>Led Zeppelin, formed in 1968</dd>
    </ul>
  </div>
</fieldset>
</section>

<!-- Questions Section -->
<section class="container">
  <div class="alert alert-danger text-center shadow" role="alert" style="font-weight: bold; font-size: large">
  All answers will be manually checked, SPAM and blank answers will be definitely rejected.
  </div>  
  <form name='mturk_form' method='post' id='mturk_form' action='https://www.mturk.com/mturk/externalSubmit'><input type='hidden' value='' name='assignmentId' id='assignmentId'/>
    <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 1</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">McDonald's has announced slightly higher profits in the first three months of the year as people look for value meals during the recession. Profits at the the US fast-food giant the world's largest hamburger chain rose 4% to $979.5m (£676m) from $946.1m in the same period last year. The company also said that sales so far in April were strong. Last month McDonald's warned that the strong dollar and high commodity prices would squeeze first quarter revenues.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">McDonald's is the world's largest hamburger chain.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="101" id="101" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 2</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Wearing a black suit with a red tie and pocket square Phil Spector showed no reaction as the verdict was announced. Now 69 he faces a sentence of 18 years to life in prison when he is sentenced May 29. Asked if he agreed to the sentencing date Spector quietly answered "Yes." Prosecutor Alan Jackson said he believed the jury reached the correct verdict and he acknowledged the strength and backing of Clarkson's family. But defense attorney Doron Weinberg said Spector's defense team disagreed and planned to appeal.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Phil Spector is related to the Clarkson family.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Neutral</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="102" id="102" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 3</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Napoli will not sign Fabio Cannavaro in the summer once the veteran defender becomes a free agent. The Italy captain whose contract with Real Madrid expires at the end of the season is looking for a club and has been linked with a move to Manchester City. However 35-year-old Cannavaro will not be granted the opportunity to end his career with his home club Napoli. "Cannavaro will not come to Napoli" said Napoli club president Aurelio De Laurentiis.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Cannavaro is 35 years old.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="103" id="103" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 4</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Leftist Mauricio Funes of El Salvador's former Marxist rebel FMLN party has won the country's presidential election. He defeated his conservative rival the Arena party's Rodrigo Avila who has admitted defeat. Arena had won every presidential election since the end of El Salvador's civil war 18 years ago. Addressing jubilant supporters Mr Funes said it was the happiest day of his life and the beginning of a new chapter of peace for the country. Branded by his opponents as a puppet of Venezuala's President Hugo Chavez Mr Funes vowed to respect all Salvadorian democratic institutions.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">In El Salvador Mauricio Funes has defeated Rodrigo Avila.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="104" id="104" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 5</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">The company also faced shortages of skilled riveters the archives showed. Dr. McCarty said that for a half year from late 1911 to April 1912 when the Titanic set sail the company's board discussed the problem at every meeting. For instance on Oct. 28 1911 Lord William Pirrie the company's chairman expressed concern over the lack of riveters and called for new hiring efforts. In their research the scientists who are metallurgists found that good riveting took great skill. The iron had to be heated to a precise cherry red color and beaten by the right combination of hammer blows. Mediocre work could hide problems.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Titanic sank in 1912.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Neutral</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="105" id="105" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 6</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">A SCUBA diver has died during a visit to a historic ship sunk off the Port Phillip Bay heads. The Geelong man 49 was with a group of six on a diving expedition to explore the SS Coogee shipwreck when he collapsed. The experienced diver who had explored the scuttled steamer 25 times before was teamed with two other divers when disaster struck. About 11am yesterday within minutes of entering the 13C water he floated to the surface. Police say that on reaching the shipwreck the two other divers did not immediately notice he was missing because of the poor visibility at that depth.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">The scuba diver who died in Port Phillip Bay came from Geelong.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="106" id="106" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 7</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">The fishermen are protesting catch quotas they call too low for them to earn a living. They say they plan to continue blocking the northern French ports indefinitely. The European Union sets annual quotas in an effort to protect and revive dwindling fish stocks. Member countries negotiate each country's share of the total catch. "The immediate opening of supplementary catch quotas for sole and cod is vital for the future of small fishermen" in the region Jacky Henin former mayor of Calais and a European parliament member said Wednesday. The French government said it may consider providing financial support to the fishing industry but called the quotas reasonable.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">French fishermen protest against EU fishing quotas.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="107" id="107" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 8</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Alistair Darling will not raise the amount of cash he wants from the new 50p income tax rate because high earners will find ways to avoid paying it experts say. The Chancellor revealed in his Budget that borrowing this year would soar to a record £175bn as the government tries to "grow" its way out of recession. Mr Darling confirmed that the UK was in the grip of the deepest slump since the Second World War with the economy set to shrink by 3.5% in 2009 more than double his previous forecast.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Alistair Darling is chancellor.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="108" id="108" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 9</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">LOS ANGELES (Reuters) — Starbucks Corp Wednesday posted slightly better-than-expected quarterly profit as cost savings helped offset an 8% drop in same-store sales. The coffee chain which has been slashing costs to compensate for dwindling customer visits had announced plans to close almost 1000 stores around the world as the worst recession in decades drove consumers to tighten their belts. During the second quarter Starbucks (SBUX Fortune 500) said it cut costs by $120 million better than its target of $100 million and that sales at restaurants open at least 13 months declined at a slower pace than the 9% drop recorded in the first quarter.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Starbucks is a US coffee giant.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Neutral</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="109" id="109" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 10</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">The pilot of an Indonesian plane that crashed at an airport on Java island killing 21 people has been jailed for two years for criminal negligence. An inquiry found that Capt Marwoto Komar had approached the runway too fast and landed at too steep an angle. The Boeing 737 skidded off the runway and burst into flames on 7 March 2007. This is the first time a pilot has faced criminal charges in Indonesia and the trial has attracted a lot of media attention.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Capt Marwoto Komar has been jailed for 21 years.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Contradiction</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="110" id="110" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 11</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">This winter's ski season in Europe and the US has been stunning — the snow arrived early fell in heaps and is still falling in many places. Only last weekend an extraordinary 4ft snowfall across Colorado and Wyoming left hundreds of drivers stranded on freeways and brought down power lines. But the future of skiing in many resorts hangs in the balance. The world's highest ski run has closed after running out of snow over several years — the Chacaltaya ski area in Bolivia stood at 5300m (17388ft) on a glacier. Skiing was established at Chacaltaya 70 years ago with Lake Titicaca on the horizon and about 14 years ago could boast a ski run 12m (40ft) deep in snow. Bolivia even had its own Winter Olympics team until 1992.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Lake Titicaca is a lake located on the border between Bolivia and Peru.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Neutral</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="111" id="111" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 12</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">The same mindset that led to these over-the-top punishments was apparently at play in the strip search of a 13-year-old student by Safford Ariz. school officials in 2003. They were trying to find out whether she had prescription-strength ibuprofen tablets — the equivalent of a couple of Advils hidden in her bra or panties in violation of the "no drugs" policy. No pills were found. Savana Redding then an eighth-grader and now 19 was so humiliated she never went back to the school. Her mother sued the school district and the administrator involved. On Tuesday the case reaches the U.S. Supreme Court where the justices will determine whether school officials violated Redding's constitutional right to be free from unreasonable searches and whether she can hold them personally financially responsible.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Savana Redding was strip-searched at school six years ago.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="112" id="112" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 13</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Norway's premier Jens Stoltenberg issued a curt "We lost a referendum on the EU and so it is not on the agenda now." Oslo has held two referendums on the matter one in 1974 after negotiating an accession agreement and another in 1994. Both times membership was narrowly rejected. Icelandic Prime Minister Johanna Sigurdardottir said that as part of the coalition agreement her centre-left Social Democratic Alliance had signed with the far-left Left Green Movement the current caretaker government would not apply for membership of the EU. "But let's see what happens after the elections" she said. "At the same time we need 30000 Icelanders to demand a referendum."</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Johanna Sigurdardottir belongs to the Icelandic Social Democratic Alliance.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="113" id="113" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 14</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Starbucks was one of the first companies to recognize the United States was in a recession when it halted its expansion plans last July. Still sensitive to the spending habits of consumers the company has not glimpsed an end to that recession. Howard D. Schultz Starbucks' chief executive told investors Wednesday after announcing that the company's second-quarter net income had dropped 77 percent that "The global economy continues to be weak." He also said "We did not see any improvement in U.S. consumer spending in Q2" and added that he was not expecting any improvement in 2009.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Starbucks is an investment company.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Neutral</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="114" id="114" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 15</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Giampaolo Giuliani told locals to evacuate their houses and posted a video on YouTube in which he said a build-up of radon gas around the seismically active area of Abruzzo suggested a major earthquake was imminent. Several tremors had been felt in the medieval city of L'Aquila 60 miles north-east of Rome since mid-January and vans with loudspeakers had reportedly driven around the city spreading the warning. But instead of heeding the advice of Mr Giuliani local authorities reported him to police for "spreading alarm" and he was told to remove his findings from the internet.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Giampaolo Giuliani works at the Gran Sasso National Laboratory.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Neutral</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="115" id="115" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 16</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">The Unemployment Olympics are the hastily planned brainchild of Nick Goddard a gangly angular man in small glasses and a navy blazer who runs from one event to the other herding the 30-some-odd contestants around like an inexperienced babysitter at a children's birthday party. The former computer programmer has been without a job for less than two months and says the idea for the four-event competition — Telephone toss Payday piñata Pin-the-Blame-on-the-Boss and the "You're Fired!" race — just popped into his head one night. "Normally you think of things like this but never do them" he says "but I have so much free time right now I decided to go for it." He built a rudimentary website contacted local news outlets and then watched in amazement as his email's inbox filled with hopeful participants.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Pin-the-Blame-on-the-Boss is one of the events of the Unemployment Olympics.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="116" id="116" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 17</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Overall the Southeast has the highest cancer death rate as researchers persist in looking for reasons said Jennifer Pietenpol director of the Vanderbilt-Ingram Cancer Center. She said technology education and outreach will curb deaths but funding and staff are also part of the equation. Pietenpol said the National Cancer Institute stands to receive $1.3 billion in stimulus package funds. "We have to look beyond a stimulus package" she said. "Cancer is not waiting for a stimulus package. There is clearly not enough money for every research."</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">The National Cancer Institute is the federal government's main cancer research entity.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Neutral</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="117" id="117" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 18</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">PARIS — Julius Meinl V the scion of a Viennese business dynasty whose name has been synonymous since the days of the Hapsburgs with luxuries like exotic coffee handmade tortes and discreet private banking has been jailed on suspicion of fraud at a company linked to the family. Prosecutors accused Mr. Meinl of artificially bolstering shares of the real estate company Meinl European Land on the Vienna stock exchange even as its investments in real estate across Eastern and Central Europe cratered.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Mr. Meinl owns a Falcon jet that he flies himself.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Neutral</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="118" id="118" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 19</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">At least 14 people have been killed in a suicide bomb attack in southern Sri Lanka police say. The telecoms minister was among about 35 people injured in the blast at the town of Akuressa 160km (100 miles) south of the capital Colombo. Government officials were attending a function at a mosque to celebrate an Islamic holiday at the time. The defence ministry said the blast was carried out by Tamil Tiger rebels but no-one has yet admitted responsibility. The Sri Lankan government has strongly condemned the attack. It urged people to remain calm and not to be provoked.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">35 government officials were injured by a suicide bomber in Akuressa.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Neutral</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="119" id="119" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 20</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">For weeks now I've been hearing chatter that Disney was close to doing a distribution deal with Hulu. Disney would give Hulu exclusive access to at least some of its online video in exchange for an equity stake alongside GE's (GE) NBC and News Corp.'s (NWS) Fox. And accompanying said chatter was this refrain: Why? The puzzlement comes from video players who don't work at NBC Fox or Hulu and who can't see the upside in Disney CEO Bob Iger throwing in his lot with Hulu.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Bob Iger is the CEO of Disney.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="120" id="120" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>

  <button type="submit" class="btn btn-info btn-raised btn-lg btn-block" id='submitButton'>Submit</button>
  
</form>
</section>
<script language='Javascript'>turkSetAssignmentID();</script>

     

</body>
</html>

<script src="https://code.jquery.com/jquery-3.3.1.slim.min.js" integrity="sha384-q8i/X+965DzO0rT7abK41JStQIAqVgRVzpbzo5smXKp4YfRvH+8abtTE1Pi6jizo" crossorigin="anonymous"></script>
<script src="https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/popper.js/1.14.6/umd/popper.min.js" integrity="sha384-wHAiFfRlMFy6i5SRaxvfOCifBUQy1xHdJ/yoi7FRNXMRBu5WHdZYu1hA6ZOblgut" crossorigin="anonymous"></script>
<script src="https://stackpath.bootstrapcdn.com/bootstrap/4.2.1/js/bootstrap.min.js" integrity="sha384-B0UglyR+jN6CkvvICOB2joaf5I4l3gm9GU6Hc1og6Ls7i6U/mkkaduKaBhlAXv9k" crossorigin="anonymous"></script>
]]>
</HTMLContent>
<FrameHeight>0</FrameHeight>
</HTMLQuestion>