<HTMLQuestion xmlns="http://mechanicalturk.amazonaws.com/AWSMechanicalTurkDataSchemas/2011-11-11/HTMLQuestion.xsd">
<HTMLContent><![CDATA[
<!DOCTYPE html>
<html>
<head>
<meta http-equiv='Content-Type' content='text/html; charset=UTF-8'/>
<script type='text/javascript' src='https://s3.amazonaws.com/mturk-public/externalHIT_v1.js'></script>
<script src="https://sdk.amazonaws.com/js/aws-sdk-2.142.0.min.js"></script>
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://stackpath.bootstrapcdn.com/bootstrap/4.2.1/css/bootstrap.min.css" integrity="sha384-GJzZqFGwb1QTTN6wy59ffF1BuGJpLSa9DkKMp0DgiMDm4iYMj70gZWKYbI706tWS" crossorigin="anonymous">
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://www.w3schools.com/w3css/4/w3.css">
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://unpkg.com/bootstrap-material-design@4.1.1/dist/css/bootstrap-material-design.min.css" integrity="sha384-wXznGJNEXNG1NFsbm0ugrLFMQPWswR3lds2VeinahP8N0zJw9VWSopbjv2x7WCvX" crossorigin="anonymous">
<style>
  dt{
    font-size: medium;
  }

  dd{
    margin-bottom: 1rem; 
    margin-left: 0;
  }
  
  .card-text{
    margin-bottom: 2rem;
  }

  h5{
    font-weight: bold;
  }
  .tablink{
    font-weight: 600;
  }

  .btn-lg{
    font-size: 2rem;
    line-height: 4rem;
  }
  h2{
    margin-top: 1rem;
  }
  p{
    font-size: 1rem;
  }
</style>
</head>

<body>
<section class="container mb-3 mt-3">
  <fieldset class="shadow bg-white mb-3">
<div class="w3-container">
  <h2 class="text-info" style="font-weight: bolder">Instructions and Examples</h2>
  <div id="Instructions" class="w3-container ins w3-animate-opacity" style="display:block">
    <h2>Instructions</h2>
    <p>Read the premise, hypothesis and realation, select a segment from premise that can determine the relation between premise and hypothesis.</p>
    <ul>
      <!-- We are adding a template variable below which we will replace with an actual link in our code later -->
      <li>Read the premise, hypothesis and the relation.</li>
      <li>On the basis of your own judgement, select a "sequential" segment from premise that can determine the relation between premise and hypothesis.</li>
      <li>The length is not restricted, as long as the segment provides sufficient informations.</li>
      <li>Copy the segment from premise and paste it into the following box.</li>
      <li><strong>SPAM and non-sequential segments will be rejected.</strong></li>
      </ul>
    <p>The following section is the definition of the three realations, which comes from the RTE-5 task guideline. If you are familiar with NLI tasks such as SNLI, MNLI, RTE, you can skip the section below.</p>
    <p>We define textual entailment as a directional relationship between a pair of text fragments, which we call the "Premise" and the "Hypothesis". We say that: </p>
    <p><strong><i>Premise entails Hypothesis, if a human reading premise would infer that hypothesis is most likely true. </i></strong></p>
    <p>For example, given assumed common background knowledge of the business news domain and the following premise: </p>
    <p style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><strong><i>Premise1 Internet media company Yahoo Inc. announced Monday it is buying Overture Services Inc. in a $1.63-billion (U.S.) cash-and-stock deal that will bolster its on-line search capabilities.</i></strong></p>
    <p>the following hypothesis is entailed:</p>
    <ul>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.1 Yahoo boutght Overture</i></p></li>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.2 Overture acquired by Yahoo</i></p></li>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.3 Overture was bought</i></p></li>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.4 Yahoo is an internet company</i></p></li>
    </ul>
    <p>For example, the following hypothesis are contradicted by Premise above:</p>
    <ul>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.5 Overture bought Yahoo</i></p></li>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.6 Yahoo sold Overture</i></p></li>
    </ul>
    <p>While the following ones cannot be judged on the basis of Premise above:</p>
    <ul>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.7 Yahoo manufatures cars</i></p></li>
      <li style="font-family: Times New Roman; font-size: large"><p><i>H1.8 Overture shareholders will receive $4.75 cash and 0.6108 Yahoo stock for each of their shares.</i></p></li>
    </ul>
  </div>
  
</div>
</fieldset>
<fieldset class="shadow bg-white mb-3">
  <div id="Entailment" class="w3-container ins w3-animate-opacity">
    <h2>Entailment Example</h2>
    <p>Here is a pair of premise and hypothesis with entailment relation. The following is the Segment you need to respond, which we also emphasize in the premise.</p>
    <ul>
      <dt style="font-size: medium;">Premise</dt>
      <dd style='margin-bottom: 1rem; margin-left: 0;'>CNN) -- Malawians are rallying behind <strong class="w3-text-deep-orange">Madonna as she awaits a ruling Friday on whether she can adopt a girl from the southern African nation. The pop star, who has three children</strong>, adopted a son from Malawi in 2006. She is seeking to adopt Chifundo "Mercy" James, 4. "Ninety-nine percent of the people calling in are saying, 'let her take the baby,' " said Marilyn Segula, a presenter at Capital FM, which broadcasts in at least five cities, including the capital, Lilongwe.</t>
      <h>Madonna has three children.</dd>
      <dt>Hypothesis</dt>
      <dd>Madonna has three children.</dd>
      <dt>Relation</dt>
      <dd>Entailment</dd>
      <dt>Segment (Your response)</dt>
      <dd>Madonna as she awaits a ruling Friday on whether she can adopt a girl from the southern African nation. The pop star, who has three children</dd>
    </ul>
  </div>
</fieldset>
<fieldset class="shadow bg-white mb-3">
  <div id="Neutral" class="w3-container ins w3-animate-opacity">
    <h2>Neutral Example</h2>
    <p>Here is a pair of premise and hypothesis with neutral relation. The following is the Segment you need to respond, which we also emphasize in the premise.</p> 
    <ul>
      <dt>Premise</dt>
      <dd>Concerns have been raised that potential leads in the hunt for missing York woman <strong class="w3-text-deep-orange">Claudia Lawrence are not being followed up quickly enough. It comes after hotel staff in Malton contacted police</strong> after a stranger in the bar expressed satisfaction when asked if the chef was still missing. The incident happened more than three weeks ago and staff said detectives had not yet been in touch. Police said leads were being assessed in a methodical and structured way.</dd>
      <dt>Hypothesis</dt>
      <dd>Claudia Lawrence resides in Malton.</dd>
      <dt>Relation</dt>
      <dd>Neutral</dd>
      <dt>Segment (Your response)</dt>
      <dd>Claudia Lawrence are not being followed up quickly enough. It comes after hotel staff in Malton contacted police</dd>
    </ul>
  </div>
</fieldset>
<fieldset class="shadow bg-white mb-3">
  <div id="Contradiction" class="w3-container ins w3-animate-opacity">
    <h2>Contradiction Example</h2>
    <p>Here is a pair of premise and hypothesis with Contradiction relation. The following is the Segment you need to respond, which we also emphasize in the premise.</p> 
    <ul>
      <dt>Premise</dt>
      <dd>But an O2 insider said there had been problems with a companies trying to sell the pass codes. Some people were "bound to have been turned away" because of fraudulent tickets. <strong class="w3-text-deep-orange">Led Zeppelin, formed in 1968</strong>, were one of the most influential bands of the 1970s with songs such as Whole Lotta Love and Stairway To Heaven. They split in 1980 after the death of the drummer John Bonham. Kenneth Donnell, 25, who was not born in 1980, spent 83,000 on two tickets in a BBC Children in Need auction.</dd>
      <dt>Hypothesis</dt>
      <dd>The band Led Zeppelin was formed in 1980.</dd>
      <dt>Relation</dt>
      <dd>Contradiction</dd>
      <dt>Segment (Your response)</dt>
      <dd>Led Zeppelin, formed in 1968</dd>
    </ul>
  </div>
</fieldset>
</section>

<!-- Questions Section -->
<section class="container">
  <div class="alert alert-danger text-center shadow" role="alert" style="font-weight: bold; font-size: large">
  All answers will be manually checked, SPAM and blank answers will be definitely rejected.
  </div>  
  <form name='mturk_form' method='post' id='mturk_form' action='https://www.mturk.com/mturk/externalSubmit'><input type='hidden' value='' name='assignmentId' id='assignmentId'/>
    <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 1</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Former Ontario premier Bob Rae received a boost today in his bid to win the leadership of the federal Liberal Party of Canada when rival candidate Maurizio Bevilacqua announced he was dropping out of the race in order to back Rae. "I'm convinced that Bob Rae is the best person to lead the Liberal Party to victory. He has the experience and the intelligence and the vision to lead Canada into the 21st century" Mr. Belivacqua said at a news conference Monday. Bevilacqua is a six-term Liberal MP representing the riding of Vaughan Ontario and was seen as a centrist on economic issues.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Maurizio Bevilacqua is a supporter of Bob Rae.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="201" id="201" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 2</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">In an election on Saturday the Social Democratic Alliance and Left-Green Movement have won 34 of 63 seats in the Althing the Icelandic parliament. They share approximately 52% of the popular vote. In February 2009 the centre-right Icelandic government led by the eurosceptic Independence Party resigned following mass protests following the collapse of the island's economy. The Social Democrat Alliance and Left-Green Movement formed an interim government under Johanna Sigurdardottir. The Social Democrat Alliance is eager to start negotiations with the European Union regarding membership and adoption of the Euro. Their partner the Left-Green Movement wants a referendum about EU membership and whilst the Social Democrats have said they will honour this analysts predict this result will place pressure on the Left-Green Movement.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">The Social Democratic Alliance is allied with the Left-Green Movement.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="202" id="202" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 3</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">A Boeing 737 with 69 people on board safely made an emergency landing at Vnukovo Airport in Moscow Russia on Saturday after the crew noticed excessive vibrations in the aircraft's left engine shortly upon takeoff. There were no reports of injuries or damage. The airplane circled around the airport to burn spare fuel in order to make the landing safer according to Interfax. Fire crews and ambulances were at the scene when the jet landed. "After the plane took off a vibration of the left engine was detected after which it was decided to return back to Vnukovo" (Translated from Russian) a spokesperson for the airport told Interfax. "The airplane made an emergency landing. None of the 69 people on board were hurt." The plane had taken off from Vnukovo and was en route to Sochi on the Black Sea.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">69 people were injured during an emergency landing at Vnukovo Airport in Moscow.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Contradiction</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="203" id="203" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 4</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">A court in Paraguay has completed its trial over the worst fire disaster the country has ever seen. The Ycuá Bolaños supermarket fire in Asunción left 374 dead 450 others injured and nine missing presumed dead. Store owner Juan Pio Paiva 64 received 12 years imprisonment whilst his son Daniel Paiva 40 was given 10 years. A security guard Daniel Areco was given a five-year sentence while three business associates of the Paivas were cleared of any criminal activity.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Daniel Paiva was born in Paraguay.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Neutral</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="204" id="204" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 5</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">A team of European and American astronomers say that a recently discovered extrasolar planet located not far from Earth contains oceans and rivers of hot solid water. The team discovered the planet Gliese 436 b which is roughly the size of Neptune using the Geneva Observatory and it is roughly 33 light-years away from Earth. "The water is frozen by the pressure but it's hot. It's a bit strange — we are used to water changing conditions because of temperature but in fact water can also be solidified by pressure. It's not a very welcoming planet" said one of the astronomers who discovered the planet Frederic Pont.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Gliese 436 b was found by scientists from America and Europe.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="205" id="205" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 6</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Brazil Denunciations of political corruption threaten the Brazilian government. The most recent case involves a deputy of the political party PTB (who supports the government of the Brazilian President Luiz Inácio Lula da Silva) in a scandal of the services of post office. Lula's government representatives said that they will investigate all the denunciations and affirmed that the government is a victim of political enemies.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Luiz Inácio Lula da Silva is a member of PTB.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Neutral</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="206" id="206" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 7</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">The explosion happened at about 9:45pm local time at the 'Rizk Plaza' shopping mall. It is understood from local media that a bomb was placed in the underground parking area below the complex although there has been no official confirmation from security services. Sources on the ground say that the actual commercial center occupied the ground floor with upper stories occupied by inhabited apartments. Located in the Metn range of mountains east of Beirut Broummana is about half-hour's drive from the capital and is popular with tourists particularly those from the Gulf states.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Beirut is near Broummana.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="207" id="207" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 8</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Fitzpatrick (42) of Larkfield Close Lucan Co Dublin pleaded guilty to fraud and making a false report to gardai at his store on June 13 2007 at the Dublin Circuit Criminal Court. Judge Martin Nolan called it a "case of desperation" and sentenced Fitzpatrick to two years suspended for three years. Garda Claire O'Malley told the court she responded to a call from Mr Fitzpatrick and found him standing outside his shop in a distressed state. He showed her the empty clothes railings and said two men had come in and ordered him to go into the back office. He said they told him to stay there while they took €20000 worth of clothes. He claimed he emerged 30 minutes later and phoned gardai. Two witnesses reported seeing the men load the clothes into a white van and were able to give gardai the registration number.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Fitzpatrick is accused of robbery.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Contradiction</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="208" id="208" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 9</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Brazilian federal police arrested Jesse James Hollywood aged 25 in Saquarema city Rio de Janeiro on March 8. James had been sought by the FBI for more than four years. According to the police he was living in Saquarema with a woman who is pregnant. His arrest occurred while they were in a mall. James was deported to the United States for trial. The two countries do not have a formal extradition treaty.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Jesse James was arrested in Hollywood.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Contradiction</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="209" id="209" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 10</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Since breaking off from San Francisco local legends mk Ultra Vanderslice has produced six critically-acclaimed albums. His most recent Emerald City was released July 24th. Titled after the nickname given to the American-occupied Green Zone in Baghdad it chronicles a world on the verge of imminent collapse under the weight of its own paranoia and loneliness. David Shankbone recently went to the Bowery Ballroom and spoke with Vanderslice about music photography touring and what makes a depressed liberal angry.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Emerald City is a part of the Green Zone.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Contradiction</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="210" id="210" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 11</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">State Emergency Service (SES) volunteers are doorknocking and advising residents to leave. Bruce Gunn from the Queensland cyclone warning centre says the cyclone will coincide with a high tide. "We are talking seawater a couple of metres above the high-tide mark possibly more than that with waves on top so this is a very serious situation we are talking about" he said. Mr Gunn told the ABC that severe weather will be experienced several hours before the cyclone reaches the coast. "While we are saying the coastal crossing will be between 7 a.m. and 9 a.m. AEST the few hours leading up to that will be rather bumpy not very nice to experience" he said.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Bruce Gunn was raised in Queensland.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Neutral</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="211" id="211" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 12</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Former city manager of Largo Florida and transsexual Susan Stanton has been hired as the new city manager for Lake Worth. Stanton formerly named Stephen was allegedly fired from her job as Largo's city manager in 2007 when her sex-change operation became public knowledge. "We said all along that we'd pick the best candidate regardless and that's what it's all about we wouldn't be doing our job if we didn't" said Jeff Clemons the mayor of Lake Worth. He added that the city's commission voted in favor of Stanton 4 to 1.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Susan Stanton works for Lake Worth.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="212" id="212" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 13</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">British actor Daniel Craig has been confirmed as the man to follow Pierce Brosnan as the sixth James Bond. Producer Barbara Broccoli and director Martin Campbell called Craig 'a superb actor who has all the qualities needed to bring a contemporary edge to the role'. "It is a huge iconic figure in movie history and those things don't come along very often" Craig said. The role makes Craig the second Englishman to act as the British spy code-named 007 based on the famed literary character created by novelist Ian Fleming in 1953.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">James Bond is a British citizen.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="213" id="213" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 14</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">NAOSC is an Alberta-based oil company founded in 2001. It manages 1110 square kilometres of oil sands leases located in northern Alberta. It is estimated that the NOASC oil sands hold approximately 2.2 billion barrels of oil reserves. The company is planning to develop an extraction project and an upgrading facility. When the project is completed NAOSC expects it to produce over 200000 barrels of bitumen per day. The upgrading facility would then process the bitumen into synthetic crude oil.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">NAOSC is located in Alberta.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="214" id="214" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 15</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">In March of 2007 Wikimedia was named in a lawsuit filed in Superior Court of Monmouth New Jersey along with 20 other defendants which included operators of the Absolute Write web site and the Science Fiction and Fantasy Writers of America who authored the list. Wikinews has learned that Bauer's Wikipedia article was deleted some time during the course of the proceedings along with the edit history of her article and its talk page as a "courtesy." During the investigation Wikinews found that all edits to her article and edits to pages requesting it to be deleted were deleted by Wikipedia administrator MaxSem.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Fantasy Writers of America is an operator based in New Jersey.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Neutral</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="215" id="215" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 16</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Australia's emergency telephone service triple-0 which is operated by Telstra has been lost in Southern New South Wales and the Australian Capital Territory following damage to two optical fibre cables. It is believed that in two separate incidents optical fibre cables were cut at Gundagai and Narrandera in Southern NSW. In addition to the loss of the triple-0 service 34 mobile base stations in the region have also been affected. According to Telstra local calls are still possible and they recommend that people dial their local fire ambulance or police station in case of an emergency.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Narrandera is situated in Australia.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="216" id="216" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 17</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">A suicide attacker detonated a bomb near the home of a prominent Pakistani Shia Muslim cleric in Karachi yesterday killing the cleric and two other people police said. The death of Allama Hassan Turabi is likely to raise tensions in Karachi which is often the scene of violence between Shias and Sunnis. Allama Turabi had narrowly escaped an attempt on his life in April 2006 when a bomb was exploded just after his car crossed the area. He was the leader of a Shia party Islami Tehreek Pakistan and a vice provincial chief for Mutahida Majlis-e-Amal Sindh (MMA) an opposition religious coalition.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Allama Hassan Turabi was a member of the Pakistani Shia Muslim in Karachi.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="217" id="217" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 18</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Since premiering on March 26 1973 YR has become a worldwide cultural institution in its own right racking up an impressive 100 Emmy Awards between the writers producers cast and crew since 1974. The show has aired in over 100 countries including Australia New Zealand France Germany Italy and Turkey and reaches a worldwide audience of ten million daily. So far-reaching was YR's appeal that Romanian gymnast Nadia Comaneci chose the serial's theme song as accompanying music to her floor exercises at the 1976 Summer Olympics. In Australia where YR has aired since 1974 the show was canceled by the original network that aired it in 2007 prompting a widespread fan backlash in that country. It was quickly moved to a pay channel.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Nadia Comaneci is a native of Romania.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="218" id="218" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 19</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">PepsiCo has acquired Poland's Star Foods a leading maker of snacks for an undisclosed sum. The deal strengthens its position in Poland in snacks sales such as potato chips. More than half of PepsiCo's total sales is from snacks less than 20% is from soft drinks. Star Foods was selling potato chips under the brand Star Chips and corn snacks under the brand Mr. Snaki. Star Foods was privately held by the Mitzalis family Advent International Copernicus Capital Partners and Cazolico S.A.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">PepsiCo holds Star Foods.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="219" id="219" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>
  <div class="card shadow  mb-3 border-info text-center">
    <div class="card-header">Question 20</div>
    <div class="card-body">
      <h5 class="card-title">Premise</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Garnett scored 15 points in the fourth quarter with 13 of those points coming in the final 6:20 of the period. "It's just about being a presence" Garnett said. "It's about making them have to deal with me. I will continue to take that approach." In addition to his 44-point night Garnett helped his team by not turning the ball over at all during the game. Such a performance was not the case for Steve Nash who turned the ball over an uncharacteristic five times during the game. The Suns had 14 turnovers as a team. It was a case of Garnett and the Timberwolves taking full advantage of the mistakes the Suns made and turning it into an opportunity to win. However the loss certainly didn't leave the Suns or their coach Mike D'Antoni discouraged. "We'll start another [streak]. This is fun."</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Hypoythesis</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Garnett plays for the Timberwolves.</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Relation</h5>
      <p class="card-text">Entailment</p>
      <h5 class="card-title">Segment (Your response)</h5>
      <div class="form-group">
        <label for="question1"></label>
        <textarea type='text' class="form-control" name="220" id="220" rows="3"></textarea>
      </div>
      </div>
  </div>

  <button type="submit" class="btn btn-info btn-raised btn-lg btn-block" id='submitButton'>Submit</button>
  
</form>
</section>
<script language='Javascript'>turkSetAssignmentID();</script>

     

</body>
</html>

<script src="https://code.jquery.com/jquery-3.3.1.slim.min.js" integrity="sha384-q8i/X+965DzO0rT7abK41JStQIAqVgRVzpbzo5smXKp4YfRvH+8abtTE1Pi6jizo" crossorigin="anonymous"></script>
<script src="https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/popper.js/1.14.6/umd/popper.min.js" integrity="sha384-wHAiFfRlMFy6i5SRaxvfOCifBUQy1xHdJ/yoi7FRNXMRBu5WHdZYu1hA6ZOblgut" crossorigin="anonymous"></script>
<script src="https://stackpath.bootstrapcdn.com/bootstrap/4.2.1/js/bootstrap.min.js" integrity="sha384-B0UglyR+jN6CkvvICOB2joaf5I4l3gm9GU6Hc1og6Ls7i6U/mkkaduKaBhlAXv9k" crossorigin="anonymous"></script>
]]>
</HTMLContent>
<FrameHeight>0</FrameHeight>
</HTMLQuestion>